You
I've been missing in my sleep
She's gutting the trout, he's eating the steak
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Oh Paige, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight
Truths get told, it goes unfold, we stir the soul with a tea, serve cold
Panels be poppin', trolls be droppin', spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love, Lola, Rudy, Marble's fan from above
It's like we awake and step in the flame, we call you truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's soul-deep play, now grab your tea and slay the dead
Excuse me. Hey guys, what's up? Hi. Okay. Well, I don't know people left during that. I mean, it's just the introduction
So I'll take my speaker one second
Happy thursday
It is thursday. It is uh seven twenty fours my brother's
Nevermind. Let's see. I need to send this text message real quick. How are you guys doing?
I hope that you're having a great day.
I woke up at like five in the afternoon, let me see.
Let's see, I need to write my brother a message.
Hi guys, hey Samantha.
How are you guys doing today?
So I was on TikTok earlier.
I'm starting to do a short,
no, TikTok is very different than YouTube.
I don't know if you,
or familiar, but basically you just do school.
I mean, it's like, so most of the people
that will come to the thing, or those schools,
I mean, I school through most people.
You know, different people are looking for different things,
but, you know, people will find me.
I did more readings there than I do on the YouTube show,
because I do quicker, I do just do one card readings,
I do people have a question, I'll pull a card.
And,
It works. It's working. I actually said I have 100% more
Viewers than
Similar channels or similar. So I'm already I don't know. It's just going really well
It's going really well and we'll see how that goes, but I'm also YouTube's going really well
I hope you guys had a fun night last night, you know, it was a little bit crazy with
With you know, Crucible Ghost and you know, a large donation now is like, you know what?
let him run the panel like he wants to run the panel tonight.
And, you know, he did donate quite a large amount.
And so I did feel like that was fair,
but some people were like,
oh, you're not controlling your show,
but I mean, people will just say anything.
So yeah, I was, I was sitting next to,
I mean, if it was like going against TOS,
but I have no problem letting somebody like, you know,
here, you run the panel like you want, you know.
I'll sit there and help you, but I thought it was a good idea.
Anyway, I did receive some very nice donations,
and I will be putting these right into the show.
I have some equipment to upgrade and stuff.
I need to get maybe a new computer.
I'll just have to see.
But I just want to thank Crucible Ghost.
But we'll do it, you know, I
Don't know. I think I the problem with crucial goes
That he was not a really problem, but it's like he just can't make up his mind to see what the person on or not and so
you know
Some people were gonna kind of getting mad, but you know what?
It's just a temporary, you know
But people are kind of judgmental against me. I think I don't know maybe cuz
I think it must be a sign. I'm doing pretty well though, right?
So here's tricks. I'm here with Trixie Trixie there. Hi. There's an alien over there
Yeah, I'm hoping spunky gets here today because spunky ordered me on Amazon
She got me some really cool new cards on my wishlist
They're called the true prime cards. They haven't looked at them or opened them yet because I
Want to do it with her?
Hey, babe, you see the move back yet. So there's Mr. Tricks. Hi guys. Yeah, hi
Yeah, so on a TikTok I had like over I had a hundred and one at one hour
You know
Well, the first half hour my microphone was on and nobody was telling me and so people were just coming in
No one was saying a word and someone finally said, oh, we can't hear you. Oh fuck
It didn't have my headphones on or anything
And so then I put them on and then people started to talk.
So yeah, that would say that's an important thing.
Make sure your sound is working, okay?
But also it's a different audience there.
I think it is kind of maybe like, you know,
there's a lot of people in their 20s and stuff,
like there's some younger people.
And so they like the fast paced readings
and YouTube for different reasons.
And they go to TikTok.
The TikTok, you go to Doom School.
Hey Trevor, hi, what's up?
You go to Doom School there.
find attractive people and chat on that with them.
So, I'm a little bit different on TikTok,
but it seems like people are interested,
I'm getting a lot of followers, I have almost 500.
When I get a thousand followers,
I will be able to do some more stuff,
maybe slightly monetize,
and then at 10,000, you are monetized.
Hey, Christine, how are you?
Christine, I never showed you,
but I did do a tarot card and I still have to redesign it.
This is just a rough draft, right?
But look, did you ever see this?
This is for Christine.
I'm sorry if it doesn't look exactly.
Maybe if you sent me a picture,
I could put it into the AI, I could look more like you.
But yeah, there's Fawzi and Christine.
I hope you like that.
That's cute, huh?
And I have summer too, do you wanna see summers?
Oh, you heard I did?
Oh, here's summers.
Summers is more loosely based on her, I think.
There we go, but uh
Yeah, it's got neck neck tattoos and stuff. Um, this is kind of loosely based on page
Okay, this is loosely based on beta
Here's our crucible goes do you see crucible goes this one's funny the hangman
And DJ Electra
Which I did put in her avatar photo to come up with that one. So pretty interesting, huh?
It's cute, huh?
Nick let's take a Karen your hair is always a messy, but okay. I'll put I'll put the messy bun in there
Yeah, I know it's it kind of looks like
Who you receive a show picket fences
There's a so-called picket fence that took place in like Wisconsin and there's six the mother on the show played it
She's like a doctor, right? I think she's a doctor and
It kind of looks like her that blonde hair. Yeah, okay, but I think it's on the right track
It also did some of me like here's the magician card. That's kind of me
And this one kind of is too but it's not that this one is like
When I was in high school, maybe with it as a fool, right? But this one is kind of like me now a little bit more
But having fun designing this deck
with you know, I have the upgraded chat GPT chat GPT upgraded is
This is a shit nurse ratchet. Okay. I'll put nurse ratchet. Nah
Once lower the cuckoo's in the song yeah, that's pretty classic
Yeah, guys, it's like a Karen. Yeah
That blonde perfectly blonde hair
I'll work on I'll work on it. So maybe maybe you know, I think the people that are in the deck
I think maybe I would like maybe them to send me a photo
So I can put into the AI if they want to if not, I'll just do my best, you know, but I'm not
perfect at describing
Translating the looks into compute. I'm trying trying messy bun with a sundress, you know, like the nurses nurses uniform
You were uniform like that
Scrubs, I like to scrub but it's a higher fit and so it's kind of like I say, you know kind of close to God, right?
You just came to my mind for that. So
Okay
Having a little so yeah, I did I guess I have a fun day on tiktok today. I
Had I said I would I did really well with my I'm gaining a lot of followers
I did a lot of readings because they're quick readings and people will just ask the question
And it's kind of like I kind of like it like that like how people here will want them will go on a more
serious reading of the one like a longer reading a little bit longer reading, right and
you know a little bit more focused on attention and
Ticktocks are very happy with you pulling one card and giving my rundown of the question
of course I was having trouble I was I couldn't figure out for God that he was a
A let's just call it. He's a labradoodle. And so I was like make it look like a multi poo and that was wrong
And then I said and then a cock a poo and that was wrong. So I have a few rough drafts of it, too
but yeah
It's very cute. Oh and the chat tpt also it keeps mentioning fozzy. It's like he's making like it's so funny
It's like chat tpt remembers what you tell it and then it will meant to bring it up on different
On different questions, I have nothing to do with it because it's very conversational. It'll say, yeah, it'll say
Oh, I don't know, it's something I can kind of cue. But you're welcome. I
Planned to do this deck. I don't know if there'll be so much YouTube theme that it was coming trying to do before
It's trying to do a panel burst theme deck and that's a little bit too niche
I would say even though yeah, I mean it will be, you know, he looks more like a golden doodle. Okay. I'll let
Catch you PT now. We'll work on it
But uh, yeah, it had a little bit more panel and I will like you know
I'm sure like a lot of panel versus people will enjoy this deck and maybe like, you know
Remember all the people that were like, oh, we're doing a blank awakens tarot
Maybe they'll get a deck and then they can use a psyche awakens deck or something like that
There are like a lot of people that there's a guy named intuitive Kev. He's a reader
Very good reader and he designed a deck and it's very it's a good deck too. It has them
It's a unique deck. It has like different things like, you know, like the
the
What's one of them? They have like, you know
Demon or different archetypes of people you are in a terror deck. Yeah, you are Chris. Yeah, I'll put you in that too
But I want to put a lot of panel versus people and but yeah, but a guy who'd have to have me in a deck
And it's just like a lot of people. Oh
You're gonna try to find the terror that you are in a deck. Oh cool. Yeah, but he
You know, he did a kind of simple draw and a lot of people in the terror readers are using it and things like that
And you know, so hopefully maybe I want to find one that will be appealing to both terror readers
and also
Basically youtubers so youtubers terror readers
And then the couple niches like you know the panel verse where I have a lot of my friends are gonna be on cards, right?
Supporters of the show so it goes without a card, you know
Pretty much everybody has been a very generous very generous and helpful to the show
And so I really want to give a little thank you with some people and you know
If you if you would like a card to you and like to be on a card, you know
If then you're not if I don't select you I do I probably will at least a few open or
for maybe like
maybe for people that would like to
To donate to become to be part of it. And so I do plan on taking it seriously and producing it and
Making like, you know, probably started with like a hundred decks or something like that
Maybe 20 decks or something tell those slowly order more and more
It's pretty good process though chat GPT is really really good
It has a new amazing thing called the valet to be heard of it. So it's just came out today or the other day
and it will, basically, it can take over your computer,
which is kind of scary in a way,
but it does it in order to like,
you know, you say, book me a dentist appointment
with the best dentist in town.
It will find the best dentist in town
with the highest reviews
and it'll book you an appointment.
It will go do it itself. It will actually go work for you. It'll write letters
So like the guy with today was saying, okay
So if you want I like you can go look for 20 of the dentists in the area that have a website
And then he says, you know because you don't want to his
So if you're selling websites if you're selling designing websites professional websites or businesses and you're looking for leads
So imagine just writing, okay, so the guy today, he said,
okay, we'll find the top, find the 20 dents with websites
because people with websites are more likely
to like have a bad website,
and also more likely to want to have a good website.
And then it's like, and then it will go
and it will research the dentist
and figure out that he likes pickleball
and it'll write like a personal, almost stalkerish letter.
You're on the Hierophant, you found the part,
okay, you found the post, I'll show it sometime.
Oh cool.
Yeah, that's what Christine's card is the Hierophant and it's interesting like a female Hierophant
Like I do see the and also I would look at my this deck the rainbow deck and has a
Patec I think the female Pope
so there is like a female
very similar to the
The I would say the high priestess card
But I like that female in the role the Pope might be a Pope Joan a little bit. It was a female Pope
I don't know how successful that she was but
Anyway, but I hope you have a great day. I had a good I had a good week
I was able to get a lot of stuff done. I have like a lot of
Wow, I've uh, I have some car decks of cards on the way another five decks
So I've increased by 10 decks of cards. Thanks to Timo like under 50 bucks pretty cool, huh?
Amazing amazing deal on cards there
So your story it was just held all the keys to heaven
And if only a person was worthy,
we'd give them their keys.
Well, that sounds like the keys to the kingdom.
That sounds like Jesus a little bit.
Jesus, after he was crucified, supposedly went to hell,
he had the keys to hell.
Also, other people have been said to have the keys to hell.
I think in the Revelation that says Apollyon,
who's Apollo, he's another word for Apollo.
He's kind of like an evil angel in Revelations,
but Apollo.
He's a god of god of basically light
Basically, he's loose for right
Okay
Yeah, but I do believe like in Buddhism too and so you boost them
They talk a lot about emptying out the hells and like locking the door behind it when it's all emptied out
So yeah, I would like to liberate the hells. I would I would love it just empty hells like with nobody there
Just abandoned hells and everybody
Sending to the higher planes, right?
I do believe it's possible, but I think there's still some people there right now
They have to wait a little bit. Did I get the card? Oh, help me. You sent me cards. I
Didn't but thank you so much as you you might want to check
I think you can check your order and see if they've been
When they were
When they're to be delivered, they might be in back order or something, but I haven't but thank you
I don't know. I don't know if you were saying if you were yeah, so um, I'm spunky did give me a deck of oh you did
Oh, thank you. I appreciate that. I got a deck from spunky yesterday. It is called the where are they?
Yeah, they're called the true crime cards. They're coming this little box. There's kind of special cards
I can't wait to break those out to you, but hey garbage bill kids are coming
I don't know. Maybe they'll be here today. He said I'm on Tuesday. Okay
Probably today or tomorrow. Yeah
Thank you so much. That was so thoughtful of you incredibly thoughtful, and thanks. Hell Billy
Hope everyone's doing great today. Like I said, I woke up from blade in the afternoon and I
Went into the tick tock live. Thank you so much. I can't wait to break those up. That's gonna be cool. I can't wait
You need to hit a lick potato head Harry you do which one, you know, who do you like to hit as a lick?
I mean, it's like a rob somebody, right?
I think that's what it means.
I'm not sure.
I know a little bit of this ghetto slang,
living in Los Angeles.
But yeah, thank you, everybody.
I mean, so many, the hell Billy,
and thank you, Spunky, whenever she's here.
I do wanna, hierophant, driven mad by the high priestess.
She thinks redemption by collecting the keys.
Persuaded, they are all the keys to heaven,
and only she can grant access to the living with them.
Okay.
So that's what that was out of your cars. That's the story of your car. Okay, you drove that you drove the the Pope mad
That's the high priestess and then now you are the pope and
Collecting the keys. Yeah, well, do you know the cross keys that the Vatican on the flag? I think there are cross keys that is the
so there's something to do with keys and and
St. Peter's Basilica, right? Hey, Gotti. How are you? Ziggy would like a reading absolutely?
Yeah, that's pretty cool though. I'd give a friend that does the tarot. It sounds like they're pretty
they're pretty
Proficient and knowledgeable
God you get to see yeah
Yeah, you have a skeleton keys. Yes. There's a good movie called a skeleton key too. It's about voodoo in a way
But it's really interesting. It's kind of like about
There's these black black voodoo practitioners
They take over the bodies of the white people and so it's kind of like it's kind of like a reverse version of get out
Right, it's like instead of like the black the white people will take it up or the white people taking the black people's brains
It's like the black people taking the white people's
bodies
So, oh cool you the community theater you thought it's a voodoo movie. Yeah, it's very good
Yeah, they talk about red brick dust and how and different stuff and
It's pretty interesting.
I think you might enjoy that if you guys check that out.
Hey, Ziggy's here, you know the reading?
You need a link, okay, come on up Ziggy.
You did dinner theater?
Nice.
I did a couple of community theater plays.
I did Sugar, which is like something I get hot.
I played in Bye Bye Birdy as Mr. McAfee,
and I played in one called Once Upon a Mattress,
which is like Princess and a Pea.
I think I had Carol Burnett in the original
performance of that one and
It's a kind of a comedy princess of the P
So I did a little bit of theater. You were in by my birdie. I play mr. McAfee
So is Alisa Alisa Jordana was in by the bird she's like him kid McAfee. Okay. Here's the key
Hey, how are you good? How's it going today? I'm a little upset
Tell me what's going on
I had the okay, so do you know Jim Brewer is?
Yeah, that he's like the goat boy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Half-baked it's up right but he was saying some crazy shit and it was relative to me and he was saying
You like how tell me okay? Yeah, so his brother died. I'm gonna do long story short his brother died
And his brother talked to him, you know, through prayer or whatever.
Okay.
I don't, I don't believe in prayer, right?
But I'm the type that I had a dream, right, where I'm like hanging over my grandmother
and she's alive in a casket, right?
What like I'm forced like she's dying
Mm-hmm, and I'm like
Why is she in the casket? I don't understand and I'm like I love you
You're the best thing I ever fucking had in my life. I'm crying. Whatever and
Then I had to walk away, you know, like what the fuck give me cards on give me cards on that
What the fuck is happening? Oh, I will but I will but I'll first talk to you about is your grandmother passed away, right?
She passed away. She's alive. She's alive. Okay. Well, okay. She's alive. Okay, so but you know, she how old is she?
You know, I just want to like get an idea of like
She helped me and like or she quite old
Yeah, she's old. Yeah, of course, so it's like
Basically, it's like I don't think it's necessarily a force. I mean she will pass away, of course
Like my grandmother passed away probably like the music now 2010 and like my aunt was always still broken up about it
I was her daughter and yeah, I'm like, yeah
But my sister was like well, she's like Aunt Harry
Grandma would be well into her hundreds, but like right now if she was to live just so it's like it
You know, I'm sure people don't want to live that long
So I think it is maybe preparing you mentally for the inevitable of that, but I'll post the cards for it
Yeah, for sure, but you know, it's all
We went like worry about it. I mean, don't do it. Will you do me one favor? Yeah
We not do, like, Star Wars cards. Can you do, like, the real cards?
Yeah, I'll do the writer wait. I mean, they're the alien. I don't have a Star Wars deck, by the way.
I don't know what you keep saying. I don't have a Star Wars deck. That was what somebody said.
You had Star Wars?
No, somebody wanted to buy me one, and I was like, well, I'm not a big fan of Star Wars, and so I think I chose this one.
No, this is actually actually sensitive to me man, you know, oh, no, I know I know it. No, I'm taking I'm taking it very serious
But I mean, I mean, what do you like Princess Leia's at the same time? Yeah, I do
Okay, and so see this almost like okay, so this is what we have right here. This is the six of stores six of stores is like
You know, it almost reminds me of Kairon like a soul making passage and I bet it's also a nicer place
It's like, you know, the world is not easy place and especially when you're older
It's more difficult and so it is like going to smoother waters
I would think the heaven it looks very heavenly there and it's like, you know
She's got the fairy man, which is like, you know, Kairon is an increase mythology
He's like the fairy man who takes you to River six that takes you to the land of the dead
And also I see like this kingly energy is like the another king. I think this is maybe probably your energy this like where it's like
master your passions and
you know also
I can see it. I know it will be very it will be upsetting, right? It will be upsetting
But I think your body's no, I'm really good with that. I was in the military. I take it. I can take it
Right, but it's different. It's different. It's a grandmother's a little bit different. You know, it's like a grandmother
You have these childhood stuff. Okay, so we also have the Hierophant right here, which is like, you know
It's definitely going to God like see the Hierophant is pointing up right there, right to heaven, right? It's like and so
I think can I can I tell you a little you know I was like in the dream I was
like hugging her and I was kissing her on the cheek and I'm like you were the
best thing that ever happened to me oh thank you and I love you and then like
these people like pushed me off and like to get me you know I had to go for you
know it was like fucking weird yeah
Well, you know what it's like also, I think it's maybe some kind of mental preparation for
Demons you think it's demons. Oh, yeah
Yeah, but you mess with demons, so if you're if you're if you're habits your symbol like a basically a
Symbol, right? What is that?
I post
Okay, yeah, here's so, you know a lot of these symbols are you know
They are ancient gods. They were actually got some of them were gods and now they're gonna. Thank you. Thank you
I'm glad that you like that
But you know God's God's with a lowercase g is kind of like, you know, the demigods
No, well, well, okay, be sure to tell them that it's lowercase g
Yeah, capital D dog. Yeah, they know they already know like they are that's one thing that the demons are afraid of is God
You know, it's like they because
Because it's a dog
Dog backwards, but yeah, but yeah, I posted the dog, right? He's a new this right and so
God is a dog
No, okay. Well, anyway, but like okay, so I knew this is actually a dog headed dog headed funerary
VAT that you know ways that helps you helps with the weighing of the of the soul against the feather and
He's a black dog and and so
Black what's the funny about black? Yes? Yes? Yes? Yes? You should you should explain what I post is
Well, I suppose is you know, he is the new this he is basically one of the fallen fallen angels
That now is pretty much
Trapped under humanity like his god put humanity over the demons right so took rule over the demon and so my god man
Yeah, so they're mad right you heard about okay, so
I don't know what she's talking about, but yeah.
I mean, I've said it, I've said it.
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, they're talking about, they're talking about Clinton
and Uga, Uga, Billy, I don't know who those people are.
So I'm not sure, but I'm, I was trying to say it.
So there's a book called The Go-Aisha.
Have you, have you said you'd Go-Aisha, right?
Hmm, more sure.
Okay, you said you'd Go-Aisha.
I mean, how, how seriously, like how, like, did you,
like do the ceremonial with all the, with the tools
and things like that?
Like that's serious?
Oh, everything, everything.
Okay, so you almost are identifying with this deity at this point.
Well, no, I'm his servant. Okay, because well because you won't be part of his invocations invocations is calling in the energy of
If he if he really don't believe me like the only no, no, no, no, I believe I believe you
I'm just I'm just a tattoo on me that that emblem is tattooed on me. Yeah, sure. Sure. Okay. Yeah, I have a tattoo
I have a tattoo as well. No, you know of a symbol as well
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Do it there's a couple ways to do it like that
But anyway, and now to bed and Buddhism it is actually a mudra for
For the spelling demons spunky. Yes with him spunky. Look at him. I cannot wait to spunky. Look
Spunky spunky. I love sparkle. Oh, she's married
Back can't hit on her
I haven't opened it yet. I mean, I haven't looked at them yet. I'm excited but I was like, what are these?
I got it and it said I opened it. It says true crime oracle cards. And so whatever are you ready for?
Why are you laughing?
Yeah, I mean I asked what is funny man like she's funny shit a lot
I mean, I asked for these car. I mean, I really want these cars because they were
I've seen them be used and other shows and stuff because there's some there's like a lot of like they're weird
There's a lot of criminal stuff going on where they can relate to specific things in the and criminal justice and and so yeah, it's not like
But what is criminal justice? Is criminal justice justice for the criminals or the justice for the human, I don't know, is criminal justice in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a, in a,
There's always justice with crimes. I mean even if people but they
When people steal they people steal it is like the money loses its value first of all because first of all
I think they're gonna steal more right it's like an unlimited amount of money to steal the second of all because and that's not appreciated
Third of all, it just tends to burn.
It just tends to just burn up instantly.
It just tends to be spent very, very quickly.
It's not good to hold on to it, especially.
Oh, you're talking about government now.
No, I'm talking about criminality in general.
There's always going to be a karmic.
Were you not ever a criminal?
I was a, I've been a criminal.
Like, I've stolen out of a store.
Criminal as in you know people there's like violent crimes. There's non-violent crimes. There's like shoplifting from a store
There's there's stealing from somebody's garage or their house or their bank account
Right and so there's different kinds of there's different things like for example like any kind of any kind of supermarket or store
You use you would steal from is insured and so that's written into the price of the
You're doing the insurance thing. Yeah, okay. That's what the
No, it is true
That's where you're talking about the nine hundred dollar if you if you go after nine hundred dollars plus
Yeah, I get where you know nowadays you can in Los Angeles you can like have up to like $500 and they'll just let you go right?
And I think you'll stick let's take this up from you if you catch you right, but it's not not not five
I think it's nine. Oh, maybe nine. Yeah, maybe it's even more. Yeah, so is that any kind of like deterrent against people like running into
Now everything's locked up at all the stores now on like Friday
You have to like ask for them to unlock the toothpaste case and stuff like that. So
South Park did I want to see that is that is that okay? Is it on paramount or is it on?
On the comedy set comedy central because South Park does have some Paramount specials right now
Love South Park. Fuck. Yeah, what watch watch the at what's on Paramount? I'm networked. They have some specials
They'd have like hour-long or even longer specials. They did of them
They did of it didn't want for the COV ID thing. They did one for
Something else is there's actually really good head-on deck. Okay, so Sponky has a Joker face after her name. Oh, yeah
funky Joker face
Eraser rain watch the newest episode. Okay, so it's on gonna be on comedy central
It's gonna be the newest episode on comedy
Rain already has it fuck fuck you. I want to see it all right. You're gonna see I think you can see it too
I think it's on thought you said so you go watch it. No, I'm gonna have to watch it otherwise, dude
I'm poor now
You can probably find it
Online you probably find out. No, I don't know. Yeah, would you like to know? I know where to get it
Yeah, I know where to get it
Where would you like have you ever watched movies like do you want a free movie site?
Um, you can put it in the back chat. Yeah, put it in the back chat, but I'm okay. Yeah, I do. I mean, I uh, yeah
One time I actually was using a torrent service. It was we go. Yeah, that's what I'm going with it
But I was recently I was using when I got it
I got an email from like the cable company saying like not to do that
Yeah
So fuck off like it's my own business
I should have but but there and I bet you know what but a race Iran said it's on
a razor rains that it's on paramount so what you can do is I think they have
probably free trial I can't tell it can I can I tell your whole crowd like where
to go just see but I don't really want to promote like because it's vocal no it's
vocal it's not legal I don't think it's legal so I don't want to like promote it
Okay, yeah, not ch. Okay. Got you got you got you. Okay. Thank you. So
Movies
But look at you, but they don't have they won't have the South Park. It's what I'm saying. There's a free. Yes. They do
There's a free trial of Paramount Plus and they don't know so though it's not a comedy central
It's on Paramount because they have somebody's gonna record it and fucking put it on there
But you'll still get all the free movies
And shows all the way back. If you liked home improvement, boom, libidia.ch
I mean it is I mean these movies are copyrighted. I mean so it looks like it's in it. Oh, it's China. CH is China
Okay, I thought it was Czech Republic because it's like, you know, Czechoslovak, right, right? Exactly. Yeah
I've done it both. I've been in both places of and it was China and the Czech Republic and they're both amazing places
What do you do me me and fucking Jan? We watch movies all the time from there. That's great
Okay. Yeah, well I used to do movie nights on the discord. It was like with Jamie and
Irona would come and like we'd have like you know a lot of people in the chat as I get in the back chat at the
Discord
What why are you not having a movie night now?
Because it was like they were kind of difficult because it's like oh you put 12 people up probably that's what happened
But you go through you go through YouTube and some people don't have premium YouTube and so
Yeah, but TOS prevents the YouTube freedom of speech for like for you know, so does the Constitution for unprevented it from like
Right, so there would be like some people that would try to view that we like I can't be alright
I just don't know why yeah, it's got it
Well, there's no there. I mean I'm saying the only speech you really can't say you're not supposed to say nowadays
It's not free anymore. It's like, you know hate speech and the hate speech is kind of cover
Well, I mean
But it's like if you think about if they had all these racial slurs all the time and it's like because it's like that
It really does affect the culture when there's like they're so out there
I mean, I'm sure it doesn't really not really if you if you go and look up. Oh, man
What the fuck is his name?
Shit, I'm gonna fuck this up. I know it. I hope I can fucking pull it on my ass
Well, who is it? What do you do?
In con in Congress come on feel the noise
Oh, it's like
He went yeah twist the sister
He went and fucking went to Congress told the people no, this is not what it's about
It's fucking about free
Yeah, because he says that but he's not a he's not a politician. He's a razor rock star
And by the way, he's nighter actually does go to my Starbucks. Yeah, he decided. Thank you. Yeah
And let me see, what am I gonna get to eat?
I'm kinda hungry than that, I need some coffee right now.
I need some coffee.
You need fuckin' ribs, man, I need a rack of ribs.
You need some of my ribs?
No.
I don't know. I think I think I'm gonna get some Wendy's maybe because Wendy's has like these
They have coffee, you know, that was weird because
Fucking one of my buddies and I were talking about Wendy's that was weird
Wendy's is it's a good quality food. I mean it's fucking good. Yeah, it's good compared to McDonald's especially like it's like
What is it?
Junior bacon cheeseburger. Bam like that. You like that one? Okay?
I might get one of those meals and a couple coffee couple big coffees and like a maybe like a
So I decided this or something, but yeah, okay. You know what I had yesterday? I had Ziggy's coffee yesterday
It's called see it's called Ziggy's coffee. I don't see it Ziggy's coffee. He's coffee
Coffee coffee coffee. Yeah, all right. I had I had a really good one one was
one was a like a butterscotch one and one was
I forgot the other was really good though. There's a coffee coffee like comes in all kinds of fucking weird flavors
It was fancy. It was really fancy. Okay, so why do you guys do that? I
Think I'm gonna go for this later's again though because slaters is
It's a
Fucking way cheaper, but they don't have coffee their shit. Yeah, I don't know why do you guys like do that though?
Like what do you guys like?
You know flavor the coffee the coffee is like terrible black
But you're like the sky's in it
The other night I had, I had banana coffee. It was delicious. And then I mean coffee is
Of course you had banana
It was good
It was it was a b it was so funny. It's not funny. It's just banana. Like I don't know what's so funny about bananas
What they're shaped like a penises or what's what I don't understand. Well, look at the look of the chat. They know why
Okay, he likes banana coffee guys
I mean, it's actually really good.
It's like a beat in the knees.
They've banana flavored chocolate.
It's delicious.
Of course.
Yeah, I know.
For you.
It's not funny.
But if you say it like this, you have to go like, delicious.
Why do I have to do it like that?
Why do I say it like that?
No, you have to do it like that.
Like, do it like...
No, I don't like it.
Come on.
I'm a metal guy.
No, I don't feel like doing that.
Delicious.
No, I don't feel like I don't feel like talking
Okay, but let me see. Okay, so four dollars of 25 chilies see the place that the other night was like 75% off
So it's really probably maybe it's a better dip. I order both coffee and that I mean, that's like I just kind of
I'm kind of hungry. I haven't been eating that
Well, I haven't been eating pretty well, but
you know, did you ever see that movie with Andy dick where
It's I'm hungry. I'm hungry. You know, I'm talking about
He's hungry. I don't know what movie is that Andy Dick movie. I think yeah
um old school
Okay, I remember from that is like is like naked a little barrel naked, right?
No, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's like, we've got to run to the yeah
Where's we got us to a street kid?
Yeah, but Andy is in there and he's like come on girls
What are we doing tonight girls
Okay, I'm gonna get maybe bacon and maybe a big baconator or they have a junior baconator
Let's see. I don't want such a my god. They haven't
Wendy's yeah, Dave single cinema bun. They have oh, they have a son of the baconator son of the baconator two patties
Boys I got the son of the baconator. It says apple with smoke baking
What's the difference between the son of the baconator and the baconator actually baconator?
Has no okay, so they can add a half a pound of beef. That's way too much meat for me
Okay, so I'll do the son of the Baconator, which is yeah
Nine nine nine dollars, and then I'll just get a couple copies
Let me see if I can get a couple for a couple a couple coffees really. Yeah. Yeah
I just know I'm a couple big copies. Let's see. Oh shit
They have coffee frosties. Let me see they don't they don't they don't have coffee frosty
Of what kind of coffee do they have they have a
Never get the get the baconator and why don't we even see I guess I mean it I mean in a son
I'm getting the son of the baconator. I want to see coffee here. That's okay. Well, this is regular hot coffee. That's not good
Where's like the who is the son of the Baconator though like I'm not like dude Dave
That's is Wendy. This is Wendy's right. I mean, I'm gonna go to Jack in the box instead
Jack in the box has actually a deal and
Jack in the box Jack in the box. So it says build your oh, okay. I'll just do a
A sour joke he has to do better
Wendy's has to be a better on coffee. I thought they had like frosty copies. I remember that kind of before
Let me see most ordered
See some jalapenos bacon old sourdough jack. I guess I'll go sourdough jack and two coffees. That was sourdough jack
Yeah, I would go jack pretty good sourdough jack. Okay. All right, it's sourdough bread and jack cheese and
Burger patties. Oh Wendy's gonna have to fucking pull her game up more
He does he does so I know I think we have formal sweet caramel sweet cream ice coffee large
And I'll get a that's all they have a mocha sweet cream ice latte, and that will be perfect
Oh, let me see how to come to 20 it comes to 20 bucks. Okay, and then it goes plus three dollars off
right so
Okay
Yeah, I agree with Gotti. Yeah, I don't like fat shaming at all
20 minus 321
Hey, did you hear it? Yeah
What about what we don't I don't like the fat shame
But you did hear about what?
What Gotti said
Okay, that's it. Okay. Yeah, that's shaming is
What is that? Are you because I because I what a big he did last night? You're a big he did
Yeah, you hear what? No, I was I wasn't here. I wasn't here
Yeah, she yeah, what happened? I don't know
She she was sitting backstage and then she like lifted up her
Her top and then her boobs were like hanging out from underneath the top
They were like long and then she was like playing with them
and like she was laughing and it was like so it was like what it was like it was just it was crazy
it was absolutely it's I mean what happened man you you're getting the like the wild side of
everybody I know I know like Sam man's wanting like he's like my shit don't even work over here
and he's coming to you and then that's weird that's crazy
okay so now I got a job well you're doing something right think about it oh
my god you know what you are doing something right hi-tesh I haven't seen
hi-tesh in forever hello brother I haven't seen you in a long time hi-tesh is
here holy shit you must be doing something right who's hi-tesh
Oh, he's a good brother. He's a good person. Yes. Okay. Hi. Welcome. Welcome to the show. Hi, Tash
Okay, so I need to add something to this cart. So I should have mini churros. This one's pretty good mini churros or
Yeah, I'll just do mini churros a mini churros as per dessert and I will take the bill down to 18
Okay, perfect, then 20 bucks total perfect
Okay
20 bucks. Oh
Yep under 20 bucks
I might even play. I don't know. What about you, Gotti? I might even play.
See I told you see Gotti even knows hot cash. He's a good dude, man
Yeah, cool. He's a deserter of the team. Oh, I should the pervert someone said hello marketer
Oh, no, no, I just the guy. No, he's like no Justin Boyle. No Justin Boyle is like a kind of a gay guy
He's not gay, but is this guy Indian? I think I've seen this guy
He's going to show several times and he's like he's that kind of like I think he might be like that's kind of Indian
He looks kind of like
Oh, he looks kind of African, but I didn't think I got it on the show before right? I don't know but I want to
Yeah, I want to talk to spunky a spunky a little bit because I want to break out these new cards, but I'm also getting like
There's a deck
Christina Ricci has a deck called a cat full of spiders and I ordered that one from Etsy for like six bucks
Oh my god, how many decks the cars do you have?
probably almost 50 maybe over 50 now
Because I've been yeah, because I bought several when I was doing professional reading in like 2000s
I bought a lot of 2020 so I bought a lot of decks on that year and
and just
Did you see what Justin Boyle just said?
Kind of a gay. He's just a kind of a gay. I think you should I think you should block him
He didn't say like you didn't say like a blur. So it's not really defensive. I don't really care. He's a slur
Yes, it is. I'm offended
Okay
Well, I'm offended for you. Okay, so but uh, here I'm gonna talk to God. I'm gonna talk to God here real quick
So go go hang out in the chat. See y'all talk to soon. Okay. Love you. Thank you
I got it. Yo, how are you? Hey, I'm gonna invoke my
Ten minutes of free panel time. We're gonna open up the panel for ten minutes bring up. Okay, funky. Let's open up these cards
Okay, let's open up the cards
At least and then I'll pop off
Okay, ten minutes. Yeah, that's fair. That's fair. Yeah
Well, Spunky, I'll just have this because Spunky bought these cards. So they're the true crime part
I'll show you the back of them and oh, it looks really cool. They look really cool
Okay, and then here's what they look like. Yeah on the back. They're also in a really nice little
Uh, it looks like it looks like it's on like a street and like a little bit of blood on the street
Yeah, it looks like some blood. It's all a little bit red
Yeah
And so it's a little gruesome but uh like but for example this card is this card is a cigarette card
So there's a cigarette and so oh that's a good one
I've never seen a cigarette car, but it's pretty cool. So
But I was okay, so I was on tiktok, okay
And I was on tiktok and I was like, oh, yeah
I was like, you know, you can't smoke on tiktok
I was you know Emma got kicked off of tiktok for one of the reasons what one of her strikes was for smoking a vape on
Screen so I was careful and I was like, okay
So I took my vape and I was an offspring like this
and then I went back on the screen. I turned on my filter, it looked like the smoke was coming off of me,
but the smoke was coming out of my mouth anyway, and then I got up in the morning and said all the
videos have been restricted because instantly it's been restricted for tobacco use. I mean,
can you believe it? It's as far as smoke coming out of your mouth. Yeah, so you have to be really...
Yeah, I think it's because China is so anti-
Smoking or something it's kind of I'm not I don't think they are a lot of kids on this so they don't want to influence them
But what the fuck?
Well in China in China, they're allowed to do like one hour that like if you're under 18 in China
You can do an hour of tick-tock a day
You're limited to it. And also, you know how it's like would they recommend that there's like a what they recommended like that
They have a science section section on tick-tock to it called stem
But they mostly go like what you recommended and so in America it goes straight to the recommended and that's recommended
It's gonna be like twerking videos and dancing and stuff in China they go
Recommended videos are the scientific ones and they put them to that section. It's a smarter than our kids. Yeah
Okay, I'm sorry. Here you go. Here's the link smoky. That's funny. Don't we spoke more than the Chinese maybe just the Russians
There's Japanese the Japanese the Japanese were pretty big smokers. I think yeah
Yeah, well, I know they did at least but yeah Japanese also. Yeah, Japanese were also doing the first to embed math and then the
NAZI's I don't know what I read, but I think nicotine is good for you
It could be I read something
What did I read that nicotine is good
It's a nicotine isn't the harmful chemical
It's the harmful thing is the tar and so it's like the nicotine is the drug that we're yeah, but it's like it's not like
Okay, let's dig here to the open panel. He says all it's good for your blood sugars
Smoking or chewing the gum now wearing the patches
Good patches the patches the patches are good, but it's yeah
horrible nightmares though. I mean, I mean nice. I mean nice
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, nightmares are actually you're working through psychological stuff in your dreams instead of in real life
And so it can be very psychologically good for you. So like, you know, yeah
It made me have a dream that seems so real
I was in like an escape room, but it was really hell and every like problem you solved gave you like more torture
And I could feel the torture in my dream. It was such a lucid dream
It was crazy
We're your we're your ankles like chained and I
Don't believe in I don't believe in like a torturing. I don't believe God is like the type that
Have soul torture
Does yes, yeah, there's a cockroach. That's all
Well, yeah, but the cockroach even like has the has an opportunity to come back as a human
It's like you have to gain merit whatever you are
So there's a story in Buddhism about that there's a stupa a stupa is like a little Buddhist
Like a little tower and if you go around the stupa if you people walk around it
That's considered merit merit and you get and you can get some work karma of lifetimes and stuff
But there's a one time there was like it was raining and there was like a little ditch around the stupa and like a little
There's a piece of poop on it and like a little
Cockroach or like a fly landing on the piece of poop and I went around on the piece of poop
by the stupa and it had an informerit to be born as a human that's a story in buddhism and so
yeah
Wait wait, so you're saying like everybody was like born from a piece of poop
Well, we've been we've been many things and it's like to become a human in Buddhism
They consider you have to have a lot of merits. No, you're saying it evolved. That's what you're saying
No, we go through evolution, but we even go through evolution as a human being
We start as like what a spur a spur which is a sort of zoid a sort of spur of toes though
Which is like a it's basically like a tadpole and it goes into a reptilian phase and the woman it goes
Then it goes finally to finally it's born the mammalian, right?
It is amazing
I love watching something like that.
They go through like the whole fallopian tubes and it's like the whole birth process and look who's talking
You ever see that movie with the baby John Travolta. Yeah. Yeah, but he plays the baby
But then the beginning of the movie
They do like a whole like inside the body where it's like this you see the sperm going there
All those from our racing and they go to the egg and it fertilize the egg and then the baby grows and stuff like that
It's pretty amazing. Yeah, so you know how you predicted the whole cooking was gonna die a few days ago, and then he did
Justin is now in an anxiety induced hermit phase and cleaning his house because he thinks he's gonna like die on the 26th
No, no, I said to be wary of the 26th. I didn't say he was gonna die on the 26th. Oh
My god, he's he's panicking
If you put it be breathing whole hood death, and I don't believe his death
I think the whole Kogan is fakes his death and it was the whole
Third wait for the third person because it was right. He was the first two the first you
Who now come
Yeah
Ozzy and Theo
Okay
It sounds like a
Psyop to me today some guy. What the fuck was his name? Oh Joe Joe died Joe who Joe mama
hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahah
Good one, good one.
Right when I said Joe, who I knew was gonna come,
I knew was gonna come.
Yeah boy, I wear a suit definitely wear a suit. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Hey, can you meet y'all you don't play songs for God?
Yeah, I will play this though
There we go. Okay. Okay. Thanks. Thanks for got it. Okay, so it's bunky. I'll do them. I'll just show you the cards now
Let's see. Okay, true crime cards
Bless you
Yeah, that's funny and weird though one day you're up another down right back from that bottom. I know that because
It was like this
Kind of like the Pope a little bit.
Okay, so should I refree you?
I'll refree you then.
I'll refree you, this will be for you.
But it's like, but it is true crime.
And so I think like this is like a supplementary deck
like, cause I don't want, it would be probably like
kind of negative stuff on here,
but stuff to look out for a bit.
Cause we're all, you know, criminality is a very
broad subject, cause the first car was cigarette.
Okay, so let me see.
So this car.
What do you come up with? We come up with an airplane. We have the airplanes for you. Okay, so there's an airplane going to be involved.
I don't know flying somewhere, going on vacation.
I don't know smuggling. I'm sure you're not into that.
There's an airplane involved, an airplane involved. And then what do we have? We have a cemetery. So maybe
Flying to go somewhere and visiting the cemetery there. I don't know
Yeah, we always look at them at night and we've had some weird occurrences
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I know like a lot of people like to hang out in cemeteries. Okay. Yeah
Okay, we also have casino
Okay
So maybe you know some some money to see don't maybe I'm going to Vegas and
Visiting a cemetery here at the casino, and we got the cigarette again. I don't do you smoke
I just vape
You vape. Okay
Well, maybe are you allowed to smoke in casinos still? I think yeah. Yeah, you are. Yeah. Okay
Well, I like these cards a lot. These are awesome. I mean, we have drug the drug
Just be so I would say just watch watch your dreams
Or if you know you you do in vibe recreationally, you know, you're always always be aware and then
We have handcuffs. Oh
So
Just hopefully this isn't about like, you know smuggling drugs to somewhere
Yeah, just maybe avoid avoid that, you know
I think the handcuffs will be more of a kink, you know, I since more of a kink of handcuffs with the handcuffs then
Any kind of thing harmful, so don't worry about it. It's like, you know
He'll get get get make sure you get the fuzzy ones though the pink fuzzy ones, right?
Yes
They're a little bit softer on the on the ink. Actually when I was arrested the police always put the uh
Put the handcuffs on so tight because I've looked at my wrist are holding you have to my wrist are they're like very
Then okay, so
And I can go like this yeah, I see my tiny little wrist a watch with watches will not fit me like a little yeah
So yeah, I'm little tiny like little little wrist. Okay, but
Yeah, they put it on so tight my I'd always be bleeding on my my wrist and you you yeah back of me
Let's pull three cards for back of Matt with the true crime. Okay
No, I got you back. That's that's it. You don't you don't give me back. I just got you back. Okay. Okay, so one second
Okay, okay, so
Okay, so bathroom that we have the incinerator incinerator so maybe like burning something or burning
I don't know burning evidence or something like that or I don't know so incinerator something it's something being burned
Okay, these kids relate to crime they could not you know, it's like they just type of messages about these things and I says shovel
Okay, maybe I'm uncovering something digging something up or maybe something by name buried treasure. Maybe
But yeah, a shovel using a tool to a tool to uncover something. Okay, I'm back from that
And this might mean something to you.
There's your soul is burning.
Uh-oh, well, this is a magnifier.
And you just mentioned burning.
I just think of the ants,
that you know, put them in the magnifying glass
and this like incinerating, right?
He said incinerating, and we have the magnifier.
So maybe a hot fire, but then what was the, yeah.
Maybe, you have to decide what it means to you.
It's a shovel, that's interesting too.
But yeah, the magnifying glass and the incinerators.
Maybe something is burning.
Maybe you can put out some fire put out some fire. Maybe by throwing some dirt on it, you know
But you dig up with a shovel. I don't know think about it
Might but I don't think your soul is burning. I think the soul is like already fire, isn't it?
I don't know. Is there a new rules? He won't let me on well you I didn't recognize the random guy
But yeah, the rules are it's like I was a panel is one-on-one right now, and I did ten minutes with the
the open panel, and then I'm here doing the one-on-one.
Yep, so you're going the wrong route.
Well, I don't know, did that make sense to you though?
Because I mean, these are kind of obscure a little bit,
I would say.
You know, unless you like look at what what represents what the card represents like what the item represents the shovels may represent something
I mean, they uh, you know, it does like it represents uncovering something
So you look at things in a metaphorical way. What else you have a coin, but I think there's some maybe some
Very see shovel and then a coin so maybe digging up some treasure. Okay. Hopefully that's the truth for you
And that everything is good and bless you and may you not
Ever be any criminal trouble
Yeah, they're really cool. They're really cool. I got these like it's almost like clue a little bit like words
They can figure out figure out everything
What is this person up to you yeah, you're like what is this person up to me?
But yeah, these are all you know, these are all metaphor. Oh, here's Rudy. Look they're all metaphorical tools. Hey, bro. Look at you
Get rude. He just came running over
I'm still with me
Reason you're getting kind of old, huh? Oh, man. He's like a little grumpy old man here grumpy a little bit of a grump
Hi
He's happy. It seems very happy good
Okay, oh
So are you doing good? I missed you yesterday. I got so I got these cards. I think yes last night and I
And I was like hoping you would come but then I didn't see you but it's a crazy past night
So if you heard about we heard about what happened with crucible ghosts and everything, right?
I was there for that. That was hilarious. It happened to get last night
No, it didn't I look so it happened again last it happened again last night
He took over the show and like everyone was getting upset and you know
I let him kind of like because you know first he donated like 20 bucks for the panel to open the panel
And then he's like he's like okay. Well, I did even a hundred dollars
And he's like I want to be the ability to they do this in business and it's like okay
I'm trying to keep him happy and stuff, but uh
but then but then he's like oh i'm going to kick this person up kick this person up and then he
wants them back right back up and so he says like he never could make up his mind and he really
does want to talk to people and just have a good debate and he's just waiting for that perfect
debate he's just really cute but he didn't say he had a great time the other night and so i'm
really happy so that's what it's all about even when we were messing with him he had fun yeah oh
my god he had what he said he had the blast he was drunk he said he's like he's like i was like
Oh, yeah, I mean, the last one, if you want to, uh, you know,
pull attention, it's like that you can alchemize it.
There's such a thing as no bullies, bad publicity, gay people know that because
we'd love to be mentioned.
If we ever were, like, you know, because we really weren't it until like maybe
the seventies, other than some really like vile context.
And, uh, and so, uh, when we were, but any publicity was like, just to be
mentioned, just to be mentioned was like, uh, I don't know.
You know, well, we're usually behind this behind the scenes. Yeah
Vicka make up the hair set design the fashion the script writing
Now it's kind of moved more into the actors and actresses, but it's like they don't have get the
Gay people play gay parts. It's like supposed to be straight people play the gay parts and like get like Academy Awards for it
Hey, by the way, look at my shirt. You like it. Oh, oh shit. I
Know that's cool. Yeah
Love it
Hey, do you know who that is? Yes, that's really a beautiful shirt. Did you get it on on team or two?
Yep, five like five bucks. That's awesome. That's really good quality. It's a really really good quality
I like some stuff is good some stuff is bad. I just you know
Well, it's like I guess it depends like the you know the light I bought is like worse pretty good
But then it's like the remote is already broken on it. It's kind of piece of junk anyway, right?
But it's like the effect is good the cars are like
You know the five dollar cards. They're Chinese. I think they're knockoff decks. Basically. They don't have the book
You can download it on the website. They have
They have they have all the books on like all the PDFs on the on the description there
So you can get get the print those out, I guess and then so but they're good decks
I just bought the Christina Ricci deck that I'm not sure if it's a real one or a fake one
But I think it might be a real one because it's really cool. I can't wait to see that one
Yeah, it's called cat full of spiders. It's like really creepy
Yeah, that's sort of like it's called but it was like six bucks and so it's like you know
Other than like I think it was probably released at like $30. So I don't know if it's the overprint or it's like or something
But you know, it's just like there's such good deals. I
I just want to get like, you know, they always have these wheels you're spinning and like, oh, it's this free this free this free
All this is like take it off and it's like and then it's like I can never figure out how to like actually get anything from free
It's like it's like always get to spend some certain amount of money or
You know, it's like, oh, just spend like another hundred dollars and you can get this $20 off or this free item
I know that always catches me into I hate that and then I feel like oh my god
It's a deal. I gotta get it and I was gonna say cuz I dollars turns into 80
You know and they're rigged so you always win those games because I've never lost one of those games
I've never I've always had the highest amount for whatever it says and then I even said in the small print
It's like oh, this is like a simulation of what it could be like. Oh, it looks like so early
What the fuck but still because Lisa Jordan has told me like she was wearing this dress one day
Addressing sunglasses like a sundry. It was really cute. She looks good in everything though. But um
Yeah, she was like oh, I got this on she knew by spinning the wheel. She's like spun the wheel on
So I don't know if it was like bought it like oh shit. I didn't talk about my pink clothes
Yeah, so uh, but she's she looks good in everything. Of course. She's this gorgeous woman like uh, well
but uh, I'd look good in
There's a few things
Cute sake you don't discount yourself ever
I know, but I'm so Tommy. I do. I thought I should it's like I'm tall, but I'm not big
And so I can't shop at the big and tall story, you know
Yeah, yeah, my son does too. It's hard to find him shoes now
Yeah, well, it's like they always like 13. I find that they would
Lot of times it's like they have like one or two people they have a couple pairs
They think they would they do it or like that the hottest shoes, you know, so the big sizes
Yeah, just sell out and then you can only get them online too
Yeah, yeah, I mean I was actually able to when I did drag like when I was for Halloween when you're at work
I would have loved to see that
Well, when it well one of the years I was the Paris Hilton in jail because Paris Hilton got arrested like a two thousand
Yeah, I had my free Paris shirt back in the day. Yeah, I
Was there's a jail that day that she was in there. Oh my god. I'm so jealous. Yeah, there's like a lot of people there
But you know first and most out of her, but
Yeah, she uh, but yeah, so I was like I had like a little prison outfit and like a little purse with like the dog's head in it
It was like, yeah, it was kind of funny and then the next year I was Amy Winehouse
And then and then an Amy Winehouse like and then she Amy Winehouse died right after that, you know, so all the icons
Yeah, all the icons. Well, I actually think Amy Whitehouse baked her death and became Lady Gaga, but that's just me
Oh, man, I kind of believe that too
But if some people don't get it, but it's like if you look at all the Amy Whitehouse
It's like and then she died and then the Gaga appears and it's kind of like I
Shouldn't think that the world is a stage and like people play different roles even multiple people playing the set
like I think I think
James Wilkes Booth was Edgar Allen Poe and what was he he was an actor wasn't he the actor and so it's like you know and
Actors act and so it's like he had like actors. I was like a role like seeing the like the assassin of the front
I think it's all like a lot of it is this
Well, he was hired.
Mythology.
Well, no, I mean, we actually know who did it, like it was almost, it was part of like
a secret society.
It was not, it was not the, it was Masonic, but it wasn't the Mason.
It was like, but it was very similar, very similar iconography.
It was called, it's like, it was like a East Coast one at that time.
And so, yeah, they have, you know, he was in that.
And so, and they're kind of known for like, their.
Yes, the theatrical you can also look on look up John looks booth on his Wikipedia page
There's a picture of him like is this as Caesar and his brothers were actors, too
And they're all dressed like Roman soldiers or something and the interesting and interesting
Okay, but anyways articles were like people look alike over the years like someone now looks like someone back in the day
And you know
Sarah Swift and Zina LeVe the daughter of the Church of Satan guy. Have you seen her picture together crazy?
Yeah, that's pretty good and
But that's like and one of the best and then I think there are also people that are
Transgender it's that's love reason that we don't even know they're transgender, but I agree
I think, and then, but I think they're female to male.
I think they're females that live as males
and we have no idea.
I think a lot of them are deception.
That's what Hollywood is, deception, you know?
And then think about how that confuses sexually too.
Like especially like, I think Iggy Azalea has some videos
where there's just like all you see
are these hot like women twerking,
but if you look really close,
you can tell they're probably not like real women
because it's like, there's like six foot tall,
like everyone's like six foot tall and it's like,
and it's like, okay, so with that said,
everyone's like getting a rat rouse this video and so the guys are getting a rouse to
Men without even knowing it. How much of a mind fuck is that?
Is that that's that's why you know because a good guy can't guys can't you start with a 40 diamond thing guys can't like
Hope with like this transgender thing right now. They're going they're going kind of like because they're confused
Absolutely
It's like because it's like men are so visual, you know that it's like
If the illusion is good enough, then it's like the men fall for it, right?
And it's like women are kind of about illusion because you know with makeup and stuff
They use like little shadowing and makeup and colors and like little like things that like
The only women really like notice like you know, we don't have like
Like men know like there's five colors or like maybe seven colors with a rainbow or whatever
Yeah, women actually see more
Yeah, they sense more they but yeah, but they also yeah, so they they don't have a million colors
It's like men just know a few colors, right?
It's like or it's like even they kind of like women also like feel stronger
So they're kind of like and also since they give birth and stuff like that
Kind of a more representative of the universe, which is like giving gives birth to creation, right?
And so pizza and Pepsi is gay. I think guys the food is on the way to I have churros and I have
what else I have a
June Jack Jack Jack burger. I don't know. It's kind of jack-in-the-box burger and I have two coffees
I don't know who potato head is when he made me laugh. Oh
Yeah, for using his mom's credit card
Oh, oh, yeah, I hope we'll hopefully, you know
Yeah
I'm totally prepared for him to charge back if he was to check later
I wouldn't be surprised if he would do something like like like that like I mean, hopefully you wouldn't but I say I wouldn't be surprised like
You know, it's like just like, you know fucking
At least since your Donna got she had a donor once he donated like $20,000 to her and then
Charged it back on PayPal and for every charge back
She had to pay like another $5 on top of it and we just all take it out of the account at once
And fuck it's like that was really bad. That sucks. Yeah
Yeah, so that's like a bottom line is don't get drunk on the internet
No, I mean you can get drunk. We're just like, you know, make sure you know what you're
Right. Well, I don't know. It's like the internet is pretty much
pretty much it opens the thing to like
Remember like you know where you like see an adult movie like you had to go to like a movie theater
Or like back in the you know the 80s or like, you know, if you've rented the video store like, you know
Look at the like little fuzzy fuzzy stuff on the on the hotel room screens
Or sometimes they would have the the lock off of it. I remember skin and max late at night
Yeah
HBO and real sex on real sex on HBO, right there real
Like really scandalous shows that was my thing when I was young
Yeah, because we always go like a little like on vacations and stuff and like, you know, they're not motels and hotels
They would have this the channels unlocked usually sometimes, you know, so HBO HBO at least right and so
Yeah, so watch all kinds of that was the time to watch weird shit, but
Now now it's just available for everybody everywhere. They don't mean like you know
There's not even an ID process for going through so like you know watching like it's all stuff
but it's like so it's like
Everybody this is crazy and now now it's getting weird or weird. It's like now everybody has the cameras on them
Like with tiktok there's like tiktok is what you're supposed to be 18 or over on tiktok to broadcast on tiktok like they really need to like
enforcing that because
There I think there are people that is it's like their parents turned it on for them or something like that
But I mean, I'm sure there are people that are I don't know. It's just supposed to be 18 or over
I don't understand why there's people that are not but it's hard crazy
it's hard on a hard on websites to
To really please that like on chatter bait
If you have somebody else on camera with you, you're supposed to have to have their ID submitted too, but that's not the same on any other thing.
So I don't know, there's also things about, I think it's like 13 or over to broadcast or to be on camera alone on YouTube or something like that.
You have to be 13 or over.
That's not scary.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, it's like, um, but now there's a lot more control. Um, they can have over the web
Like you can like basically spy on the kids really easily because of all these
Tool available that weren't really like my parents had no idea use computers
So I could get away with anything on when I was doing it
But it's like nowadays now the parents are wise to it. They'll put on like a little, you know
You know all about history and trackers and all this kind of stuff and so you can even like a GPS or kids and a lot of people do
Right. This is like I'm never gonna look at it. Just see. Oh, I totally have it on my kids
Well, you know, it's like so it's kind of safer, but it's still
There's a lot of parents that don't care that don't care where their kids are up to you know, so yeah
Well, even though I had all kinds of like normal parental protocols on my son's stuff when he was like 13
I busted him doing something terrible
on a discord server and
he had like
mirrored his computer's hard drive and
Built this private computer that I couldn't see on there and then was able to access the internet like unfiltered
And it was, it was a mess.
I didn't let him have the internet until he was 15 years old again.
From, it was like two and a half years of no internet.
He almost lost his mind.
But didn't he do something like terrible?
Like he put like, like child porn on the, on the server or something.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's kind of crazy.
He was like people he knew personally in school and then he was selling it to
other kids for, uh, money.
It was terrible.
And like he knows, he now he knows.
And now he like.
he apologized to me and then I guess you know apologized to these people but um it it was like
such a stupid thing for it but he thought it was an easy way because all the guys were like asking
for stuff and he's real slick and you know got all these pictures and just thought well i'm gonna
Well, that's crazy, but uh, yeah, it's like and that's kind of dangerous. So she was like when they're some of these kids make to make more than their parents with
Very like how smart he is and they or you know what such a young age to be able to do all that
scary
Yeah, very scary. So you're so by the way, so
Yeah, on this court there is that kind of there are those problems with people like I think that in one time
One of my nephews at school like I think like there's somebody like using the urinal
But the first one would like pull down their pants all the way and so
I think middle school or whatever, but yeah, so they took it
They took a photo of it put it on the internet put it on like Facebook or something like that
It caused a big scandal like about you know, yeah, I would be mortified. Yeah
But yeah, it's pretty, pretty embarrassing, pretty embarrassing. Let me see. So it says, yeah.
Hey, Jamie. Hey, card guy, psyche Bruno, psyche Bruno.
I don't know what that means. Got you. And card guy, who's the card guy?
Let me see, I'm gonna go to the glasses.
Yeah, my Dahmer glasses.
So somebody actually said last night,
Jeffrey Dahmer in the TikTok room,
and I was like, did you hear me say that,
or did you think that, did you just thought that?
And I just thought that, and I was like, okay.
Yeah, they look like it.
Yeah, I did a good job,
but I could be like a costume designer or something.
I knew exactly what to get.
I guess I couldn't, but, sorry, I'm sorry babe.
I just said, yeah, I'm kind of like,
I'm kind of getting good at shopping now
that I'm able to, you know,
Hold on a second. I'm easy. I'm a very, you know, good shopper because I don't try to spend more than $10 for a t-shirt
You know, it's like
Well, yeah, I mean clothes are very expensive clothes are very expensive. So yeah, let's support easy
Okay, sweetie, okay. Okay. Okay. You too. Okay. I've had me one at a time right now
Unless somebody wants to sponsor the panel whoever is first I will put on and
Here's the link and I'm gonna grab my food. Okay, so we're back
Let's see everyone ask Bruno go up please Bruno come on up. Why does Bruno want to talk to me Bruno?
We got something to say. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what a Bruno is that he was talking shit about me
Oh, baby
Here's the face of a fucking cat killer. I don't like that screen name. So somebody like hide that first one
There's nothing interesting to say anyway
Here babe
He's important from the TPP. I know I know who he is. I did I've done a reading for him before and he was pretty rude
After that
But everybody else in the chat was pretty nice
No, thank you. What up, thank you. What's up?
See that mr. Bruno over there. So he's talking bad about me. So I came to join since he I see he's talking
Don't be over here, but I got notification that he was over here. So okay
Well, do you want to you want to address it once and for all or do you not want to address it?
Or is it I don't know if it's no matter
I want to see what he got to say if you got something to say come say cuz this can his his main channel is shut down
They don't go live no more. Okay. It's a TPP. Yeah, they don't go live no more
So if you want to address something he's on the internet, let's see. We gotta address
well
Yeah, I mean to say I
I mean, I can't I can you know, I don't know if you want to address it though because it's like, okay
So we're she's this and he's not talking bad
Okay, so I can't address it
So okay, so but you know because it's so hard to like like police anybody saying something about it in the chat because it is not
Like, you know, they're okay, so I think they say is allegedly because it's not nothing been going to court, right?
Okay, allegedly
Okay, so yeah, so I guess it's like a yeah, and I don't want to this main question is everybody do everybody just support me and
The way he's saying it is slander and that's one of your rules, right?
Yeah, it was you slander you think he's staying a slander's way. He's he just asked
Slander in my name without me being convicted
Right
There are some facts though aren't the facts that you know, there are some facts right like we there's something like
You you've admitted to whatever right? I mean, I don't know. I guess it's in legal
But it's like yeah, but I know but I yeah, it's your familiar people familiar. Yeah
Yeah
Easy easy ones to address it. So it's like it's time to if you want to Michael Bruno full video is on you
Yeah, so it's like
But well he's right in the chat
Okay, it was that yeah, so yeah, I don't know if it's been thank you. We have says let's
Dude who stats his audio? Okay, so that's it and Bruno's the guy that shit on his stuff on live
Just everybody know he's a big TPP fan. He's a big supporter of the other guy. He's shit on his stuff on live
He's a big drunk
He came on YouTube talking about he had cancer. He started off with I had cancer
He joined the panel saying he had cancer. He lied about that
That's basically who Bruno is
Okay, so that can be considered. Maybe I wouldn't say slander, but it's like that's landed
But that's all facts from YouTube. So
Okay, but it's like we're not bringing up anything
Anybody anybody body and I'll tell you the same shit that I just said acts Amanda acts anybody
They'll say yeah, Bruno came up on TPP. So come on. Yeah, I can't sir. He lied about that and then so on so on
Did anybody see the video of this? It was like a Coldplay concert or something and there it happened a few days ago
There was this CEO of this company called
Astronomy, okay
And he was cheating on his wife and he was like sitting up in the rafters of this Coldplay concert like
Canoodling with some other woman and then they put him on like the big screen at the at the concert, right?
Then the woman screamed and then like and he like then he got now he had to resign as CEO as fast as this happened
But uh, yeah
Did you hear about everybody heard about Ozzy, but you heard about Hulk Hogan this morning
Yeah, yeah Hulk Hogan's dead. Yeah, I don't know. I I don't know that the internet sees it or not because
I don't know what the internet sees, you know.
I don't watch, I can't watch everything.
I just saw it today.
I saw it today on the internet,
but it's like it was just a clip on a.
Yeah
Guys hope I'm one of the most amazing human beings in the world, you know
It's so much for humanity and we'll all you know hope they'll always miss Hulk Hogan
You know, he's just go. Hey, brother. You know, it just really touched everybody's heart
So it's not getting in the middle
But if you're using YouTube for facts Bruno, then your YouTube dealings can also be used as facts just being logical
Yeah, you're right. You're right, Katrina. Katrina, you're right. I'm mad at you, but you're right.
I understand what you're getting at. Yeah, he was racist. But I guess they're from Florida.
Are you okay? A whole RIP. Bruno, you said that you were a sick liar. He definitely inspired people.
And then he's he's a winking. Okay, so let's be some kind of an inside joke
Let's see Hulk RIP. I didn't mean to see me
Are you big fan of inspiration on a lot of things wrestling and motivation and and a whole lot of shit that he did
So shout out to Hulk
Well
In music, yeah, Mr. Sensen, but I wouldn't be the point. Mr. Segi and Mr. Jamie. Okay. So anyway
Ziggy, I'll do more important. Who's more important? Well, I guess music doesn't bring a gift to the world
But I know
I can't I can't talk to you, but I really came to talk to that Bruno guy
Okay
If you don't
I'm willing to go down and you could come up and talk to psyche by yourself
Okay
So if you're in the background if you come in the background psyche just drive me and bring them up. I don't think it's coming
I don't think it's coming up
Because he said he said stuff about me in the past and he's never like in front of me in my face
He just talks about me behind my back
And so I don't think he's gonna be coming to show but maybe you will he's gonna chat but double up easy hold down
okay, yeah, so uh
Go ahead and yeah, I'll try to get him up and
I'll have you up to if he wants to talk to you well, but I don't know but if he has anything to say
I don't think he's talking anymore though in the chat. I haven't seen him talk for a second. So
Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay. I was just um, yeah, I'll just make it sure but yeah
Hogan was a big inspiration shout out to Hogan and people if y'all don't like him
It just respect respect his legend. You know the legacy left behind whatever the case like
Well, it's not really much of a legacy besides some wrestling videos, but okay
Yeah
Yeah, but at least it's like, you know, at least I've been trying to help people I mean, it's like I don't know
wrestling is big here as a career. It's like
I still inspire people to motivate, move, lose weight, get worked out, just to, you know, stuff like that.
Yeah, fuck it. I love the face.
You'll fuck it up.
It's so hard.
I like wrestling. I like wrestling to find.
It does motivate people. It does, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Well, no, basically it's not to watch TV. Yeah, I stopped watching that just don't call us, but you know saying hope was the man
Yeah
Was very 80s
Slayers dog seeing it beta. Well, no, I call you mr. Sensitive. What I don't know. She didn't say anything
Okay, so Michael Bruno says I don't talk to gay freaks. Okay, so mod you can just just out ban Michael Bruno
He doesn't even need to be in the chat. If you ever want to talk to me you can come talk to on the panel
I don't need him talking in the chat like that. Yeah, he said that
Well, I don't I didn't I'm looking for it. Oh
It's right here. I'll put it on screen
I don't talk to gay free. Oh wow, so why are you on why you in the chat? Why are you asking people in the chat?
Yeah, why are you here? No, go away. I mean, I'll get you out of here the model and Jamie. Can you just kick him out?
They do JB
He's a piece of shit fat bastard. He's shit on his off. That's what was so funny
Yeah
Of it, but you don't like pictures I seen them playing pictures the other day and I was laughing my ass off of ghosts
But yeah, I don't know
So no, it's not worth it. Okay, so I'll say guys. Can you go ahead and please?
You can do it for me a psyche just go to the chat and tap on his name. You can promote your bath
Here's the sound this means please like the stream guys if you're on a cell phone
Just double tap the screen I think and then it should give you options to like
Help me get my life up because it's like almost like somebody is coming to my party and then they you know
Eat all the food and then they don't even say hello
So it's like somebody actually take the they invite you to dinner, but you got to pay
Yeah, and so that's not really inviting you to dinner. That's like, you know, it's like
Darker and so, you know, so it's like just go ahead and like the stream. It's free. It's free 99
ee 99
Hit the like button it's free like subscribe your notifications
Yeah, I can put it on the screen too like I bet yeah
I suppose I'm supposed to like say it three times during the show because you need to remind people sometimes
People kind of get probably get caught up in the drama on the show and forget so
Here is the oh, where did I don't have any more? I took it down. Oh shit. You don't got the
Out in the link
Okay, let's see
But yeah, I'm kind of like well
I was kind of slowed down the panel because I don't
Wait in the background, you know, if it's not that you know, it's not
Then they start getting mad and stuff like that like
This is how you are your panel now psyche and I respect you
KZ like totally KZ. So it's this guy KZ. I basically would have him on he would sit on panel for like almost a whole show for like
Maybe over a month, right? He was always like always and then he never would really say anything
And then when he did talk his microphone was terrible or you know, we just wasn't interesting, right?
And so he's just always there. Okay, and then like
Then I'm trying to like have less people on the panel and stuff or like just one at a time
And he's sitting backstage and I was like what I was talking to somebody else
He's like well, if you don't want me here, then just tell me I'm like I don't care
Like you can you learn time will have you on after this discuss or whatever and like he just got so mad
I started like say oh you're a liar you're a figure fun. It's so
Rule you by crying no, yeah
It's like what it's like there's no like nobody is entitled to it like is it because everybody can have their own
Show everyone everyone have their own show everyone can
if they want to and they can have their own panel talk see whatever they want to on their show
as it is like people are like he was like so entitled to like the panel like where it's like
the panel is like you know it's up to him it's like it's like not a place to like especially
come up and then disrespect me it's like but you know i think it's like some people have
It's like someone coming to your house and disrespecting you.
It's like, yeah, they'll have to do gaslighting and like sneak this thing.
It's just paving your house and jump on that shit and say, fuck your couch.
Yeah, it's like, um, you know, I think I should have the right to use firearms at that point, you know
So it's like, you know, that's it's really like that. And so, um, yeah, people should not just like
It's that so you're on
I'm coming in the background. I'm willing to drop good because I came up to talk to psyche
I got notification this was in the time I was and I got all what I'm going over there
Let me see you come up and put that shit
Yeah, and also the chat the chat too if I'm just please I'm like I can I don't even care if mods really
blocks people if they're saying like it's like so it's like if I if you like find yourself not able to talk in my chat is like
You know just go on a different account like you probably will or
Theme set I heard Casey joined the rival terror count on Trevor channel discord, you know what I mean Stacey
Oh, no, all I know is that he went to he went right to beat us and like and I started like like talking shit about me that night
I mean, but I don't care. I'm not even
But he was like so everybody was like don't have KZ on don't have KZ on he's boring
He's this he's like well, and I really wanted to like
Give him a chance and stuff like that and I and I did it
I was like always understanding he like supposedly they had this domestic incident
I was like, oh, I haven't seen the police report and I say and I don't even like really know the whole story and so but then it's like
You know that might have all turned out to be true and and or whatever, but it's like
Don't know. He just seems like he's like he's very just mental for someone that's done that. Okay, Z. You heard you heard it
Drop the links like he hit the link right now cuz easy boys out of here
I wanted to just talk to you for a few not too much here in there
You know, I'm trying to stay up panels. So I'll be joining time to time
Shout out to everybody in the chat without child. We ain't shit. Yo hit the link hit the link next one up. Let's go
We're good. I'm glad he's glad he is who cares guys. I'm not friends with her anymore
So he can be friends with her. I like Vampira everybody else is just a cheap knockoff of her
Yeah, but even a virus a cheap knockoff of Vampira. It was
It was I'll tell you the story of Vampira actually. It's a really good story
so Vampira was
the first
Like the I think one of the first
What are they called
I'll show you her picture here
First ghoul first ghoulish woman like she was like, you know this first vamp. Oh, I guess vamp is a good word vamp, okay
She was a vamp like short for vampire look at her waist
Now that's real talent right there
Give that our best waste
And she was on TV. She's gorgeous. Like, look, here's her eyebrows. She has great eyebrows, great arched eyebrows. Very beautiful woman. I think she was Russian.
Okay, so I'll see if I can... I'll try to find a good... I forgot what picture to... What is she doing? Okay, so I'll try to find a good...
article about her. Her name is Malia Elizabeth Jojunimi, which is, I think she was like
Polish or something. Let me see.
Vampira.
The incredible but true story of
Malia Vampira Nurmi. It says in 1954 a 31 year old former model
nightclub coat check attendant and network or necktie painter named Malia Nui me
Attended a Hollywood party with her husband actor writer Don or Dean Reisner
She made her own vampire costume vampire costume inspired by that cartoons of Charles Adams out of fabric scraps
So the original morticia, right?
She must have quite a profile because months later, another attendee at the party still
remembers her.
He was Hans Stormberg Jr., the newly-installed program director at WABC in Los Angeles.
At the time, movies were shown only infrequently on television.
The major studios were not much interested in cooperating with the small screen, and
in fact considered it a mortal threat.
So most of the feature films available to broadcast were from such poverty-row operations
as Monogram and PRC.
Stromberg's idea was to add some sex appeal to his channel's late-night horror movie screenings.
He remembered that Vampiric knew me, but did not know her name or had to get in touch with her.
Fortunately, the designer, Rudy Gidd-Garrick, remembered her name and Stromberg hired her
to create a vampire character who would not, however, infringe upon any existing copyrights or trademarks.
Nuri Nuri got to work at once on her look for a character that which is christened Vampira
She combined elements of Snow White's Evil Queen a comic strip dragon lady and under the cost counter bondage models
To exaggerate her already waspish waistline
She strapped a flesh wasting polis of meat tenderizer to her midsection with a tightly bound rubber inner tube
Her measurements were advertised as 38 17 36
She took to wearing a vampire a drag whenever she left the house and even rented an appropriately funeral looking black packer convertible
For her John's around town. She became a celebrity in the nightclubs and jazz clubs of LA
It was here that she met James Dean who became fixated on her the feeling was mutual and they became close
Companions often cruising the late night drives together dives together until he morbid stories to one another
Nermy was no competition in this department for the death obsessed Dean
Okay, now it's getting weird, huh?
Eventually, the vampire character became so popular
that WABC decided to take ownership of it
and asked Nermi to sign it over to them.
She would not, and the show was terminated,
scarcely eight months after it had began.
She still made public appearances and reprised the role
in 1959's Plan 9 from Outer Space.
But the vampire character has passed
into popular mythology by the time, right this time.
Normie continued to attract weirdos, though.
In 1975, she told an interviewer,
I couldn't attract anyone who wanted to live.
When one of her followers asked her
to a Halloween party in 1975 she said leave me alone my whole life has been a Halloween party.
Okay well that's the story about that but I guess there was a curse with James Dean,
that was said Helen, James Dean curse if you look deeper into it. Hold on.
James Dean's Black Madonna, How Hollywood Killed Vampira.
Like many, I discovered vampire in my early teens
through the misfits horny tribute in 1982's Walk Among Us.
I became instantly enamored with Hollywood's
preeminent glamour ghoul.
But in time, I became fascinated
with the vision behind the vamp,
the iconic Malia Nermey.
Last month, I finally picked up a copy of glamour ghoul,
the passions and pain of the real vampire of Malia Nermey,
written by Malia's niece.
The book is an 11-year-long labor of love that sensitively pieces together reflections pulled from journals Malia kept into her death in 2008.
After reading it, I immediately managed to rummage through digital archives for more information on the circumstance that pushed this radical figure into the shadows of show business.
Okay, so where's the James Dean part?
So James V, on the other hand, was relatively unknown on the ascent.
The young actor secured co-starring role in Issa Vita in April 1954, but it wasn't until
the release of Rebel Without a Cause in October 1955 that he truly became the perennial poster
boy for disenfranchised youth.
Then the morning after the premiere of Sabrina, Leah's wish to meet him was realized.
Jack Simmons took Malia to the late night copy hangout with Googies, where they saw
Malia claims she could see since Dean's yearning for mother figure and he subsequently invited her
to his apartment where he read her a story about a 12 year old boy who commits SUICIDE.
So some soon enough the Nermi Dean Simmons trio were joined at the hip keeping late night
hours as goohies and even taking twilight drives to local cemeteries. The press apparently dubbed
the night watch for that unusual antics and archives show that columns frequently reported
on sightings of Malia and Dean. On 20 November 1954, Dean even made an anonymous appearance
on the Vampires show, acting as a naughty schoolboy who the thriller hostess beat with the dictionary.
And then it says eating a hamburger we flee with onions and all the trimmings on the strip were James Dean and vampire
They have been seen till they're constantly
Vampire he used to see James Dean visited the rebel without a cost set but with another actor in the cast Jack Simmons
And and what on earth has vampire? Oh?
Hold on give a super chat
Hey random guy
Well, okay, you're lame anyway
So
Anyway, I thought my father wrote on sentences. I'm trying to get the interesting story
So it says the Malia insisted she and D or kindred spirits who are comically drawn to one another many have suggested that she embellishes the story
Well, if one thing's for sure Malia adored Dean
She stayed many times that their relationship was strictly platonic when asked about her connection to Dean and Simmons
She told Andy Warhol's interview magazine. I feel it's my duty to clear up the rumors
We saw our psyches that reflected in each other like cocktails and fonts terrible
an incestuous managé toile without the sex. Despite Malia's obvious devotion to her friend,
Dean publicly discovered her in a widely syndicated interview with gossip columnist
Heda Hopper, who was a driving force behind the creation of Hollywood Blacklist.
I don't date witches, and I dig cartoons even less.
Vampira was merely a subject about which I wanted to learn, and after engaging the girl
in conversation, I found that she knew absolutely nothing and was only obsessed with her vampire
makeup.
And that's what he said about her.
That's not very nice.
So no one already got cursed.
James Dean on Malia and Nermy,
the quote was printed in Hedda Hopper's syndicated column
in November 18th, 1954.
Some have suggested Dean's comments
may have been the machinations of the Warner Brothers,
who felt Malia was a black mark on his rising star.
Malia suggested Dean with Bitter
after she spoke about their relationship
to Hopper's rival columnist, Luella Parsons.
However, in an interview with Aline Mosby in April 55,
Malia seems to confirm that Deans struggled to separate the person from the performance.
I'm not at all like the vampire character. James Deans sought me out,
but was disappointed to see I'm not a character.
Then here's an old article part of Dean's occult interest had been provided provoked by his good friend
Myla Nermey an actress who had created the role of Vampira on a local TV television station
Word of their affair has leaked out and the resulting publicity sent Warner executives reaching for their terms
Dean at first refused to deny the relationship no one tells this cowboy had a ride was how he retorted
But eventually he relented in an exclusive interview with
Had a hopper and I call him dated November 18th. He said I have never taken vampire out and I should like to clear this up
I have a fairly adequate knowledge of satanic forces and I was interested to find out if this girl was possessed by such a force
Okay, so the way that is
Worded it. It doesn't sound like
James Dean it sounds like
An executive writing that
Doesn't sound like James
Or said that this doesn't seem like something he would say or but it's this way. It's worded. It seems and it's very like
worded very well, I don't know cuz uh
So anyway, that's all I guess that's all it has to say about that but he did die in a car crash and you know
Okay, this one says that she took down the Hollywood legend
Okay, this is the I'm gonna read one more article. I'm sorry if you don't like it
The headline read, James Dean's Black Madonna, the most chilling and tragic love story in
Hollywood history.
The scandal magazine whisperer ran this issue February 1956, just a little over four months
after Dean's fatal automobile accident.
The Black Madonna, who many blame for Dean's death, was his supposed friend and rumored
lover, Malia Nourmi, otherwise known as America's very first late night TV whore-host, Vampira.
Already disruptive and rebellious female figure in the 1950 ideals,
Vampira's gothic and lurid image of sex and death
was all many Americans needed to link her to the dark arts,
the occult, and witchcraft that took down a promising Hollywood heartthrob.
If you're not entirely familiar with Vampira,
she was and is, remains a powerful example of mid-century female sexual rebellion.
Through her late night variety style show, Dig Me Later, Vampira,
she overtly mocked the role of submissive mid-century housewife
with unapologetic eroticism.
Vampire was born in an era when being the perfect housewife meant everything.
Women of the greatest generation were told large, shiny, efficient appliances to make
domestic work faster, easier, where all their hearts desired.
Women cooked, cleaned, voted how their husbands told them how to vote, and only had sex as
a means to appease their spouse or to get another child.
They stayed home, they stayed beautiful, they stayed quiet.
Vampire refused to do any of this.
She was not silent.
Vampire screamed.
She was sex and death all wrapped in a tight black tattered dress with a slit up the leg.
She had soft raven hair, long phallic nails, dark lips and commanding eyebrows arts just so.
And she floated through the night's eerie haze through the airwaves of the family television
and right into the living room to let out a horrifying yet pleasurable scream.
She would look right in the camera, right in your eyes, calm after such a gratifying
right before she introduced the nightly flick.
I had recently discovered the link between the pioneering horror hostess and James Dean
while reading a story in David J. Skull's study on the culture of horror, The Monster
Show, in which he mentions the two icons initially bonded over a shared interest in the occult.
Their relationship remains ambiguous, not entirely clear if it was platonic or romantic,
and most of the stories surrounding the couple exist solely as rumors that cast Vampira as
I say Vampira instead of Nermi because where Nermi and Vampira begin and end is often indescribable.
She lived, breathed, performed, existed in character. Never really appearing as herself,
but always as Vampira. Nermi once described the character of Vampira as a combination
of Pola Negri, Mary Antoinette, Marilyn Monroe, Norma Desmond, and Tallulah Bankhead all ruled in
one. But I really think it was Nermi who was a melting pot of personalities and Vampira was just
America viewed the empire as a dangerous woman bent on satirizing and disrupting the ideal image of a demure housewife, cocktail in hand, ready to serve her husband home from the office.
She naturally became the sorceress who summoned a young handsome star to the grave.
W. Scott Poole details more of the rumors surrounding the glamour ghoul in his book Vampire,
A Dark Goddess of Horror.
Vampire's alleged infatuation with Dean, an enthusiasm that was unrequited, led her
to craft a handmade postcard, meant as one of her macabre jokes, and shows her sitting
alone on a folding chair next to an open grave.
The card read, Darling, come and join me.
The postcard was supposedly later snagged by journalists and printed in whisper.
Darling come and join me. She's sitting on the folding chair with the empty graves
It says, infamous 1950s gossip columnist Hedda Hopper apparently roused Dean up in a conversation
about Vampire in which he shouted, I don't go out with witches.
The comments seemingly upset Vampire when she heard them and left her feeling wounded
by her perceived friend.
As a response to what she saw as self-destructive behaviors with his car racing, Vampire reportedly
built an altar to stop Dean from killing himself.
to have witnessed the altar seven months before Dean's death,
although this is now believed to be bunk
and part of a generated hype to pin vampire
as a sinister origin of the actor's death.
Hopper ran stories of vampires conjuring black magic
and other occult and supernatural forces
to curse Dean for his snide comments and unrequited love.
Vampire became the queen of darkness,
the literal blood-sucking vampire
that stalked and damned America's fledgling golden boy
to the grave.
What is known true or not as vampire didn't little to dispel these rumors held bent on up turning the status quo and not succumbing to what society expected of her, i.e. women.
Vampire made what I believe to be a defiant, albeit rather odd and slightly insensitive statement that vampire and only vampire will control her own narrative.
Vampires showed up uninvited to a Hollywood costume party dressed as a witch, complete
with the obligatory pointy hat.
Her unidentified date came as a bandage James Dean, indeed playing with the rumors that
she was a witch who could resurrect Dean from the grave and also that she was the witch
who put Dean in the grave.
Additionally, there is also the urban legend that Dean was not dead, he was just horribly
scarred that his family in the studio faked his death and he was institutionalized because
the automobile crash left him disfigured.
Although much context of the situation has left wanting a photo does exist of this daring
appearance.
There is no notification.
But there's the bandage James Dean and this is right after he died, right?
And she's kind of a little bit insensitive, right? She comes as a witch playing playing up the rumors actually
Vampire's career defaulted after Dean's death, perhaps as part for the spandalous rumor surrounding her and Dean and the alleged occult ties,
perhaps for entirely different reasons altogether, she would not accept the press crafting stories about her,
so she made them her own. She refused to be painted the petty scorn lover.
She refused to be America's housewife and she wasn't going to be a witch either, at least not on anybody's terms, but her own.
Okay.
Have I done more than three streams in 24 hours?
No, not really.
I think, yeah, maybe I have,
maybe just because I had to restart a few times more.
So, oh, that's what does it, the three streams in 24 hours.
I don't know if it was the other day.
I think, but is that forever,
or is that there's no notification?
Okay.
That's why well, is that is that permanent is that or is it like you know if anybody does that just one time it?
What if you know the technical difficulties? I mean I've done it way before that too
So okay, like it also could be the n words like Benny Blanco was the shadow band for
They say in the n word like a hundred times or something
And then the nine-time H. O. L. C. A. S. T
It's normal on YouTube. Okay. Well, it's still I have 26 people
25 people that's a decent amount of people so people are obviously still seeing my thumbnail come up on the screen
Unfortunately, there's not a notification. So it might be a little bit slower going
It's different on tick tock tick tock
I just had so many people flooding into the room like a lot like a lot of people coming in and like oh
They said I was I did more people and tick tock than
than I did on 100% of other people related to the amount of time I've been on, I guess.
But, you know, I'm a professional.
I mean, it's going really well there.
Tomorrow, I will stream, and that will be my last probationary kind of stream, because
after three days of streaming, they will give you all the tools, all the regular streaming
tools.
to use and then 1,000 subscribers I'll be able to do some more stuff and then my
mom's almost halfway there and then 10,000 subscribers monetized I just got
I can't signal cast it it would be a different kind of show
There's only three notifications in the 24 hours. So I did but I didn't do I didn't end it within 24 hours
Okay, so maybe I did between nine. I did it. I did end it because
Okay, so maybe 24 hours. Yeah, I just ended it secure my streams last night
Secure the streams with their large donations, okay
So the panel is available to be sponsored if you'd like to sponsor an open panel, but it's pretty quiet
Some people are mad about the open panel. I think I'll do a free day on Sundays. I'll do a free
Free open panels like where it's all sponsored or whatever. It'll be my day to sponsor it
And so that'll be kind of like an open panel kind of free-for-all day
that'll be kind of maybe the wild day and then
But I do like talking to people one at a time.
I don't like when people are in groups necessarily
because they seem to like all like to gang up against me
by, I don't know, whatever.
So I like to talk about one-on-one.
So a person does not put it on a mask
because especially with like, you know, from pages here,
the guys are showing so hard to...
To impress her and I don't know if they think I'm pressing another girl's like they were trying to like put down somebody else
But being a panel hose isn't easy to deal with all the rules and weirdos. Thank you girls. Yeah, it's not it's not it's like and it's basically like
Putting it's like also very risky for the show, but my I talked to chat GPT about what makes my show unique and stuff like that
And first of all, I said I have a unique sense of humor,
like a really good sense of humor.
And then it said that it's an open panel.
There's very, very, an open panel format
for terror readings where it's like,
usually it's all pre-recorded.
And so, or just the chat, you know?
And so that's unique as well.
It inspires you to want to punch yourself in the head.
Oh, well, well, random guys don't watch it.
If it inspires you to like, you know,
Do bad, then why are you here? No, it's like you should be wanting to like improve yourself
That's kind of dumb. See AI is always watching
Well, yeah, cuz I well, do you know like chat GPT has a new a new part of it where it's like it is able to
Do things now I can go into your computer and do things for you
So if you say book a flight you can book flights
It's like the guy was giving the example today. He did this
He said okay
He says you're a website designer and you want to like sell some websites to businesses, right?
You can say to the chat to BT find ten
What's that? I mean this is to find ten ten dentists in the area with websites
do research on all of them and
find out
Um infer all their contact information and then write a letter very almost stalker-ish very custom and
with information about them and like like and try to sell the some of these websites and
The chat GPT writes these letters and it's like oh the chat GPT figures out the dentist plays pickleball
And it figures out the dentist this Kundalini yoga and and it's how fast he graduated and all this stuff
You know because people will put a lot of information about themselves online
Do I own a set of weights? No, I have a pull-up bar. I have a pull-up bar. That's all I have.
I don't have any weights, really. But I do like to carry heavy bags from the market sometimes.
I mean, I don't like to do it, but I do occasionally because I do walk everywhere.
But yeah, TikTok is really cool guys.
I really recommend you guys check it out
like because I didn't know how cool it was,
but it's also super good for business
if you have a business, right?
Or a show, okay, so here's what you can do.
You can go and go, you know,
set it up your account as a business account.
It's just, it's free to do, you know,
set up as a business account
and then it will give you an auto responder.
In the auto responder,
you can just put like a little message,
a welcome message with your
with your link on it for your page or for your business or whatever and
Then it goes to I don't know it just it seems to be just going out to people
So people are just responding to me without me. What's my tic-tac psyche awakens?
Let me see if he has psyche awakens. Maybe he's a key awakens. Let me check
Okay, so tiktok is this is my tiktok username
My shows there are pretty good too. They're a really fast pace. I'd love for you to say hi to me
So there you go, that's the that's my
Account
So I'm going to be probably trying to do about an hour to an hour and a half there every day.
I do really fast readings there, like one-card readings, and I take questions.
And then I answer also questions in the chat.
And they also have like a little random question generator that you can run.
And so if I ever get low on questions, you can run that question generator,
and I can just answer those questions.
And so there's always stuff to do.
There's a lot of people just coming in and out.
It's a really like different website.
People go to YouTube to like watch the videos
and to get like, you know, cuddle in
and sit in for the night and like hang out.
And they go to TikTok, most people are just scrolling
really fast through and they'll skip right by me, you know?
But a lot of people will stop in and like listen
and get a reading and
Then afterwards they connect with me, and so it's a really good way.
I have two TikToks, there's also a Psychee Awaken.
Yeah, I don't use that one.
That was my other one, but I'm not using that one.
It is technically me, but I just have that for at least my backup one.
The one I'm using is the Psychee Awaken Tarot.
That's the one with that.
I have like 500 followers and stuff.
Yeah.
Okay, sorry.
Unfortunately, I'm not able to follow anybody back.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you, person.
Yeah, that's really cool.
Thank you so much.
That's perfect.
And yeah, I really like to talk I really think there's like there's some really cool people on there too
Like I never was able to like just like sit and chat with people like I mean it like one-on-one
And then it's like you can also like don't like give them like little gifts and stuff like that
So I like to give like no gifts. I kind of spend a little bit too much on that
because I get kind of like crazy on there, but you can like donate to people and stuff and
and your little games, and it will make the graphic on it.
I don't know, it's really cool.
I enjoy it, and then you can talk one-on-one.
You can also bring guests into the studio.
Never downloaded, never will.
Yeah, maybe it's not for you, but it's pretty cool.
I would say there's something for everybody there,
even if you're just in the science,
you can just go to the science, take talks,
but they have mostly, there'll be a lot of people,
like pretty sexy people.
But yeah, you will get like a thousand like spam like people like trying to catfish me right away
Like I think there's you have to be careful with your emails. I'm not gonna be careful not to like give too much information
So what is sick? So your appreciation for psyche and it seems to say that like be sure to go out and share with your friend
Yeah, thank you so much doggo
Yeah
Yeah, so as for sickness, you know, it's if the world is thick if the world is so it's the world would be the culture if the
Culture is poison then the people aren't there for our internal poison aren't they because we are part of the culture
And so it's like we were proud of our environment more than even ourselves. Think about that
So if the world is sick, what does that make us?
Show your appreciation. Yes, exactly. Thank you so much and you don't download tiktok. You don't really don't have to
So all of this is a video website, you know, it's a it is what the people make it
But it does have a great infrastructure with the effect. It's the store integrated and so some people are just selling their shit
And you know, it has six so oh, it's just means awesome. Yeah, but there's like they've had double meanings
Yeah
So say that word, okay. Yeah sick. That's it man. Yeah, do you say it to a skateboarder?
Or skateboard with a stick. Yeah, dude. You stick Olly or something like that. Okay, man, this one. Yeah
But what what are you emphasizing?
This is really good coffee though caramel
No, it's the mocha it's the mocha this chocolate mm-hmm
I mean, did you not have a guy up on the panel who actually
stab, yeah, well, but right random guy, but what am I supposed to do? So I'm
supposed to, is he charged with that? No.
Is he like wanted? I don't think so. Um, you know,
as for the details of it, I don't know. Yeah, there you go.
I'll be back. Hello.
Yeah, see you something you mentioned the devil and the devil appears right no, but yeah, so easy gonna dress it
If you want I'm done addressing it. It's not my business really. No, it's like a guy fine. Yeah, he's fine. He's alive
Thank goodness
But uh, anyway no more okay, so
It's like there's a big difference between victimless crimes and victim crimes
There's plenty of things people can do that hurt themselves, you know, it's like there's like, you know drugs
Things that are illegal even SUIC IDE is technically illegal like hey, but how you charge a corpse
So you so and if it's not successful then how is it a SUIC IDE?
So I don't think the attempts illegal, but the act is for you. So it doesn't make any sense, right?
It's like saying, oh, let's find out if you're a witch.
So we'll throw you in the water.
And if you float, then your witch will kill you.
And if you drown, then you're not a witch.
And oops, but then you're dead.
So it's kind of like a, have I seen the animation
someone made?
Well, what's the animation?
Is it a unshelattering one of me?
Or what is it?
Tell me.
I've seen the fish taco. I'm turning into a fish taco. I've seen the Mexican pizza lady and I've seen
the butthole scam.
Paisa, yeah, Paisa, she's a witch. Are you surprised?
Yes, but it's like she's one of those nature witches. I don't think she like worships the devil or anything, but
maybe she does.
No, she's like, she's like, I'm not a Christian remember when people were accusing her of being a Christian. She got so mad. Oh Mexican pizza lady
Yeah, that was a good one. Yeah, that's true. I mean, there's other true stories, but they're funny
Like they're they're kind of true, but they're like I kind of said it in a funny way
So I do like those Lord of the Groove animations. I do like their Cyrax series, too
They have one of Marty and Cyrax the last one and then they have a they have a gang stalking series, too
They have all these streamers that are saying they're getting gang stocks
Right now, which is a better evil, you know, it's like you can say you can say in general, you know
Like it's just like saying it's just like saying nymphs kind of it's like it's like it's like a just like a general term for
The feminine the feminine maybe it's when you said demonize them
But I think it's so that's maybe a word of the taken on their own as a power word, right? So
Not all witches are bad or evil and you know only only bad witches are ugly, right?
That's from the Wizard of Oz that I don't know about Dorothy logic
In the satanic witch I talked to many Manson about this many Manson was related to the satanic witch
So we're to sleep with socks on now. Not really. It came to enjoy my content
Also, if you hear of Gotti or G to come up make a fool. Oh, that's your um Gotti was already up here doing that
I'm just kidding. Yeah, there's the Lord of the Groove. You can see my cartoons over there. It's really good
I think it's RG's network. Is that our black RG's network? Did he make those? I heard he was associated with that
But I'm not 100% sure your new Patrick. Awesome. Well, I've seen you before and
Welcome everybody. I did tell the tiktok people to come and you like to fish taco. I'm turning into fish taco
Yeah, I don't know if I was like really crying at that time. So I
Was player one, okay
I don't know why I heard black arches or something like that, but it's really flattering to have a cartoon made of yourself and have a couple of them at this point.
Maybe I'll talk to a lecturer about what she uses for AI software because she uses some pretty good stuff at this lake.
The one I've tried the shrimp taco. I did I'm not into I was actually they have shrimp tacos
Yeah, and I'd like to shrimp tacos. I do I didn't like the shrimp burger though very much
But I think the shrimp taco is a lot player one is one of us. He's a great guy. Oh people awesome
He's a stream. Yeah, because it was like I was like so great to watch those cartoons
I gave it like make me look stupid and I was actually like kind of funny
They're like it was me doing like my little comedy routines, right? There's some shrimp. Yeah
So but I watch it out and they're funny. I even played them on the show at one point and so oh guys by the way
All the content now is in members only I put all I put everything back there everything
Well, there's a lot of stuff that's still on private like the older streams
I've privated still some of the first rooms I did just because I want to go back through those and see if they're even worth
We should have a Muppet stream. I like you wish that we can't have that Tom flash guy. He is the Kermit puppets
But he's the fucking I think he tried to pour and bought my show and stuff
but uh
Yeah, so
Yeah, so I forgot what I was saying, but yeah, so I but I like those cartoons. Yeah, so I hope I'm in some
more flattering ones
Well, but I do think and I was pretty funny. I was like wow
I think I'm pretty like I tell pretty funny stories like the way it's like kind of like looking at your my show personality
It's like I have a different show personality than my real personality. It's not too much different, but it's like more
sarcastic and jokie and also trollish a little bit and
So there's a creator that makes puppets dark side Becky
There for you go. Oh, yeah, I know that um, you know
I'm surely has a stuttering John puppet and I was one of the first things I was thinking
I was like, what if I did this like a puppet show on YouTube like an adult puppet show, but then it's like
Yeah
It's headed. I said we go this route
I don't want the puppets to be more famous than me.
Oh, I'd get mad.
Then I would probably burn it.
Shrimp with french fries, okay.
Oh, that sounds good, french fries shrimp.
Well, I don't know, yeah, you can get that at the pier.
They can get that at the market.
They can also, they'll cook anything you want there.
So, and they have everything, they have all of it.
So, they have these big platters of lobster
and stuff people get.
They cook them up and you can just take them to your...
Table and the big metal trays are expensive though. There's some dishes that are over $100 just full of seafood and lobster and stuff
And that's just like one night of food pretty good
Chase, I know puppet guy on these streams
Yeah, puppet people kind of freak me out though. You're seeing there's a movie with
Deadly I think it's a deadly more or something like that. It's really weird
He has one of these Charlie McCarthy puppets that like it kind of comes to life
He starts to put his starts to put his personality in the puppet and the public starts murdering people and stuff
And he doesn't know it's doing it because he's like he's like it's associated himself into the puppet
There's dark side Becky check out the handmade puppets for sure
And I'll pin the link again. Here's the link if anyone comes to come up
I will pin the link too. You just don't like any dolls. Yeah, my grandmother was a doll maker
Okay, so she made a she had a she had a doll named Michael that she made that was her perfect
You know, I think her like masterpiece because that was the only doll that I said she made that I was actually hers
But it was a professional doll and it was named as Michael and she just loved that Michael doll
I wonder where Michael is now, you know, like
Unfortunately, I didn't get anything but uh, you know for dolls for after she passed like I got like a poster of the dolls
But people used to freak out
Spending the night at her house. She would uh because she had a doll room, right? And it was just like all these dolls staring at you
Okay, okay the doll collector, you know a doll woman
Okay
So tiktok is going crazy
I'm getting some messages from there.
Yeah, unfortunately, I can't right away follow you back,
but I will, because I've been following so many people,
I'm banned from following for a little while,
so I'm following too fast, so I'm clicking through it.
Really trying to get to the 1,000 subscribers on TikTok,
and you might like my show there,
it's just really quick and formal.
I'll answer your question as quick as I can,
usually pretty fast.
It's not too busy at the moment,
but I think it's gonna get busier.
But yeah, it is the kind of like, I think it would be good to do private readings too.
I think it would be good to, because then people can contact you easier than they can
here.
Like, because we're following the accounts and so we have the email access on YouTube
that you don't really have email access, so you can't contact people that easily.
The Dildo Collector also, nice.
So is Ariel from Little Mermaid, but she called them the Thingamabobs.
Interesting.
Okay, so I was also compared to like three other channels and they're really good channels
Like they're and it's like I'm smaller than them
But I was compared to them on chat TV T
I was like give me some my competitors channel and a really good channels and
But we're different, but I'm different and so it's like it tells me to focus on my differentiator. You can't do tick-tock
You're not the tiniest your info. Yeah, I know that's kind of true
But really, I haven't given them that much info.
I did take a picture of my driver's license.
Before I started streaming,
that's to prove that you're a team, you know?
That's all I think they use it for,
but all collectors keep you out.
Do you ever see the movie Dolls?
There's also the Puppet Master.
Pretty good movie.
Yeah, interesting.
I like doll there's also these doll videos on YouTube look like a haunted dolls and it's like the dolls like move throughout the night
Their heads will move like and they'll or they'll like have like little movements or eyes will blink sometimes or like toys to turn on by
Themself
Keyleta Keyleta has the thing where she found this doll and it laughs like her
Potentially offensive if I post there go large, but why do you want to do that because they're I mean I really don't care
But it's like not like
It's offensive. I don't I find it offensive just as long as it's not against TOS and like, you know, I
Think to do with like, you know hate of any race. That's fine
Who will defend is the question and who's it meant to defend?
Because a lot of trolls will just do this thing called dog whistling and it's like it's like going after certain
subcultures, but it's like only the people from the subculture understand the lingo and
so
That's why it's considered. Yeah, it's considered. Yeah
It's hard but part of trolling is like trolling the subculture
With like or with the dog whistles, which only they can do though Don what's that mechanism you have on?
It'd be a porcelain penis from days gone by and I did I hear that you grunt as you shoved it up your well dog
I mean, that's just like, you know, okay that you write that poem
Is there a reason you want to say that?
Is it necessary? Is it is it kind? Is it true? I don't know
Doesn't seem like something that needed to be posted but go ahead express yourself doggo
Anyhow, anyhow, I mean I like that. I mean if it was like the limerick those limericks were like
We're like a clever, you know that that wasn't that was kind of like it's McLean and McLean someone mentioned a dildo collect, okay
Okay
Well that explains it. Okay. Thanks for it. Thanks for breaking it down. Oh
God
Yeah, I'm not into dildos. I like for the real thing. Okay. Let's see
Mmm, okay. Get any slice half price on July 30th cheesecake factory. That sounds good national cheesecake day humble bundle. Okay, see
T-moo free island. What gmail is this? Oh
That's my combined email
Okay
Guys, if you're interested in graphics design, just hit me up.
I will help you out with it.
One okay, so complete complete professional video. Where's this website? He is the re-vid. I think this is the one that the guy told me about
Okay
Yeah, I hope you're feeling good. Jamie. There's a streamer called psyche who got himself an e-bike. Oh
Well, let me find the limerick. Hold on. I fell off the e-bike. It's not working right now
Oh, I don't see you up to tell me.
Let me see the limerick.
Best.
OK.
This is my favorite one.
The once was a grugal from Cancun who
had the most curious poon.
It was coarse like a thistle, but tight as the whistle.
And while it's coming, could play you a tune.
Okay
Whenever my sweet lady beckons I'm there within minutes I reckon but try as I might her pussy so tight. I'm coming within 14 seconds
There was a young lady from do who filled her vagina with glue and she said with a grin if they pay to put it to get in
They will pay to get out of it, too
Says I love this okay, it says she frowned and called him mister because in sport he kissed her and
So in spite that very night that mister kissed her sister
Okay, there was a man from Man Tuckett his dick was so long get suck it
He said with a grin as he wiped off his chin if my ear was a cunt that would fuck it
There was was a man from Kent whose tool was so horribly bent
So to save himself trouble he put in he put it in double and instead of coming he went
There once was a lady named Grace who said if the whole human race depends upon what the boys call its what then
It's put in a damned awkward place
There was once a fella named Ben who was constantly mocked by his friends
But one day he snapped and he got them all back by inserting himself inside each of them
There was a tale of Michael Kool, the man who was born with a spiral tool.
He spent his life in desperate hunt to find a girl with a corkscrew cunt.
When he found her, he dropped down dead.
When he learned that she had a left-hand thread.
That's terrible. Not a limerick, okay?
Okay.
Guys so there's just a joke. He says the teacher asked little Johnny if he knew his numbers
Okay, and then he's yes. He said my dad taught me and he said good what comes after eight
And he says nine answered Johnny and she other what comes after nine and
He says ten if you guys and what comes after ten and he says the jack
Okay
If ever it's a Jill one
So little Johnny raised his hand and asked the teacher if he could go take a leak and you should say urinate and say
Can you use those that said in a sentence Johnny and he says if you had bigger tits?
Yeah, you'd be a 10, but since you don't urinate
And he corrected him again as an asinine answer Johnny
Do you know what asinine means and he said he said he used the word asinine in a sentence and he's like overall
You're a seven, but I'd give your asinine
Okay
Damn little Johnny
Math class, little Johnny's dedication to math after seeing a nailed figure.
When I got to my math class on Monday and saw that guy above the blackboard nailed to
a plus sign, I knew they weren't missing a round.
Addition, Johnny's unique approach to solving math problems.
Two plus five, that son of a bitch is seven.
Three plus six, that son of a bitch is nine.
Essays on my dog.
Johnny's creative answer to an assignment.
I don't know. I guess it's a joke. Hold on.
Oh, yeah, so this is the whole joke my mate told me this describing it as the best little Johnny joke
I'm inclined to agree little Johnny's neighbor had a baby
Unfortunately, the baby was born without years
The mother a new baby came home from the hospital Johnny's family was invited over to see the baby before they left their house
Johnny's dad had a talk with him and explained that the baby had no ears
His dad also told them that if he so much mentioned anything about the baby's missing ears or even said the word ears
He would get the smacking of his life when they came back home little Johnny told his dad that he understood completely
When Johnny looked in the crib, he said,
what a beautiful baby.
The mother said, why thank you, Johnny.
Johnny said, he has beautiful little feet,
beautiful little hands, a cute little red nose,
her cute little nose and beautiful eyes.
Can he see it?
All right.
Yes, the mother replied.
We're so grateful.
The doctor said he will have 20-20 vision.
That's great, said little Johnny,
because he'd be fucked if he needed glasses.
Oh, it's terrible.
Okay
How about this one little Johnny's at the park with his dad, okay?
Okay, Lincoln's pinched.
Okay, Little Johnny is at the park with his dad. They see two dogs humping and Little Johnny asks,
what are they doing, dad? Little Johnny's dad, not wanting to lie, responds, they're making puppies.
Later that night, Little Johnny walks in and his mom and dad making love a missionary position.
Little Johnny asks, dad, what are you and mommy doing? Again, not wanting to lie, his father responds,
we're making you a little brother or sister. Upset, Little Johnny says,
Then flip mommy around I want a puppy
Little Johnny was in the classroom,
bored to the back teeth on a Friday afternoon,
and the teacher decided to have a game for the kids
to get them thinking.
Okay class, now I'm going to say a famous quote,
and the first person to tell me what the quote,
who said that quote, can have the Monday off,
so the teacher, who is credited with writing the phrase,
to be or not to be?
That is the question, answered the teacher, as the teacher.
Little fam lamb, fam lamb, win,
at the front of the class called out Shakespeare.
Well done, said the teacher. You're going to have Monday off.
No, thank you, miss. I'm a Vietnamese origin, and it is our culture to study as hard as we can,
so I will be here on Monday studying hard, said little Pham Lam Nguyen.
Well, okay said the teacher the next quote is I had a dream little free some cut is also at the front yelled
I believe was Martha Luther King. Well done customer teacher. You can have Monday off. No, thank you miss
I'm of Chinese origin. We also do not take time off of school education is everything to us
I'll be in on Monday studying hard to so little free some cut
Okay, so the teacher
Then she heard a voice in the back of the classroom
Effing Asians who said that you know the teacher in an angry tone
Donald Trump said little Johnny see you Tuesday
I'm sorry, you love little Johnny jokes. Yeah, they're fine
Little Johnny is sitting in a class, the teacher is going over vocabulary words.
She has the class to use a word of a sentence.
The word the teacher says is contagious.
Little Johnny is waving his arm up and down. No other students have their arm up. The teacher figures
There's no way Johnny can come up with something rude for this word
So she calls his name to use the word in a sentence Johnny says the other day
My dad and I were driving down the freeway and women and women was painting the billboard
She was using a very small brush the teacher says what does this have to do with the word contagious?
Johnny says my dad turned to me and said son is going to take that contagious
To paint the billboard with that little brush
See you next Tuesday. Yep. How about one day in class the teacher asked calls on little Johnny and
Asked him to tell the class a story with a moral in it
So Johnny says one day at the farm a chicken and a horse were playing together
The horse falls into quicksand and so he implores the chicken to go get the farmer
He can't find him anywhere. So he jumps into his BMW
Backs it up near the horse throws a rope around the horse and pulls them out
The next day, they are playing together again, but this time the chicken falls into quicksands.
The chicken says, quick, go get the car, pull me out. The horse listens to the distance and
sees that the farmer has taken the car, so he straddles over the hole. The chicken grabs his
penis and the horse pulls him out. The teacher is confused. Okay, Johnny, but what's the moral
of the story? She says, Johnny replies, if you're hung like a horse, you don't need a BMW to pick up
Any more? Let me see.
Little Johnny was in Bible study one morning Sally was sleeping in front of Johnny the teacher asked Sally who our Lord and Savior was
Little Johnny poked her in the butt with a pin and she screamed Jesus Christ
And went back to sleep a little while later the teacher asked Sally who created our world Johnny poked her in the butt again
And Sally's confused oh my god and fell back to sleep later the teacher asked Sally
What Eve said to Adam when they had their fifth child Johnny poked her in the butt and Sally's if you stick that thing in me
One more time. I'm gonna break it and the teacher fainted
Okay. Johnny moves to a new town. He joins the local PB football team and for the first
game the coach lets him start. Once the first quarter is over...
The coach checks the roster and sees that there are a few kids who need to get some more game time
So he says to let little Johnny play another quarter before replacing him as a team huddle the coach says to little Johnny
Hey, Johnny, you're playing great
But I'm gonna have to put you pull you off at halftime little Johnny replies Wow
Oh, we got with my old team with Gatorade. Oh
my god, I
Don't know if you get that but
Okay
So little Johnny was pulling a wagon up the steep hill this motherfucking wagon is so fucking heavy
God fucking damn it. Oh, hold on. I have something in the back. Oh, sorry, Gotti
No, no problem and go ahead finish
Okay, okay
Okay, so little Johnny was pulling a wagon up a steep hill this motherfucking wagon so fucking heavy God fucking damn it
How long is this bitch a hill?
Uh, how long is this bitch in the hill?
Call it, said Johnny.
Little Johnny passed a priest while cussing up a storm.
Hey, Little Johnny, you know it's bad to swear.
God is always watching, the priest said.
God is watching, Little Johnny said.
Well, yes, of course. God is everywhere, said the priest.
Well, where is he? I don't see him, said Johnny.
Right here.
The priest said, well, he's been your wagon.
Little Johnny said, well, tell him to get the fuck out and start pushing.
Oh, that's so fucking blasphemous.
Holy shit. It's not as blasphemous as you use in the name of God. I got a story for you. Listen to this story
That's how they're gone. I just had to go on, you know what I'm just kidding.
You're gonging me? You're gonging me?
I got more if you want to hear it.
All right.
That's a classic.
You don't think that's funny?
Thank you, Gotti.
Thank you for sharing.
Oh, I think I lost them.
I think I lost them actually.
Okay, anyway, let's continue with the jokes.
Right, do you guys anybody on reddit for you? That's pretty good. Let's see
There once was a revs website called reddit
Which users could read view and edit the joke sub was boring each clip had these knowing because someone had already said it
Pretty good
Um, said the neighbor said said the nun is the bishop with drew not bad for a bishop
It's true, but the prick of the vicar is slicker and thicker and two inches longer than you
Okay
There was was it there was a young woman named Jenny whose limericks was not worth the penny
Oh, the rhyme was all right, and the meter was tight, but whenever she tried to write any, she always wrote one line too many.
Dear Lord.
Some of these lyrics. Okay.
Okay, so there once was a young man from Belgrave who kept a dead whore in a cave.
He said, I admit, I'm a bit of a shit, but think of the money I saved.
There once was a man named Dave, who found, okay, I got that one.
Okay, there once, this is a toast to give at bars, okay.
Here's to you, here's to me, hope we never disagree.
If we do, well then fuck you, here's to me.
Here's to the girl in the little red shoes.
She'll drink your liquor and she'll drink your booze.
She's lost her cherry, it's a terrible sin,
but she still has the box that the cherry came in.
I found this one scrolled at local beach change rooms and once was a young lady from
healing who had this wonderful feeling she lay on her back and opened her crack and
pissed all over the ceiling and once was a man from Peru who fell asleep in his canoe
while dreaming of Venus he played with his penis then woke up with a handful of goo there's
a cute little vampire named Mabel her period's always always stable when it's full moon she
The dirty old witch of Bogota has elued Pagoda, and the walls of the halls were festooned with the balls and the tools of the fools who bestowed her.
There once was a man from Nantucket who thought, I should come in a bucket.
So he came, and he came, and thought, that was lame, and he said, fuck it, and chugged it.
A weird-less young farmhand named Cole accidentally was milking a bull.
The farmer said, boy, you're dumb. You've done milk the wrong one.
But said the boy, but let me hold buckets full.
There once was a girl from Madrid who thought she was having a kid, so up her hole she shoved rubber and coal and popped out a Dunlop non-skid.
There was a fellow named Jaro who tried to fuck a sparrow. The sparrow said no, you can't have a go, the cheeks of my fanny are too narrow.
There once was a girl named Alice. She used a dynamite stick for a phallus. They found
her vagina in South Carolina and bits of her asshole in Dallas. There was a man from Dundee
who buggered an ape in a tree. The result was most horrid, all ass and no forehead, blue
Miss Lois was visiting Trent, got lonely the story went, she was found quite dead with
a hole in her head for it seems like she went down on Clark Kent.
A scream that resounded for Miles rang out from the crypt of St. Giles.
The big car said, gracious, it's brother Ignatius, he's forgotten the bishop has piles.
There was a woman from Neath who circumcised men with her teeth if it wasn't for fame or
love of the game, but to get the cheese underneath.
There once was a young lady named Grace who said if the whole human race depends on what's a boy called the twat
Then it's put in a damn awkward place
There once was a queer from cartoon who took a lesbian up to his room
They argued all night over who had the right to do what and with which and to whom
There once was a man from Madras whose balls were made out of glass
He'd bang them together and place stormy weather while lightning shot out of his ass
There once was a girl from the Azores who's cut was covered in sores the dogs in the street cute chewed out the green meat
Which hung from blood spatter drawers. Okay, that's just disgusting. I'm sorry guys. I'm sorry. I was just disgustingly nasty
Oh, it's when he's coming. Hey, be that. How are you sweetie?
There was was a gay named ghost who played all his money to host everybody booze so psyche was sued
Okay, and now is so is left right beside her. No, that's not good
Goddy, come on
And what about my soap, Beedah's Kitties?
They're wild, yeah, they're pretty good.
Okay, Beedah, how've you been?
Okie-dokie, Gaudi's just a little sore.
That kicked him off.
Boo-hoo.
Okay.
At least we're a little Johnny.
My mate told me this, describing the best,
okay, so we already got that one, okay.
Go back.
Okay.
Okay, well now, this tablet is making me upset.
Okay, there it goes, back back.
Okay.
Okay, let's see.
Little Johnny was in a seat in an airplane and a fellow passenger took the seat next to him. The stranger said hi
As long as we're going to be traveling companions for the next three hours. Let's talk
I've heard that the place will go quicker if you strike up a conversation with your fellow passenger
Little Johnny who had just opened his book closed it slowly and said to the stranger. Okay. What would you like to discuss?
Oh, I don't know said the stranger. How about nuclear power?
Okay, says little Johnny. This could be an interesting topic, but let me ask you a question first a horse a cow and a deer all eat grass
They all eat the same stuff get a deer excrete little pellets which a cow turns into a flat patty and the horse produces clubs of dry grass
What do you suppose that is?
Geez to the stranger. I have no idea and
It says well then said little Johnny. How is it you feel qualified to discuss nuclear power? Well, you don't know shit
Okay
the teacher
A teacher gave her fifth grade class an assignment. They were to have their parents tell them a story with the moral
I got this one already. Oh
Oh
Hi, hey Saxon
Hi, how are you? What are you reading?
Just some like little Johnny jokes off of reddit. They're like you ever heard of them like
Little Johnny's always telling these outrageous punchlines. You're very very easily amused
You're right. I am
I'm a cheap dig so I'll I'm gonna send you some stories that are gonna blow your fucking mind
They're good. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, and then you can read them
Don't make them up. How have you been? I've been okay. I mean I watched I was in your room the other night
I didn't say anything, but I was like I was in your room a lot the other night
I think you did like the 18 hours of streams or epic streams
There's 20 hours 20 hours. Oh, wow
Yeah, I know 20 hours of bullshit
I know what have you been up to?
about the rules so I didn't know when I should come up. I know you do one-on-one so I was like
Yeah
The rule is it's like I'll do one-on-one, but if it's gonna be an open panel with a multiple people then it was on top. I
Am I am how can you we do it one-on-one when we're just side-by-side?
Cuz well, I can make it like this hold on the layout you can put yourself in
Yeah, I can't like this here. Oh come on. I feel like a little mini person now. Oh, I'm on top now
bend over
Well, yeah, that's it. At least we're equal or side by side. I don't want to be ahead or behind anybody
I don't walk side by side because like that's how friends walk. Let me see change this play out
Let me just let's go. Let's go. Yeah, that's good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I've been good like I've I cleaned my like house
and so and I also was able to order a back to get a new vacuum cleaner because my old one's broken and
It was pretty crazy the last couple nights on the show with ghosts
It's just pretty crazy.
Well, last night, it goes paid to take over the panel,
basically.
And it was a little bit of a disaster.
It was funny.
And then the night before, he also paid to.
It was just crazy.
He wanted to keep Summer up.
And then he's like, OK, we'll keep Summer up for five minutes.
And then he kicked her off for five minutes.
And then he'd like, run her back.
And then I don't know what he wants.
He just said he won't be clear with what he asked.
I've been doing tarot cards. I'll show you the cards I have. I don't know if you've seen
yours yet. Have you seen yours yet? I drew a card of you. Hold on. I'll go through the order of
the cards. These are just prototypes. I might redesign them a little bit with some of my own
stuff, but there's the fool card. You're in that one. See? They're laughing at me.
Okay, and then we have the magician. Okay, and then here's you
Yeah, I look evil
You're the emperor the Empress look evil
Okay, I know it ain't the color
Looks like
And this is like the high priestess kind of came out similar to page. I'll say the page inspired. Okay. There's the high priestess
Thank you, and then I did like one kind of like pop culture one for the emperor. Here's the there's the emperor
And then I do and then I have one of Christina's the higher fit here's Christina's the higher fit
Oh, wow! That is so cute though!
Yeah!
And we have then I did like here's a summer inspired what I close to I can't get the tattoos all perfect and stuff
But this is summer inspired is straight
And then I have a DG a lecture I asked for I put her photo through and I made her the queen of swords
That's the DG lecture of her avatar space
And then I did ghost, you know after he donated I did one of ghosts and so here's ghosts of the hangman
Does this ghost look like that?
Yes, they're putting up his photo.
He looks kind of like, well, I just kind of said like,
he has long hair.
He's like kind of like a little bit on the bigger side
as artists.
He's very short, man.
Are you going to make one for Flirty Diamond too?
Yeah, I will, I'll make one for you.
I think so, you know.
What do you want to make of that one?
Hmm, I might make her a queen like a queen of something like a queen of
What's her brother Simon, but I might make her a queen or maybe a princess or like a page or something
Because yeah, it's really like well queen because you know
Queen no, but I don't know. I'm not sure. I don't know exactly what would be perfect
But yeah, I do want to do it after people in the community
I'll put
You know, I think hopefully, like, you know, I'll try to do a Sam and car
Different people I know and some airplanes over there
Yeah, oh, actually
Spunky got me a car on these car deck called the true prime deck and that was like one of the cars in the next of plane
They have a cigarette what else we pull we pull the shovel before the graveyard for the casino has a really cool
I'm true prime cars like we're
I told some of those.
There was a guy named Digger.
Oh, God, I don't want to see anything wrong with Digger.
Okay, so we read the trickster.
Oh yeah, but the trickster is gonna be the magician.
The trickster.
And so, but also I think maybe there's like a juggler card.
Like, I guess that would be like the fool
or the magician are kind of like the more trickstery,
but I'll have to find another Gemini.
kind of type card. That's very trickster energy, mercury. Yeah, I'll figure it out. I mean,
I'm working with the AI and the AI has a really good idea. It also has a memory of things. So
it's constantly referencing things I said and how about this here? Like, this here, it's like,
it's really good. I really am enjoying the AI. So bring Gadi up. Come on. Gadi was just up.
Yeah, I'll go down so Gadi can come off.
He's not here. He's not even backstage. And he's already been up twice tonight. And so it's like,
He's not taking away anything. There's nobody backstage or anything. It's like it's getting a little quieter. Sometimes there are 22 people in the chat
So it's like, you know
Some people did not did not understand
I thought I was charging for like everybody to come on and it's like no
It's a guy the whole thing with the panel. I put the rules in the description
I think from what I understood was like you want to do one-on-ones
But if you want someone like you want a panel you want someone to sponsor it and then that person does sponsors it
They can kick off somebody off the panel that they don't want, right?
No, I mean that that was that I was doing that for ghosts because ghosts donated a lot of money
He donated over a hundred dollars, but like that's why you don't know much on you
Well, I'm I think he's a great wonderful nice guy. He's like he's like he was like I'm like your big brother
Like he's like he's like he's I'm gonna defend you and he's like really like I believe he means it means it too
I think he was he's like on my side and
You know, did you hear about Michael? What happened?
Michael L. Yeah, is he okay?
No, oh
What happens you car accident or?
No, he's no longer in this world with us. He's passed away. Yeah, what happens? I
Don't know exactly. It's like the arbitrary says it was unexpected, but
No, it was July 18th
My god, yeah, I feel bad, you know, it's like because you know the last I think one of the last times I talked to him
I think I would didn't talk to him after he was kicked off like the last time I think but it's like and we he always said
Hey, I love you. I love you and I'm like, he's like, you know, I'd never mad at you or whatever
So that's nice, but then it's like I feel bad cuz I did kick him off like the last two times with a gong and it's like
Um, yeah, I mean that's you always, you know, it's a natural reaction to kind of feel like, okay
You know, it's just because you know, it's like no matter no matter what you really don't want to hear bad news about someone
Even though you don't like them like I personally gonna like him because you know the shit that he did to like Tracy
And just constant like bugging me. I mean he really went out me
But yeah, I feel bad about putting him backstage, you know, but yeah, I just didn't know if you knew
It was a rumor going around, but then it was it was confirmed, you know, that's super sad. That's sad. You know, it's like, you know, and I always did like Michael like I kind of had a crush on him, like that's why I would have him on a lot.
He was kind of like, you know, he was kind of like bragging about what he did to Tracy and stuff like that.
Yeah, there is HK. There is HK. I just thought today.
Oh, that's sad. God rest his soul. You know, Michael, I hope that, you know, you're out of pain. I hope that you're
That's exactly that's one thing is that I
Won't never be fake about that. Like I was you know, of course
It's pretty it's sad because of you know with people's family and even like you think okay
Maybe I was a jerk, but like that's that's nothing that I would feel like, you know
Was that what you mean is it's I didn't I didn't know him that well
I really think I really think of this world as a very temporary place
Like I really do I think it's like and the time the time we spend here is like such a tiny little slip on like the radar of the all
All time all of time, you know
It's like this word is here for like a little second on this earth and it's gone and it's like and before we know it like
You know either will be the last one of our family or the
And we'll watch everyone pass away or we'll be the first to go and everyone and everyone's like there's gonna be one person
That's that everyone's funeral, you know
So we know, but you know, I know I have like a big, like I have a lot of families.
So, you know, there's like a lot of people, if I live a long time, I'll have to
probably have a lot of people pass away and it's sad.
And, uh, but no, I do believe in afterlife.
And that keeps me thinking that they're in a better place and that their soul is
free and hopefully they're onto their dreams.
You know, it's like, yeah, I just.
That's, that's exactly how I feel like HK as well is like, you know, I do feel bad for him as family, but you know, it's not enough for me to like get emotional and cry over it. Yeah, we are all gonna die.
Even in that speed I think some men as little toy. No, I don't I was just saying what happened
I didn't know if psyche heard what happened because first it was like kind of like rumors
You never know because I know I've been in the community where people have like lie
They faked it. They've you know all kinds of stuff, but yeah, it was confirmed
Yeah, yeah
Maybe I'll maybe I'll maybe you know, maybe we'll have a somebody might have a dream about him or like, you know
Maybe I'll hear like a whisper or something like that
I think he's like I do think he was like a
Good a good guy at heart, you know
It's like he was a little bit like on the defensive because of everything
I know just online stuff and so and he would like you know upset people and stuff
But I think he was not a bad person and I you know God was in peace Michael. It's sad. That's really sad
But maybe like an angel now helping maybe he can help people and you know
It's finally getting some rest from people saying payback Tracy
Well
Ziki Aldous Ziki used to love me but
Why once I decided to put him backstage and not deal with him because he was being racist now
I'm a little bird brain. Okay. All right, you deal with your little chicken brains, dude
It's the same thing as the KZ KZ
I like didn't like let him up one night because I was doing the one-at-a-time thing
He's like he just saw the going off on me now. He's gone to Emma Levi-tons discord and chat and like I don't so
You know, God rest your soul too, KZ, it now belongs to Emma, you know, I got out of the contract, but you just step right into it. Smart move, buddy.
Anyway, so let's see, Dogo.
Turn on the drain backstage.
Okay, well, I'll have them on.
Do you want me to leave and then I'll pop them up?
Yeah
I don't I don't need to leave but yeah, but I'm just doing the one is yeah, we'll do a switcheroo. I'll be back
I'll be back in the chair. Okay. Okay. Love you. Love you sweetie. Bye. Okay. Oh
Connet you know, what's up? Oh, I thought it was Popeye for a second. No, it's like a little bear little bear with a little
It's little pretty nice man
Oh, well, he's not wearing pants. So it's probably balls are probably cold, but okay never mind it. So, um, yeah, HK Memphis
Hey, yes person. Yeah, you know, I just wanted to sorry
I you guys are talking about this guy and I'm trying to figure out is it the blonde guy who used to come on and he's kind of loud
Yeah, you always fight with data and like and like, you know, he would always like they say, you know
He's always been a bad mood because he like apparently like was eating Tracy and then he like kind of dumped her after she'd send me
800 bucks and like he's like I'm never paying her back. I don't know if you're
I'm just trying to figure out who he is. Did he used to hang out on TPV? Do you know I?
Don't know. I mean, I've had him at Benny's and he used to hang out here a lot
I don't know if he went to that many places, other places, but he was like a blonde kid.
Not skinny, but not fat.
He was like he kind of looks ahead like that kind of like a he was like Puerto Rican
But he was like I kind of looked white and he might have had like lighter hair
But I'm not sure he like always has if you have short hair or shaved head or something
I'm you can like look at it like you had the goatee and the girlfriend
I'm can but yeah with a girlfriend named them though
If you would say her name is Mary or something her name is Mariah or Mary and it was more yeah, they'd come on together
Yeah, yeah that guy mm-hmm
Yeah
So he's passed away
And uh, yeah kind of sad he was I think he was pretty young too. I think he was in his maybe 30 years old or something like that
I think he was a little bit younger. He was not blonde. Yeah, but he kind of had like a almost like a
No, he had like brown hair kind of no and like a goatee. No, I remember that I was confused about two different people trying to figure out
Who it was that's wild
Yeah, pretty sad. I mean, I don't know how it happened. It says that the beneficiary didn't have that information, but
If I had to guess I would say maybe it's something congenital
Congenital heart defect or something like that because it's very unusual just to pass away out of in there
But I can't speculate
This is Canada dry up on panel. Well, I'll take it. All right. No, I can get down
I just I'm just trying to figure out who it was that that's so crazy
Yeah, it is crazy. God rest your soul, Michael. Hopefully, you know, you're in a better place.
Kind of sad. Kind of sad because he was gonged all the time off the show, I think. And then he's in the song, too, in that song.
He's always memorialized Michael. He's never got to hear the song, but he's always memorialized in the song.
Michael getting gonged. And when the guy in the video dies, too. Oh my god, that's really weird.
Oh, hey, Jamie Rose. How are you? Jamie Rose is here. You remember him? Yeah, it's like he's he's in the song though
He's my more he's he made it. He made a song, you know, he got into my song. So that's pretty cool
so did uh
We'll play the song. Yeah, okay. I'll play the song. So here's
Here's the song with Michaels. It has the gong scene in it here. Here you go. It's Michael's song
Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Sikes twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob splashing on cam chat losing their minds my
getting gong. Alex taking flight. It's wild. It's wrong and we do it every night. Paige got
him simping hearts in the chat, but she ain't got time for a dude like that. Diamond flirting hard,
let the girls react. It's a freak show party, no filter, all facts. Yo.
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex tried a joke boom sent into the night
Panel looking sideways someone's got a fight
Producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low. Oops. She says with a wink
That's the whole show sides half asleep but still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls we pretend to play one hand on the mute other letting it spray
wrong word and we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight boob
smashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight it's wild
it's wrong and we do it every night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't
got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show
party no filter all facts yeah
Lights out one more round beat is on the line yelling at a ghost from a bottle of wine. We laugh we cry we crash rewind
Same time next week, you know the vibe
Welcome the madness
Enjoy the ride
Yeah, welcome to the madness
I
Need to ask you a question
Did I offend you did I offend you last night a couple people told me that I offended you
No, I was
Said we had a great time last night. I said to them. I I think psyche didn't even think about me
Like at all and we had a great time last night. He made some money the last year
I remember you saying like, you know, I remember the night like, uh, like the ghost said, oh
Kick Athens off the panel or whatever. Exactly. And it was great, but you but you said
Yeah, you said something really nice to me after that
I didn't mind getting kicked off. I wanted you got money. We got content like people take shit so seriously
They're like you offended psyche. He's mad at you. I was like, yo, it's like he doesn't even they're not even thinking about me
What the fuck are you talking about? Yeah, I'm gonna see how you feel tonight. I'm feeling good. Yeah
I mean, I'm not no, I like you. I mean, you're always good. It's just like oh, yeah
That's it. I just want you to do good. I want you to I want you to make money and I want you to like um
I want you to be successful in your endeavor, you know, being a being a host always
Thank you. Thank you. I want you to clear out of it, man
I want you to fucking be a fucking youtube host as a career and make fucking money and support yourself and be healthy
That's what I really want
I like those pictures of you
I like the pictures of you like, you know, listen, i'm straight heterosexual, but i'm not a fucking like
I'm comfortable with my sexuality to say those pictures are cool that you got up like the glamour shots
Yeah
Cowboy, I'm all about Jamie's cowboy. You know that. Yeah. Yeah
I'm gonna be there one day
Cool, I'm just fucking around all I'm here to do is have fun man
I want everybody to fucking have fun and that song was cool
How like it says next next day rewind, you know, we do the same shit over and over again, and it's just fun
Yeah, I have some of these. Yeah, you see these new AI pictures of uh,
Of one see the newest ones. I need to I need to download it. Let me see
Look at Memphis shay. I miss coke. Yeah, bro back in a day
20s, bro. You and I would be chilling
Yo Ziggy, what's good? See all the comments Jamie's cowboy right a big blue heart right back to you, honey
You're a beautiful fucking woman. I always got you back
Who else we got?
Yo, wait a minute. It says Michael linguine 2025
Yeah, he passed away. Wait a minute. That's not the guy that was on here that had the girlfriend in like yep. Yep
Yeah, how did he die? Please don't tell me drugs. It doesn't say on the obituary. It's oh my god, bro
You know we he had a lot of
Mental health issues with like being like jealous and worried that people were like
You know like how he looked he was always like you know, and I was like Mikey man. You're a nice guy
Why do you have to like make it about you and then defend it? Like why can't you just?
Fuck I feel bad. I know I hope he didn't commit suicide or anything like that because
I don't think so, but he said he died unexpectedly and so it seems like okay. Okay. Okay. Okay good
Thank you for saying that so nobody make anything up no rumors, you know, we don't have any
Does anybody know him personally where we can just find out?
Well, I mean I had it. I mean I had his number at one point
You know, I don't know if his girlfriend is still, you know, or is you know, Mora if she ever wants to call in and give a
Yeah, please do you know listen everything aside?
You know rest in peace and and like you said, I feel bad, but yeah
He got he got he was he was gonged off the show many times and kind of like you know
But he'd always sit backstage and stuff
You know now he's gone. I fucked with him a little bit when he like got like with you tried to fuck with beta a little bit
Remember like like yeah, he took and beta like slapped him up like verbally, right?
Like she always shut him down and then I had to do that a couple times too when he got out of line and but
all that shit is bullshit you know that don't mean anything he's that's a life snuffed and
that's that's really terrible like I hope his family yeah he's think about his mother you know
that's what people have to realize and no parent ever see their child die before them
beat it if you're out there love you girl you know I'll show you a few pictures so here's
so here's uh Memphis you're correct to Memphis you're correct to all right bro like
Memphis says it's nobody business. You're right. That's the family
Right, you're right
Yeah
Thank you. Can you get me? I'm gonna be straight honest with you
It's late and I'm in a car and I'm making moves if you know what that means
I'm not trying to act tough, but um, I'm gonna be right back. Okay. Okay, you don't have to take me off
I'm gonna I'm making a phone call. I think it'll cut the verbal thing and you won't be able to hear you
Okay, I was thinking about fire hydrant. No, I was not I'll go back to that
I don't know if you'll be able to hear me right now, but I'm making a phone call if you guys hear this and say it's funny
Okay
Let's see what was that when I was worried sitting by the campfire I think
Lost already
Okay, I'll go slowly here
Dude, it's kind of like my dad used to dress but you guys they put this all like they put all the clothes that I'm wearing right here
Like on like the description and so I get and I'll like words on sale
And so I get I can actually order these outfits and like dress like this. I
Want to see right and how good I would look right? I just need to shave
You know fix my hair a little bit. That is my face. I mean they just put it on different bodies
I don't know how it knows so well how I look I mean in those from the side and everything it has a lot of different expressions and stuff
Here I'm gonna skate at the hockey game, right?
I was a host of the hockey game. They're traveling
I'm on a safari right here. I didn't have this interesting life
Okay, so here's the campfire picture though, where is it here? I'm not sitting on a fire hydra. See it's a bench
It's me on a regular bench
I'm sitting alone in the rafters that would be some kind of game right there.
There.
On a yacht.
I mean, that's some kind of fancy restaurant or I'm just walking around.
I had to be careful.
Oh, here's a Christmas.
Here's not Christmas morning one day.
Christmas.
A cool fire shirt.
I'm gonna strike a polo, like a rugby shirt.
It's like you have a question.
Why do people like beta wait until a person dies
and they say a nice thing?
Well, it's not beta, it's not people like beta.
It's like everybody, like when my grandmother died,
you know, I love my grandmother,
but it's like, there's regrets, right?
If you don't hold on to this guy,
hold on, I'm gonna put the math in backstage.
Oh, right here.
Hello, what the hell are you going going on about now, dude?
Well, we're talking about Michael passed away, you know, and I don't know that guy
Okay, well, he was on the show several times and you know, I've known him for about a year my condolences
Yeah, kind of said
Controversy playing that AI crap again, huh? You're playing that AI shit. Remember. I told you it's like yeah, that's what's up artists like me
That is like with artists. It is. Yeah, it is
Yeah, cuz I told you I make my own songs and you're like, oh, I want to hear it sometime
I said, I make it for myself and you're like, oh, whatever
Okay, well, whatever if you don't want to play it for me, it's fine. I'm not okay. Give me a sec. Here we go
Let me know if you can hear it
Is the copyright or anything? Oh, it's me. Okay
Here we go. Let me know if you can hear it. I
Want to fuck a big booty practice with them big
I don't want to hear it. I mean, please
No, it's not music that you know, it's better is like MC Nemesis's song with better and all it was was the Edward
Okay, and MC Nemesis had a better song than that. So now all he said was the Edward over and over. So anyway
Thank you though. Thank you for you know, I don't want to like, you know, make the audience's ears bleed from like to talk about disrespectful
That is disrespectful to music in general. But those kind of lyrics in there a rapper. I
Love some of the sort of rap rap has the word
Like crap. You think it's a banger? Well, you should like you know become a groupie sweepie
BKG getting there. Thank you again. I'm learning everything all over. Oh, Jamie's all
You're learning to rewalk. Oh my gosh
Yeah, okay, it was oh, it was hilarious. You know, it's just like
Kind of dumb. We try to try to attack the dermis to work on niche as late body and put it in the living room. Oh, okay
Well, that must have taken a lot of stuffing, you know a lot of
He said I have a black pill moses on the show. Can you ask him to come?
Ask him to come over here. I
Need a hey summer if you have a suggestion it was comedy. I know I know
It was it wasn't just wasn't funny to me. I'm not in the mood
Take the window to get in the room. I don't know. I think they just taxed the dummy to her in the living room
I don't think they just left they just left her in the house. It was I think she was too big to
Move so tax the dermis here
No, and she, you know, she, she, she will feed an entire city, you know,
and maybe I need to die for, you know, she will, that's me for everybody.
It's okay, I'm just not, sometimes I'm not in the mood, you know, I'm just like,
I just woke up a little bit ago, I'm a, I'm under a lot of stress,
and I don't want to hear about big, booty black women and,
Hi babe.
and fucking them and stuff.
No, it's just like, yeah, show your chicken hole, Ziggy.
Okay.
I want to I wish I looked like that. I'm gonna look like that
It looks like instead of it looks like Jeffrey Dahmer
Distortion I don't think so
Okay, it says I said a teacher gave her fifth grade class in assignment
They were to have their parents tell them a story with a moral.
The next day the kids came to class one by one told their stories.
Little Kathy raised her hand first and said,
we live on a farm and we have hens that lay eggs for market.
Once we were taking a basket of eggs to market on the front seat of the pickup truck,
we hit a big bump in the road.
The eggs were flying and broke all over everything.
And what is the moral of that story?
Don't put your eggs in one basket.
Very good said the teacher.
Then little Tami raised her hand and said we live on a farm too but we raise chickens
for the meat market.
We have a dozen eggs once but when they hatch we only get 10 live chicks and the moral of
the story is don't count your chickens before they're hatched.
That was a fine example Tami, Johnny I believe you had your hand up next.
He goes yes ma'am, my daddy told me that my aunt Sara was a flight engineer in Desert
Storm and her plane got hit.
She had to bail out her enemy territory and all she had was a bottle of whiskey, a machine
gun and a machete.
She drank the whiskey on the way down so it wouldn't break then she landed right in the middle of a hundred enemy soldiers
She killed 70 of them with the machine gun until she ran out of bullets
Then she killed 20 more with the machete and before the blade broke off
Then she killed at least 10 with her bare hands and then it says good heavens of the horrified teacher
What did your daddy tell you was the moral of that terrible story?
And he says we'll save the hell away from Aunt Sarah when she's been drinking hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
Are you crazy?
Frickin tricks is that going nuts
Okay, okay
Um, let's see little Johnny's mom and dad couldn't have babies. So she went to a Nash net
NATO natal path here. Yeah, we're his heart is beating like a drum
Okay, she went to a Nate Nate natural path to put three ball bearings up mom
So the sperm would have something to grip to nine months later
Johnny had two brothers who were born and they turned 13 the first brother went to mom and mom said I was having a
We and a ball bearing came out so mom told me what happened next day brother. She went to mom and
Told her he was having a wee and the ball bearing came out on the third day little Johnny came up
Mom said I know you're having a wee and a bearing came out and Johnny said no mom
I'm having a wake spanking the monkey or whatever and shot the cat cats make great
Cray bait and very warm hats to kill them all
I was on a good one. Okay
It goes Patrick who was holidaying from Ireland on Bondi Beach couldn't seem to make it with any of the girls
So he had the local lifeguard for some advice
Mate is obvious in the lifeguard. If you're wearing them old baggy swimming trunks that make you look like an old geezer
Yours are out of style your best bet is to grab yourself a pair of Speedos about two sizes too small and drop a fist-sized
Potato down inside them. I'm telling you man. You'll have all the babes you want the following weekend Patrick hits the beach with his
Fanking a new tight speedo and his fist-sized potato
Everybody on the beach were disgusted as he walked by covering their faces turning away laughing looking sick
So Patrick went back to the lifeguard again and said what's wrong now?
He says, Jesus, in the lifeguard, mate, the potato goes in front.
There was once a tomato, who lived on a farm, but he was very afraid because the chickens
liked to eat tomatoes, so he uprooted himself and rolled down a hill into the forest.
One day a man came walking to the forest, picked him up and ate him.
The moral, no matter what you do, you end up dead.
Okay.
Well, speaking of Little Johnny, here's another one of the jokes.
One day Little Johnny asked his mom what sex was.
Tonight, go to your sister's room, hide behind the curtain, and watch what she and her boyfriend
do.
Little Johnny explained well first they were kind of talking and laughing but after a while they started kissing and hugging sister
Got a fever because she was feeling hot
So sisters boyfriend put his hand up under her shirt to find her heart just like the doctor would accept
He's not so smart because both of them got sick and they started panting and getting a lot of breath
His other hand must have been cold because he put it under her skirt about this time
This got worse then begin to moan and sigh and squirm around and slide into the end of her bed
And I finally found out that was making him sick a big eel had gotten inside her boyfriend's pants somehow
Just jumped out of his pants and stood there about ten inches long. Anyway, he grabbed it in one hand and kept it
From getting away when sis saw she got really scared her eyes got big her mouth fell open
She started calling to god and stuff like that. She said it was the biggest one she'd ever seen
I should tell her about the ones by the lake anyhow sis got brave and tried to kill the eel by biting its head off
All of a sudden she grabbed it with both hands and tried to keep it from biting again
Sis laid back and spread her legs so she could put a scissor lock on it and her boyfriend helped by lying on top of the eel
The eel put up a heck of a fight sis started moaning and squealing and her boyfriend almost upset the couch
I guess they wanted to kill the eel by squishing it between them.
After a while they both stopped moving and gave a great sigh.
Her boyfriend got up and sure enough he had killed the eel.
I know because they just hung there and also because some of the insides were dripping
out.
Sis and her boyfriend were a little tired from the battle, but went back to bed anyway.
He started hugging and kissing her again. By golly, the eel wasn't dead.
It jumped straight up and started to fight again. I guess eels are like cats.
They have nine lives or something like that. This time, Sis jumped up and tried to kill it
by sitting on it. After a 35-minute struggle, they finally killed the eel. I knew it was
dead because I saw Sis and his boyfriend peel its skin off and flush it down the toilet.
Okay, one day, Little Johnny and Dad went shopping.
While they were out, they stopped at the neighborhood drug store
to pick up a couple of things.
While they were walking through the aisles,
they passed the place where condoms were sold.
Little Johnny asked his dad what they were.
Dad excited, it was time for the talk,
because we explained the mechanics of it all
and why some people would use a condom.
Little Johnny looks up at the box
and pulls it off the rack and says,
well, it says that there are two in this box.
Who would buy two of them?
Dad sighed and,
Realizing a little Johnny was still the age where girls had cooties that were meant to be teased and well Johnny
Those are for boys that are in high school. They buy one for Friday night and one for Saturday
Johnny look at his dad and put the box back
They didn't pick up all the box with three off the rack and these who buys these yes
Dad said oh these are for college men one for Friday one for Saturday one for Sunday
Johnny looks at his dad not as it puts the box back. Finally. He pulls out a very large box off the rack very impressive
And says, gee, dad, this has what has 12.
Who buys these?
Dad looks a little sad and says, well, Johnny,
those are for married men, Johnny says.
But dad, they're only seven days in a week
and you have to go to work and stuff, right?
Oh, no, Johnny, his dad, you misunderstood a bit.
The big box is for the married men.
One is for January, one's for February,
one's for March, one's, and so on and so on.
Okay.
So it's for a year.
A year supply, basically, for married men.
Mm-hmm
Ah
Guys, did you know that Helen Keller had a dollhouse in her backyard? Did you know that?
Well neither did she
Sorry, that's a little bit dark, I'm sorry
Oh god
Man, but you can never please that guy random guy. He just he's playing about everything. Okay. I talked to you fast
I stutter I play AI songs. I read for say if you don't like my fucking show, why are you?
I mean, it's like I complain about everything
via
Tell me this is the excellent version
Um
What do biscuits eat for a treat?
Bish and chocolate chips
What do biscuits do when they're happy they give a crumbs up
Why was the biscuit so rich it earned a packet
Why are biscuits meaner than cakes because they're twice as hard
Why do biscuits? What do biscuits use to fix things?
Jaffa tape. Look at that. Okay
Why which biscuit is always insulting people? A biscuit
What did the biscuits say when it got in trouble?
crumbs
What biscuit floats? A water biscuit. What's the oldest biscuit? A Jimmy Codger. Which biscuit is friendliest?
Nice biscuits. Which biscuit is always picking pockets? The Jammie Dodger.
Which happens to a biscuit when it's asleep? It has custard dreams. How do biscuits pay for things? With chocolate chips and a pin.
Which biscuit always has an upset tummy a digestive which biscuit is the most royal custard Queens?
Why did the biscuit cry because it's bothered with a wafer so long what's the difference between an elephant and a biscuit?
You can't dip an elephant in your teeth
Okay, I'm over my biscuit thing obviously
I just yeah, I like to do is read some jokes about it kind of takes away the edge
Anyway
But just risk it all for a biscuit, guys.
Risk it for a biscuit.
Why did Bea go to Psyche's?
Because everyone hates her over the, oh, come on.
No, they do not.
Bea had 80 people in her chat, or almost 100.
So obviously, she's doing something right.
Mm-hmm. Why can't why can't Helen killer drive?
Hmm I do too I
Think those are probably British British because they're like they're like words I don't understand them
Little Johnny's third grade teacher asked the class.
She's a word definitely in a sentence.
Johnny was the only student to raise his hands
with the teacher reluctantly calling him.
Miss Smith, do farts have lumps in them?
Johnny, I don't see what that has to do with the question,
but no, farts do not have lumps in them.
And then Johnny says, well,
then I definitely just shit my pants.
Okay, Little Johnny's Sunday school teacher asked the class,
what's the first part of the body that goes to heaven?
Johnny raised his hand and started squirming all around, but luckily the teacher noticed Sherry had her hand up and the teacher
meant motion to her for the answer. Sherry jumps up and says,
It's your hands when you're praising Jesus. Your hands are reaching for the heavens.
The teacher says, very good Sherry. Look around to see who else thinks they know.
She sees little Johnny still dancing around trying to get the teacher's attention, then luckily Holly raises her hand.
The teacher motions for her to answer. Holly jumps in and says, It's your head.
Your head is the highest part of your body and the closest to heaven.
The teacher says, very good, Holly.
Is there anyone else who wants to give it a try?
Reluctantly, she calls on Johnny
as no one else had their hand up.
Johnny jumps in and says, it's your feet.
And the teacher replies, why your feet?
Little Johnny says, I don't know for sure,
but I heard all this commotion coming from my parents room.
I ran over and peeked through the door.
There was my mom with her feet straight up in the air,
yelling at the top of her lungs, oh my God, I'm coming.
And you know, I think she would have went to
if the postman wasn't holding her down.
Okay, and it says Monday was science day.
Each child was supposed to bring something
from home to show the class.
First up was little Susie.
She goes to the front of the class
with some bugs in a jar.
Susie said, these are grasshoppers
I found in the field behind my house.
I punched holes in the lid to let them breathe.
They eat grass.
Very good, said the teacher.
Susie went back to her seat.
Next up was Bobby.
Bobby came to the front of the class
with a drawing of a volcano.
He explained what forms them and how they erupt.
Good job, so the teacher and Bobby returned to his seat the rest of the class presented their science projects in the same way
Eventually all but little Johnny had gone the teacher reluctantly came
Called him to show his project little Johnny came to the front of the class with a shoebox
This is a bullfrog. I found in a pond behind my house. He said after I caught him
I broke into my neighbor's garage and stole a firecracker and shoved it up his ass
Rectum said the teacher damn right at rectum blew his head clean off
No
Hello
Yeah, I'm here. Do you not see the back sometimes, right? People get all like upset. They're like
So he why are you keeping me in the back on purpose? I'm like, yo
Everything doesn't have to be about you. Let him finish his fucking story and he'll let you on the right. Isn't everybody worry
You're mad at me. I couldn't believe these people. I'm not gonna say who they are
But today I like I'm working and I'm like getting messages on YouTube school
Psyche is upset with me.
I start fucking laughing.
I'm like, is this what you people do all day?
Watch YouTube and then talk about Psyche and me and how he's angry.
I don't fuck yourself, man.
Psyche, me and you got a good thing going, brother.
Yeah.
No one really...
I've said
I'm so I'm mad at them unless they're like, you know
I know
Yeah
I'm with your brother
I'm having a this is a Jack in the Box burger
and some sure
California baby
California love
with my Jamie girl at the beauty
Mira Mira on the wall who's the fairest
of them all
Jamie girl
I love you beat up a Jamie girls the fairest of them all
I
Love you beat up
I don't know if there's mess I guess you can do messages on YouTube that post it on your wall
Yeah, they wrote messages on a message board and said psyche is mad at school. He offended him yesterday and
Kicked him off the show. I like you people off fucking idiots
Well, yeah, a lot of people don't watch it and so they hear from other people like they heard like oh
He's a charging ticket on the panel and stuff like that. And then so people are like thinking about it. It's like
I know buddy
I'm in a really bad area right now and on Long Island
See the cops over there. Yeah. Yeah, I'm in a really bad area. It's a tad like a lot of drugs and homeless and
It's really sad. Are you the LA LA E with the Long Island Expressway? That's correct. That's correct route 495
Has 73 exits the first exit is the Queen's Midtown Tunnel
That's the tunnel that connects Queens to Manhattan
That is route 495 exit one is in Queens and exit 73 is in Riverhead all the way out east
I am on the south. All right, so you do you know what Long Island looks like like on a map
It looks like a fish. Do you know what I mean by that?
All right, let's what I want you to do
Can you pull up on a map Long Island really quick? You don't have to put it on the screen, but just for me buddy
Because I'm sexy
Crocodiles to me
No, it doesn't. Look at the tail. Look at the fit. Oh, you mean the mouth. I never thought of that
Yeah, the the tails of the fish are the mouth of the crocodile, right?
Yeah, I mean it can look like both. I mean it's like
psyche
Man, it looks like teeth.
Yeah, yeah, totally. Oh, you got it on this. You're the best, bro. All right, so you want to know where I am right now?
Mm-hmm. Okay. Yeah, so check we put the map up so everybody can see and fuck anyone who's trying to make this bad or anything
So I can I have any good time. Okay, so that's Queen. That's Brooklyn in the left now move it a little bit to your left
We're so yeah now the other way left
Yes, now that's Brooklyn now. That's Nassau County and now go all the way over
Suffolk County, this is where I live and where I am right now is on the south shore. Okay
Now go a little to your right
This way. No the other way the other way. Okay now go down
Right under the word island. Do you see that I?
Am right at the a on that island on that blue road. That's underneath the a that's where I am right now
Oh, I see a lot of islands. You're right. You're a little red dot right there, right?
Love you psyche is such a good guy man. Yeah, the port the name of it the name of the um
The name of the town is Bellport and Jamie girl. I wish it is Jamie girl in the chat
I think I have seen her. Yes, Jamie girl. You're the best mod for psyche. You're sexy as hell
You get the trophy your first place beta is second place. Okay, beta is second place. Jamie girl is first
But I do see the fish too I can see the fish too
Hey, do you agree with me that do you agree with me that Jamie girl is the fairest of them all?
Well, Jamie just has like, you know, I've known Jamie like since then before I started doing the lives
Like she was like and she was just been here since the beginning of the show always wanted to be the best mod
The best mod and I appreciate it. Do you think that Jamie girl is the fairest of them all though?
she definitely has
the most beautiful heart and
And it is very very very fair. Yes, very fair and lovely. She is the sexiest all good things
Jamie girl, are you in the chat? Is she there?
I
Jamie girl you there you out there
Don't see her
Ziggy beat it is third summer is second. Yo
She is Jamie girl. Yo Ziggy good call son
Good call some is a beast. I call
Yeah, I have a
He's still here. I don't take him up.
So Jamie said I can show the pictures of her in the hospital.
She sent me these the day after the accident.
Let me see.
My message is Jamie, okay.
What the heck is that? It's something weird. Oh, no looks from here. It's just a fake oil
Pretty bad, right? Wow, Jamie is so lucky. Thank God. You're okay. It does look
Pretty terrible. Wow, look at the blood the hand is your hand. Okay. Oh my gosh. Oh boy
I saw all of them is that Jamie girls accident. Yeah. Oh my god, Jamie. My hawk goes out to you girl. I'm so happy that you're here. Let's think about Michael where he is right now and where you could have been. I mean it guys everybody out there.
You know take care of each other. I don't give a fuck what you think of me if you think I'm a fucking
What's it called when you like hit on girls or the fucking simp?
I'm a simp. I don't think I don't care if you think I'm a fucking pussy or being feminine
This is real facts. You got to take care of each other man, and you see homeless people, you know hook them up like
We're gonna do that right now. We're gonna go on a mission because I finished my work
I'm gonna go out. I'm gonna go to 7-Eleven. I'm gonna I'm gonna search for a homeless person and I'm gonna feed them
That's what I'm gonna do right now
Okay
Great idea
Yeah, that's what we're gonna do and I want to talk to you about a sweet pee
I gotta go in 7-Eleven to get a drink and I'll be right back. Sure. Absolutely
And everybody you know everybody think about
You see somebody that's hungry
Many some help, you know
Sometimes there's a little bit of encouragement and like maybe like you know giving someone a sandwich or something kid
Excellent psyche their day. Yeah, so that's right the guys. I like fuck all this shit
You know where like it can be small, but then it gets too big and Mike's not here anymore Michael's dead
That's a life that is gone
His mother his father if he has any sibling his girlfriend
I don't imagine what they're feeling right now and be so grateful that you don't feel that way
My name is yeah, my name is school of Athens for a reason empathy is one of the most important
Personality traits that we possess as human beings
The problem is yep
The problem is let's get psychological psyche when ego takes control of our behavior and
We you know
What's the adjective I'm looking for psyche on when when we're in a situation of power
Okay, when we have power over somebody else in control and we enjoy that if that goes on for a long time
We lose the ability and I don't give a fuck out there if anyone's saying this is boring or beat it. Fuck you
We lose the ability to feel empathy for other human beings. That's why I'm not gonna go on with this
I love you Christine
cops they have lost the ability to feel empathy for another person because they're so um uh used
to being in control i'm not going to talk about cops anymore so we have to channel play-doh
aristotle socrates empathy and try to feed try to think about how others feel think about mike
his family right now that's what i want everybody to do take a second think about his mom and how
It's putting yourself in other people's shoes and like knowing how they feel because we are humans
We have to understand this but there's something called dark and past and there are people that have the empathy
But they also have like some kind of like psychopathy or something along with it
So they use their empathy skill just for manipulation
Yeah
So that's a problem that they have dark empathy
But most people have either empathy or dark empathy like the people like this you naturally know how those are feeling unless
There's some psychopaths that really are like or they have like very little emotion, but they know how to fake
That's right. I had a like they know how to watch other people and so they watch other people do it was crying
They cry too. That's what I got. Yeah
So right
I said Christine come up on the panel if you're listening and I love you
Can you hear me now? Yeah
All right, Christine if you're listening, please come up. I love you come up on the panel Christine. I love you
Christine's one of my favorite people man. I'm serious like we talk about empathy
have this isn't me being conceited but I do have the ability to almost feel what
other people are feeling because I've worked on that and I know you know what
I'm talking about meditation right deep thought yeah and like when I channel
Mike's mother I can't feel what she feels exactly
But I'm like halfway there because of meditation because of play-doh and fuck everyone else's thinks this is bullshit
all right because
Mind over matter man
Be so grateful that you're alive that you live in America if you do that you're safe right now from terror
You got if you got jobs
house
and what's the word for food?
Substance, is that correct?
Substance, you're a smart guy, I know you know.
But just remember, you can have all that stuff
and we can hit by a bus,
there could be some kind of like,
thinking you're taking time bomb in our bodies,
it's like we're very fragile here and like,
so just like-
And we don't live long, right, Psyche?
We don't live long, lives.
A little small, little blip on the radar.
That's right.
If we're lucky, we'll make it to 80 years old,
but if that time we'll be all wrinkled.
We wrinkled and like hard to move and stuff like that.
That's right.
We're now able-bodied, and most of us
are able-bodied and have our senses.
There's people that have no arms and legs,
but can write no operative stuff.
One of my best friends lost an extremity at Infilusha
in Iraq, OK?
Yeah, I went to Walter Reed Hospital.
That's on Long Island.
That's the big.
Vet that's not on Long Island. I'm sorry. What am I saying? That's in Virginia
It's one of the biggest veteran hospitals, you know
Um, and it is the biggest thing in our country and I sat next to him and it changed my life
You know, he was all on
Dilordid and his
I'm not gonna get into a bed and well stapled up because he was on his fit surgery and I changed my life
I was like 25 and like you just said it's so good about people who don't have arms and legs
You know good for you. I really like you psych. I like your um, I try to protect you brother. I try to
Thank you. I really do like I
You know like I'm hard on people and I know it's kind of rude of me to say like yo
I'll give you $10 if you go and pay for fish tacos yourself
You know because like people like are you trying to point out that he does drugs and I'm like yo, man
We don't know each other. Okay. I'm trying to help him out
And this is the way I do it if he spends $10 on fish tacos or with his own money
Then I will give him $10 but not anymore psyche because you didn't you've done great and I want
Sweet Pea to know if you donate $25 right now to Psyche, I will drive to the Amityville horror house
Sweet Pea wrote in the chat
Go to the Amityviller house or beat it. So I will drive there. I'm 15 miles away
If you donate about $10 Psyche, you think she'll do that or he'll do that
Yeah, you're gonna do it. So yep, I will sweepy donate the money or beat it
This is how you turn the tables on people. They try to act tough
Sweet pea is still there. You're not talking anymore
You're gonna bark all night sweet pea like it's sorry
Yeah, bullshit, uh Canada get up here. See that sweet pea. You're here
He's in the back whenever
Fuck you, sweet pea. Fuck you
Little bitch. Sorry, sir
Yeah, go to the Amityville our house or beat it don't eat $10 to psyche or beat it loser
As we pee have it been up on the channel or is it like a fucking sock account or somebody that like it's on is it?
Do you know?
Well, I think I talked to her before the phone, and we know we've oh really?
Yes, yes, yes, so get up here sweepy. Let's hear you bullshit
Scared now
I love British. I know a lot about UK. You scared sweepy. I'm sorry. I don't got my glasses on psyche
Can you read the chat for me? What's she what's she saying?
Said I hurt little man's feelings and then you're trying to turn the tables on me
But you can't do it and I'm fucking mine more bro. This is chess mental chess and you can't do it
You're sad a sad existence don't need $10 or beat it
Probably a very lonely lonely Brit
Oh, oh, did you start it though and try to boss psyche and I around and control the conversation and tell me to go to the
Where's my defense like you defend everyone else I'm defending you. I'm like, you know
This is all content, roll potion.
Yup, Psyche will defend you,
but I will destroy Psyche and then destroy you.
She's British, man.
You know what British people are like, right?
I have a brother in law.
Ugly teeth.
I have a brother in law with British, yeah.
Big hands and ugly teeth.
Well, I think there's some there's some birds with good kids. Yeah, I'm just I'm just
Yeah, this is all content. Oh bullshit. I bet you she's from York. Hey, are you from York or Manchester?
Are you from South England like London?
What she said
She said, oh, yeah, where are you from in England this week? She yeah, if you're the south in London or you north York
I like Yorkshire
That's just enough from Yorkshire
Had there's no home so homeless people down here cuz it's too nice of a neighborhood. We're gonna go into the bad neighborhood now
All right, it's not being asked what's who a what? Oh, okay. He's gonna be an asshole to a woman. I mean, it's like who started it
I mean who tell him who started it?
Nothing else is
Usually goes like tab or everyone kind of like it's as close to each other right that's right except for Jamie girl
If anybody fucks with Jamie girl, they got a deal with me
Anybody I know it's just like I hear so much shit about myself that it's like I know I know people people are so obsessed with psyche
Holy channels with you and like people talking about like video. I watched the video of you the other day
Somebody sent me a thing and I was like guy like I don't care about this
Somebody was like, but did you see what he did? And I said, yeah, I don't care. He doesn't care
Don't talk about it. And what I'm doing right now is wrong. I shouldn't even bring it up
So yeah, but as far as I know as far as I know about that I was asleep, you know, and so it's like you're the best
Yeah, keep it out of your mind
Yeah, no, I don't I don't worry about it. I'm actually wrong for bringing it up. I want to tell everybody that's
That's what we shouldn't do on the internet like if you're sitting here
We're having a conversation about like homeless people and helping them and then what I did just now is wrong
I started talking about psyche in a channel and even though I'm saying nice things
I'm still bringing it up and now people want to know about it. So I apologize like yeah
I mean, I mean we've already we discussed it on the show
It was brought up on some channel. It's like, I don't know. I didn't I never watched it. I don't care to see it
It's like yeah, good good, but it's like but it's like guys
It's not it's always people someone like you know, I even though maybe was on my show or whatever
Someone's going around making clips of you from your show of that kind of stuff
It's like
You're so good like psychological you you understand like I call it an out-of-the-box thinker, you know you you're very smart that way man
You know you with you have a job somewhere. You're a manager. You're not a you're not like a bottom person
You're a middle-level top manager, you know, you can close your eyes and see the business from a whole like let's take a FedEx
Factory right with boxes coming in and out you're a guy that can see how the whole thing works and understand the different right?
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Yeah, I've been I've been an office manager. So I've been like an assistant
Basically, this is the CEO which was like a fortune 500 company out of the assistance of the CEO for like two years
Yeah, so I have some good experience like working with executives and then
They have done a no event planning. Yeah
I mean we did this he is in this thing called young presidents of America and it was kind of like this
organization of these presence of companies and they we arranged like this
uh like a 3a thing in albuquerque where we went and saw like the balloon um the balloons like
they have these uh you know like a hot air balloons and then we went to like um so historical
stuff some historical houses there and yeah and I was I was there like you know doing so much work
and uh making sure everything went smoothly and so yeah I've uh I've done some big projects and
stuff and I was in play there like twice in that couple of years and what happened?
What happened with what John? I don't know what's happened like we're talking about like, uh, you know Michael passed away and oh
Please rest in peace prayers to the family
Yeah, it's very sad. Damn it man. I feel so bad
I do too as I don't remember the last time I talked to him was like when I gong him off the show if he came
Yeah, me too. Let me know that yeah, I was mean I was mean the last time I'll own up to it
You know, he was being a dick
He was he was being rude to beta and he was making it about himself and I feel bad, you know
I was like Michael. I was like a dad. I'm like Michael you started out good and now you're fucking up
And he's like, you know, I was really mean to him and yeah
And he was combative to you, you know, it's like he was he always liked he kind of liked the fight
I think he likes that you always like, you know put himself where he knew he would get kind of like, you know roasted
He just needed a new and uh, so you know, he you know, I think he was a good sport about it, too
He hadn't understood. He was he was he was constantly on the defense and so he would get very annoyed. Yeah
For well said constantly on the defense. I like that. I'm gonna use that quote. I'm gonna regurgitate that shit
Constantly defense very well for anybody would even say anything. He'd be like, oh, okay
So he was just assumed this one's gonna go after her but sometimes they did but sometimes they really didn't know
Yeah, you're guessing his balls, you know, right? Um, is there you occasionally?
You're right. Is there people like trying to get up on the show right now or no?
No, I think Irby was a few minutes ago, but he's gone back down Canada drives that he wants to come along when he
There's more people on the panel
Canada sit in the back the Canada sit in the back. He was back for a few minutes, but
because
You don't want to do it one-on-one he came down when I said it was just one-on-one right now
Yeah, no, but I'm here
I texted him I texted him on his phone and said yo I'm in the back and want to hang out and he said cool
So I don't I don't wonder why you left. Well, I'm just wondering why you left
I was I was doing one of his times so I wouldn't bring him up
I'm such an idiot. I'm so stupid. Oh, did anybody sponsor the show tonight? Did anybody sponsor the show? No
Sweet pea man. This is your time. I sponsored his show. Um
Ghost he's probably that drunk ghost I sponsored it out and goes. Oh, he's not drunk
He's drunk man. I love ghosts though. He's a good person. Yeah. Yeah
He gave you so much money man
And you know what it's like and that was like such a blessing like I'm gonna like spend it on something
That's gonna be like help the show forever. Yeah, a computer and stuff like that. I think I might get a new computer
And then I'll be able to run the show from that
That'll be a lot better too because I'll be able to because a lot of stuff
I can do from the computer that I can't do from my tablets and stuff like that
You know, I do that. That's my second job, right? Like, you know that or no the computer programming or what?
I sell like I got I'm you know, I'm not trying to act like like I help money out
I'm gonna go see him in a couple days
You know we're giving him that this you know the dual monitors with the fucking you know set up
So he cannot have to work on his iPhone if you ever need any like
You know, I help you out too, you know
Hey summer, how are you? Yeah
The loop
of the
Well, it's been a very emotionally draining week. So yeah, I love that
Here you go. Hey
Got it. I got a catch up on hot mess. I got a catch up on it
Okay, guys, like it's a no, it's a big week for her because they didn't you put a one behind bars
That was a bad bad bad copper a dirty copper or something about
I guess they got sentences since it's the 33 months, but he and he can never be a cop again anywhere in the United States
And he'll have three years of probation
But there's a chance that you know Chuck Mike part of him
But he has a he had to he's got two weeks
I think it's two weeks they gave him to get his affairs and orders and shit
So but I mean the census scene that is the sentence. So yeah, we did
You know, he will have to go into a federal courthouse
Quirk
I hope everybody understands like you're witnessing history
So like you have to think like psyche said summer is a part of this big cog and she's making moves
All right, her name will go down in history. I don't care if anybody laughs at me
This is big news fucking way to go summer. I'm so proud of you, man
Yeah
She's fucking amazing
Honestly, it was just I mean
Prosecute it was just it was really it was traumatizing this court
This is the scene was very traumatizing like it was literally war in the courtroom
Like you've seen the process because the prosecutors supposed to be on our team
But the prosecutors over here suck at a crop the dick and so like we're all like
Basically, I mean really it was it was it was wild. It was wild, but I mean we did it
So you know and people are like you should have got more and you know all that
If you've never put a cop in federal prison you have to understand how hard it is to do that
So to get anything is amazing. They were always trying to give him time served in a day
Which was a day with which he never even served a day. He only got
Fingerprint and photoshop, but yeah
Can't wait to tell my mom so I can't wait to tell my mom I forgot to ask you I was waiting
Even all over the news. I know summer. It's just you know me. I'm working and stuff and I try to I'm always there
But like the past two weeks have been really busy for me, too
And you know my mom follows hot mess summer. She always asked me we watch some of the protests together
We have lunch and watch you and I can't wait to tell her I can't wait. She's gonna be she's gonna be so happy
You know her now. She says you know this woman. I said, yeah, that's my friend. That's my
So good guys it's called Bob privilege also host privilege. I can bring up who I want to bring
Like three or four panels, so
I love you taught me so much about just human trafficking open my eyes
I'm a history guy. I know a lot about history summer always says that school you teach me a lot
But there's so much that we don't know okay, and she taught me so much about human trafficking
And it's right underneath our you know fee right summer. It's happening all around us all the time
You know, it's also called isn't it also known as social engineering in a way where it's like this manipulation of social systems or
Um to this is engineering. So it's like a train, right? It's like uh, so the same as traffic is very similar question for summer
What do you think some what do you think summer? Do you think it's similar to social engineering or do you think they're completely different?
Um, I don't know. What does that mean like social social engineering is social engineering is kind of like, you know
railroading people to certain to certain outcomes or things like that you know
if you got you can certain trains like the train goes to one destination right
and so it's like but so it's it does move people around but it's like through
through like different social means and it's like in order to
You know, they see ultimately for the first help society there's some some of these social engineers, but it's kind of like social justice
Some of my social justice warriors that takes it to an extreme. I don't I think I think there's good social justice warriors
There's ones that are let's look at let's look up the definition of it
You said you're you're you're saying like a social warrior. Yeah, 100% I understand that I don't know how like human trafficking
Besides maybe if they're combatting, right?
I'll take the definition of social engineering.
I'll get a good definition.
OK.
Social engineering is RNG.
It says.
Social engineering in the context of information security, social engineering is the use of psychological influence of people to perform actions or divulging confidential information.
It differs from psychological information and that it doesn't need to be controlling negative or one right transaction, but it does exploit human psychology from malicious.
I guess it is pretty different.
No, it's not.
Can I say something?
Go ahead.
You're right.
And Summer, let me ask you a question.
To make other people do things right to power. Would you would you say, you know?
Well, I mean, yeah, there's a part of that. I just have it. I didn't understand, you know
Being someone that experienced it and now does the answer work. I've never
Talked about it that way in some sense of you know, the truth and good and bad
I don't see any good in human trafficking at all. I think it's I think it's evil
but
Yeah, so I'm just learning new verbs. That's all I mean, you know, hey, I'm a professional but I'm not too professional about to learn
Not me neither and I didn't really understand what it was either and that's why I love you like we have a conversation
And you're like, I don't know what that means. Can you tell me? You know what I mean?
And we keep it real like you don't try to bullshit
I'm trying to look up the definition
Engineering is kind of like railroading people to certain careers
You can say it in good sense. You know, it's like you're saying you want your child to be a doctor
Yeah, like when you say when you say it like that 100% I can understand that in that setting and stuff like that
So I guess if I take it in the aspect of the manipulation part the grooming part and different things. Um, I
Still have a hard time because even in social engineering
There's usually some kind of well, I guess it could be bad because they would be brainwashed and manipulated
Yeah, but it's like, you know, there is like the subconscious mind and the subconscious mind is where a lot of our behavior will stem from.
And so people that understand a subconscious mind can kind of manipulate it and the manipulation of the subconscious mind is really hard to detect because the mind is below the level of consciousness.
So yeah. And so it's a lot of, a lot of manipulate. Like, you know what I mean?
Like all people always like, Oh, where's the chains? It's like, Oh, you don't really need chains.
The chains is in the brain. Like people get in your head and they fuck with your head, you know,
and they take control over that space. So yeah, I guess I could see it in that aspect.
See, I just have to process it when I play it out sometimes until I can because my brain
Well, I didn't know I didn't know what it is an idea to pop to them in my mind
I just thought I thought about engineering and then it's like I kind of think of like what I think of soul
Trafficking I think of people like kind of on trains
I don't like I on trains on like a one-way path to some someplace else
Do you think do you think a Jewish people right Jewish people in like the World War two and I'm not comparing it to but you know
I mean just like
the train the train thing like that's all
yeah that's okay so there's a train track we went straight into Auschwitz that's where it ended and that was like the last stop right
that's like the train the train the train tracks going right into it if you look at the picture of the camp in the front of it
there's a big train tracks going right that's right so that was the train that was the last stop
it was like bringing them straight to this place and then dropping them off kind of like what they're doing on uh
the A-L-C-A-T-R-A-Z, alligator A-L-C-A-T-R-A-Z, like I'm just spelling it out.
Oh, yeah, it's in Florida and it's like one of these new
Places they just dump off people without any trial or you know, just pick up people drop them in this place
Yeah, it's in America in America, right?
And it is they just opened it up
And there's people there and it's like
They can make phone calls though, but it's like still it's like there's very little legal recourse because it's kind of like they're not
putting them through the judicial system, they're just
Of course not. There's no due process somewhere, right?
Due process.
That's about it, right? I think that's what a lot of people they're like, oh people like you similar bitch
No, well, I don't have an issue with getting people out of our country that is doing bad and shit like that
I don't have an issue with that at all
I do have an issue though when you are not giving people due process
And that's the way we do things and I said it in the beginning
I said this is going to end up coming down on now Americans and that's exactly what's happening
Unfortunately, there are Americans that are getting caught up in all of this and because there's no due process
There's no way to really see who's who's what what and so we're girls people believe it or not
But yeah, there is people getting fucked over about the whole thing. Well said summer. Well said
Yeah
I feel weird and I love that we're having this conversation
But if I could be honest, I feel so weird being all like professional and regular conversation over here because it's just not what we
Well, you know what? I'm trying to do summer. You know what? I'm trying to do
I muted up and yelled a couple times like what you taught me because once I get started talking about subconscious unconscious
What I want to do is interrupt and take over the conversation because I love these conversations
I'm not trying to do that
I would hate to have the spans out on you tonight, and I probably would because I'm not emotionally stable tonight. So just heads up
And I don't want to do that
So yeah, but you know, you are you are an expert in it
And it's like in that you both experienced it and then so you can you can really come from that place of empathy because you've been there
You know you've been there you you like you see I see if you see yourself sometimes and some of these women like
100% there's times that I talk to some of these girls and women and stuff
And I'm just like I see all different ages like you know what I mean like throughout my life like just I'll be like damn man
I could only get you to see what the outcome is going to be so you don't have to you know what I mean
But that's just not the way life works. So you don't judge people you walk with them. You help them where you can and
So that's what you do
I think you do you're being but you do change lives and you do I think how you brought people out of it
You brought you got you right haven't you? Oh, yeah
They brought themselves out of it. I've just been able to stand along with them as they do it
Yeah, well, it's like sometimes it's all you need sometimes you need one like one just one person to have your back
And that's like and they don't you're out looking for that that girl, right?
There's who else was out looking for rather than like her pimp, you know, well take her back
You're talking about the woman that died or that was
I don't know if it's the same or found a woman right recently. Well, they're there. No the woman that died actually
So let me give you an update on that. That's what I was doing with today's school
So the fucking chief decides to go and tell everybody that she played a role in her own death
Right now. She was killed by her boyfriend the girl that I was looking for we found her and we found out and he got
Arrested like a week ago. Oh, I don't know how long my brain's so bad with time
But he just got arrested for it. Right. I came out of the news and they said
Tasha's white killer has been arrested. It's her boyfriend, blah blah blah. Well, then the cheek because they dropped the ball on this
I look for missing people and so they dropped the ball on file on her missing person's report and all kinds of other shit
Right in the very beginning. That's why I got called in because the family's like look
We're not getting any help. Can you help us? And then now when I start looking into everything
I noticed that her missing person report wasn't there. I'm just a bunch of shit. So long story short
LMPD had to wear egg on their face because then you know, I got involved. We did a community search. We found her
Unfortunately, she was dead. So, you know, people were upset with them and instead of them humbly going
Hey, we fucked up because that's what I would never do that and said they go on the news and the chief says, oh, well, you know
I mean, yeah
You know she played a play she played a role in her own death and we were so this morning
We were doing press conferences and i've been going off on the chief all day because i'm like, dude
You'll be not you know, we've done replace six chiefs since 2020
I was like you keep fucking around like this that promise she'll be up for then the fucking year like it's just
And you're good on your promises this girl's good on her promise and he knows follow us through
And well, it ain't just me, right?
There's tons of people that make these actions happen.
But yes, he's the sixth, he's the sixth chief right now.
So he understands that, yeah, this is what I'm talking about.
Right and why summer because accountability right and it's not even about them taking accountability of themselves
But us holding them accountable and following through and when there is action like you do six chiefs
He knows that in the back of his head. I got some of the fucking she's gonna fuck me up unless I stay in line
Right, I'm just being a little exaggerated, but it's true, right? Yeah
It's well because it's the community. It's not just me. You know what I mean like now
I'm good at being vocal and getting people in the community
You know whatever but in this situation these cops they fuck over everybody like it doesn't matter what color
It doesn't matter what town it doesn't matter what so a lot of people are affected because of it
So this is one topic that I don't just you know say hey, this is you know
Now this particular case happened to be a black woman. You know and so yes that that was brought up, but
there's white men this happens to, there's white women this happens to, there's Hispanic people,
you know what I mean? Like the cops fuck over everybody. Now I do teach, I do, I do treat each
case for that individual, you know what I mean? Like, and I make sure people understand that
as far as that goes. But other than that, I mean, it's something that I want, I mean, most of us
have had a bad, and there's of course going to be like, no, I've never had an encounter with cops.
Well, good job. But guess what? Some of us fucking do.
Yes summer and and and I don't mean you know me psyche I get really emotional
I can be dead tired and then when somebody starts talking about 1a activism
I boom it get up and go because I am so serious about this movement. It's it to me
It's just as important as the 13th amendment
and the 19th amendment and the 13th amendment was slavery and the 19th amendment was women's suffrage
And this is just as important and in a hundred years from now some of your names your name's gonna be in book summer
I'm just letting you know like it's gonna happen
One second school um a panel member died and you act like nothing happened who died
Michael did Michael
He's like sorry
You know Michael L with the girlfriend the mora it a girlfriend mora. He was like you the guy with trees
I remember he was with Tracy, you know, I come in the way. Yeah. Yes. Cool. Hold on, please
Sure
Um, there's this an obituary he died on July 18th, I believe like and then it says, you know
He but he was unexpectedly passed away. I see I've seen this obituary
And he's on the funeral home website, too
Yeah
Yeah, and I'm sorry to the person that's at the common arena. That's the first I've heard of this
I did not know that at all. That's fucking crazy, dude
No, yeah
Like about an hour ago from psyche
No, I didn't know that's the only reason I came in here talking about this stuff because I didn't I had no clue if I had
Any clue how to definitely took space and I mean he was you know, like we all went out had our little
Things you know to me, but damn dude. I don't see nobody fucking die. That's crazy. My heart goes out to his family
That's my girl. I think that's the same. What do we say before psyche? Is it not that like see right?
What do we say? We take a second try to imagine his mother his father
You know, I'd be grateful that we're not you know, thanks. We'll set some
Dude, I didn't know anything fucking happened to body. So jump off a fucking bridge. I don't give a fuck
I didn't know anything happened. Obviously now I see it. So I'm bringing it up
What do you what are you talking to somebody in the chat?
Yeah
I
Was talking to you on then I looked down and I was like what and I was being somebody shoot me please and so I was like damn
I was like that
And so you somebody shoot me you're doing this to just get an emotion out of us
And it ain't gonna fucking work and somebody shoot me like I'm not even gonna talk about you for the rest of the fucking night
Just like they did it before right psyche. They were just trying to provoke every little thing. We were talking about cars
Anyway Michael or anything like that
I don't I almost agree. I almost like kind of remembering him saying like something like he didn't have the best
Like there might have been something wrong. I'm just but I can't remember exactly. It just seems like he was alluding to like some kind of
He helps
Very sudden and you know because he always seems like he was
Healthy and you know, he was he's like to fight and stuff and you know, I feel bad
He was you know the last few times I talked to him. He was like, you know pretty much gone off the show and
You know and now I can't talk to him again, and it's like that. No, so we just have to remember
you know life is fragile and
You know we get we don't know how how long any of us are gonna be here, but you know as long as we
Have some kind of leaf and an afterlife or something. You know, at least it's not in pain or suffering anymore
He wasn't any I really hope he wasn't
Life is paint life can be painful, you know, and he was definitely
a little bit troubled and things, but I do wish him the best
and my thoughts to his family and to him.
I hope he's up there or around us, you know?
And I liked him.
I met him actually, I met him on Benny's channel
probably like last year, like, you know,
I was on a panel with him and I kind of like hit on him,
I think, and he was like one of the first people
that was like kind of like didn't care.
And I was like, so I kind of like had a crush
on him a little bit, but you know,
it's kind of controversial character.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, he can be obviously me we all had our
Moments and that's just what happens and especially in this community
But I think that you know most of us can put a sad dumb shit
And I mean takes some time and just be like damn dude that sucks
And I've you know, so like I said some good energy and shit to his family
Yeah
Indy I mean he was up here roasted and having fun and trolling and we did the same thing
I don't feel guilty for anything that was said or done or not like that. Well, I don't
Never do that. I don't live in
He liked each other like, you know, I mean, I didn't know he was
I
Know like exactly. Oh, I'm gonna get it now. He's like I he always knew like he's gonna be like, you know people are gonna be
Summer
Yelling and
Just be like summer. I love you
We got it
Yeah, I mean, you know, like I said, it's just that you can't remember it all, right?
We all say silly shit, you know, it is what it is, but he was having fun.
We had fun in some times, and sometimes we got on each other's nerves, but that's just
a part of what we do.
But that, you know, they don't, yeah, I don't feel guilty for none of that.
Think that was nice summer. Hey, that was a good memory of him
But you just said like everybody you know like when you go to awake and you laugh about like a memory about someone
We kind of didn't do that before and you just did it right psyche like you brought up that lovely summer
You and I really laughed hard like a real laugh and I think that's what it's about remembrance though. That's good. Yeah
Yeah, the good times there was good. There was good time. There's a lot of good times too and like
Yeah, it's about we don't have fun busting his balls and you know, and we'd have fun
Like yelling at us too. Like if you come back and always like fight for you know fight for himself or whatever
Yeah, I really love and respect and peace to the whole family. I'll say it tonight
You know here and there so if anybody new comes on the panel because
You know, no kid should die before their parent, you know
He was there in his early 30s. I think he was
34 yeah, yeah, yeah, so very young. Yeah, they didn't have a really beautiful
The picture I saw was a beautiful obituary picture. He has like clouds all around him and
He was like an angel. I mean, I think he kind of did like angels, you know, he's named Michael like after probably
Archangel Michael and stuff so I said Michael the Archangel, you know, yeah
I think he does look very angelic in the photo.
It's a very nice picture.
I don't know if I can share it right now, but yeah.
It was, it's sad, it's sad and I wish I could.
There was a couple more time and what is Hogan I'm said Hogan gun. What is um, yes
Listen the other night me and Goddy and all of us were sitting around and it was like what Ozzie pastor, whatever, right?
It was like just the other night and I know where Goddy was like, you know, how coke is gonna be next and I was like
What are you talking about? He's like, should he go to that next?
And I was like, really? I was like, I ain't, I ain't sick. He was like, yeah, he's been a little sick. And then boom, he died today.
I was like, first person I thought of when I heard the news, I was like, hey, he's got him. You fucking call that shit.
Did he really?
Yeah, I swear to God, he didn't.
He's sick. I mean, I did hear he was sick. I didn't hear he was sick, I think. Like, wow, kind of, maybe very sick.
But for him to call it, and then like the next day he fucking whooped, it was kind of like, damn.
Yeah, yeah.
Intuition, right?
It sounds like smart intuition.
Maybe he did it, you know, it's like,
but that's what the police would say.
Maybe he did it.
It's like, you know, psychics that have found bodies
and they have his psychics that have full crimes and stuff,
but sometimes the suspicion goes to them,
because how would they know the exact place to go, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
God, maybe he did it.
Maybe, yeah, maybe it was also.
But Summer said it.
Ozzy, that's what I was just, sorry, go ahead and say it.
I was just gonna say summer when somebody brought up Hulk
I was just about to say eyes out of my mouth and you said it first, right?
Like that's yeah, so many people wait one after another happens in threes happens in threes like my mouth
Yeah, Jamal Warner
Or yeah, that's the same I think I thought it was yet is I thought it was um
I thought it was Carl Winslow who passed away.
Somebody said the guy from Family Matters,
and I figured it was the father,
Carl Winslow, Reginald Valjansa, but it was the kid.
Yeah, yeah, I was a kid from the coffee show you feel oh, oh, I'm so stupid. I thought it was fucking
I'm dumb. I thought it was Carl Winslow's kid because somebody said family matters before
Eddie from family matters. Yeah, what's his name? What's his name? Eddie ever got
Fuck deal is
Fuck like I looked the shit up
the guy from the Cosby show his name was his name was
Darius McCrary
Yeah, Malcolm Jamal Warner he played the oldest son. Yeah
Do you know the best movie that he was in the best movie that Malcolm Jamal Warner was in?
Hmm
Tuskegee airmen Tuskegee airmen. Oh, okay
I know you know that right yeah, that's about the syphilis
No, it's just you. Okay, so that's what he's there. They were caught. There's all black squadron, right?
I was yeah, I knew you'd know it's psyche summer. Do you are you familiar with the Tuskegee airman?
Yeah
He was in the movie, but the taxi experiment is something else too. And that's when they they did these big medical tests
They had people come in for these medical testing and they're gonna help them for something
But they just they see and injected them with syphilis and they're doing syphilis testing on black on black men
And so it's a very controversial
I've heard of that and
Heard about the syphilis thing and I think I'm wrong
I was thinking that had to do with also the pilots today
Or was it just the area because I know Tuskegee is a region. I think it was the area
It was the area
I think they had the gotcha like lower like the lower you know people don't need to be free medical care or something
They came offering them. It's not like medical care, but it was just like they actually made them worse or yeah
Because they did do experiments on the pilots and do you know what they said at a Congress hearing?
They literally said and you can read it like the black African American has a problem
At heights, you know, they can't keep the zero G and you know, they can't be pilots because of that
Like that's what they fucking argued over and some of the experiments they did. Isn't that crazy like?
Message
Okay, I'll be there one second Katrina Katrina says, okay, I'm sorry you got them the cat move behind
Okay, so Katrina says
See I don't see it. Hey, Sam man Katrina was the last
Well, come on Sam
She said if I share Michaels go find me then his mom made
Oh, she made something in this ball made. Okay. Like how do you know how you would?
Okay, go ahead and share that link please. Are you a mod? So you can get free to yes, you're a mod.
Thank you so much.
And yeah, it says about the Tuskegee experiment and says the Tuskegee city of untreated syphilis in the Negro male was a study conducted between
1932 and 1972 by the US Public Health Service and the Center for Disease Control and Prevention
Yeah, I'm a group of nearly 400 African American men with syphilis as well as the control group without the purpose of the study was to observe
The effects of the disease when untreated to the point of death and autopsy
Although there have been effective treatments to reduce the severity of the disease since the 1920s
The use of penicillin for the treatment of syphilis was widespread as of 1945.
The men were not informed of the nature of the study, proper treatment was withheld,
and more than 100 died as a result. So that's all.
It's like you don't need to be an asshole. Just where'd you get that from? And of course,
I know it's true. That is from the Wikipedia. Yeah, but what is the footnote?
I didn't show it, I didn't show it, I didn't show it, I just mentioned that I've seen something.
I shouldn't even say that, I'll look it up.
I'd like to know where it's from and that's like what I wanted to do when I was younger.
So like if that's from a published paper from a historian that uncovered that,
you know, that the US tried to like hide.
I guess what I wanted to do with my life when I was younger,
but it's a very hard road, you know, getting grants and stuff like that.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
Yeah, um, yeah, I was what I said to you psyche. I think you shouldn't show but I mean people
just find out I just wanted you to know just as confirmation but the go fund me I mean for people
that want to you know, whatever. Yeah, I mean, uh-huh. Yeah, I'm not going to show it. Like,
It was it was it's beautiful photo though. I just thought it was he's the kind of like a little bit of an angel
He's a little bit of a little bit of a devil here, but he was you know, he's the little bit of angels here
Okay, so we have a man is here. Hold on a second
Hey, hi
Real quick, I think we're conflating
Two situations the discussion had nothing to do with it to ski right experiment. Yeah, that's what we said
Yeah, we know that's what we just said and so I just want to make sure
Because the experiments were not done on those gentlemen. It's got me
Some people in the chat
Also thought that it was being conflated, so I decided to come up here and
Clarify that
Um, because of what happened in multiple institutions and things of this sort, like the Tuskegee experiments,
I had to go through something called institutional review board.
and grad school when I wrote extensive papers and published them and had to go
through the training because of that because it involved even though my stuff
didn't involve human subjects just know that people at universities have to go
through extensive training because of this bullshit because it was done to
these people without their knowledge.
So I just wanted to put that out there.
Yeah, so that's why there's still
a lot of lawsuits today about it, right?
There's like a family.
Absolutely, and that's just one of many things
that were done to people without their knowledge.
It's just horrible.
So anyway, I just wanted to put that out there real quick.
And I'm just going to put that out there.
And I do believe that the last member of the Tuskegee Airmen, somebody checked me on that, I believe he passed away.
Almost passed away. Yes, a lot of people used to fly airplanes, it's a real thing.
Yes, I don't think there's anything there.
I don't remember the email head.
Quick that up.
Oh, Benjamin OD.
I still don't got airplanes now.
What are people talking about?
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
I mean, there's like, but I guess it was back then it was like,
there was like a cultural thing that said they're afraid of flights.
Heights or something.
Correct.
And also that they couldn't handle zero G, you know, and like the.
when if a plane of the engine died and it would go into a tailspin like they couldn't stay conscious and parachute out and that's what they tried to put out at Congress you know congressional hearings
that's where the whole joke where Morgan Freeman flips the plane upside down
right
where's that from not Tuskegee is that red tails
it's flight
Denzel Washington
oh yeah that's
Sorry
Yeah, that is
Yeah, I take all
From Canada we know
Amanda, what's Canada? It's like, you know an apartment under a really big party. You know what I mean Amanda
what was that no we're the attic above a really good party yeah that's what like you know it's like
it's like the apartment above the garage under a really cool party that's canada you know i mean
amanda oh yeah you have that's the they have a black panther blowing fire as is the spitfire as
Together the university is a very cherished thing by the way in case anybody
Like Howard. It's like Howard. Absolutely. Yeah honor. Yeah, my friend
going to veterinary school there and
it was he chose that over all the other offerings he got because of
You know the Tuskegee Airmen and what it means and all the things
a man that are you familiar with toughs university
yes I am my my my youngest cousin just graduated from toughs
I I I and she got a um what's it called when not not the internship but after it when you
succeed and then you go and work there I know you know what it's called so she's
apprenticeship
No, he's right the apprenticeship internship is first and then if they want you then apprenticeship you're right
I apologize, so she's in Wyoming. That's where she's going and she's working on horses and fucking cows and like
So excited like that's cool. Yeah, Magnum cum laude
Tufts University really proud of her
Awesome. Yeah, it really is. Yeah, I actually visited that college when I went to on a college show
Oh, oh, hey, very nice. Mm-hmm. Just sit on a college tour there. Yeah, I
Think about going there
I don't want to show up on that fucking what on that page what
I want to take your camera off right logic I know I know but I
Yeah, that was that was great. Put your camera off. I just looked up and I know I just looked up and I see that thing on his face. I'm like, what the hell?
Desperate for attention
Like he just fucking puts it right out there. He puts it right out there. It just says it
You're good, Canada. It's okay. It's tired tonight. Yeah
Okay, oh my gosh, I've lost my back on the table
Sorry, okay. Yeah, um
Gosh, what does I mean? So yeah, I got a yeah
Lot of stuff going on. Yeah, I'm just opening the panel tonight for free because you know, we're Michael pass away
It's in his memory
Yeah
Did you see ghosts last night the donations thank you shit psyche last night for you
Did you see ghosts on her?
No, but I had
He's so bipolar about it. He's like, okay, we'll kick it off for five minutes. And then I say, okay,
then five minutes later, bring her back. Then he's good for a minute. And then he's like,
okay, kick her off again. I'm like, no, no. He thought I was gonna stop talking shit to him.
And I'm like, no, dude, I'm gonna get a pay to get me off. Fuck it. So he kept paying. Then he's
like, okay, bring her back. And then I'd talk shit. I'm like, well, that was that one. You have to pay
But he didn't have fun.
He told me he did have fun, he said.
And so I was like, okay, good.
He said he had a blast or something like that before.
So he, yeah, so it was good.
Like, you know, that's what it's all about.
And last time I was kind of letting him like,
run the panel himself a little bit.
People kind of started getting really mad
because, you know, he can't make up his mind first of all
about who he wants stuff and who he doesn't.
And so he kept just kicking people up,
bringing it back up and stuff.
And people were like, what's going on?
And I was listening to him because
If you donate over a hundred dollars, I'll give you a little bit of like a leeway on the panel just for the other panel
You know because so, you know, just let them play a little bit but people were like, oh, you're bad
You're not controlling your show. Hey, you know, I think I thought it was fun. Okay. We have cheese with us
This is random guy coming up
Narky oh, it's not that's why you're so snarky you snark show hey psyche. Give me like three seconds
I made you a rock song since you hate
I don't want to hear this right now. I don't like this. I mean, it's gonna be bad song. It's rock and roll come on
It's like it's like 20 seconds
Kind of talks about it talks about some dumb shit again. No, here you go. Here you go. Okay
We made a song it's right random those songs. I forgot okay. Well, I think my AI
Better than that song anyway, I'm gonna write a song about random guy and put it through the AI
It'll be better song. Okay. I promise you. No, it's okay running guy. Well, I understand
It's keep keep it keep at it y'all that doesn't sound like it will be a great number one hit, but
No, enjoy yourself pretty good. I like what happened? We have a rubber's voice. Oh you do
Well, you're the only one interesting camber to his voice. Okay. Okay, great. Anyway, what happened with chat? What is happening with
Shit, and then he's like so like, oh, let me up. Let me up. I deserve. I want to be here
I'll be part of the group. I'll be part of the group, but then he's rude to me
And so it's like when am I rude to you?
When am I rude to you? Okay, please. Yeah, you're always rude to me
You've been rude to me since I got you off that first time
And then I even brought you back after you got kicked off that night that they gonged remember and then I brought you back for like two seconds
And I it sounds like you're rude to me. I haven't been rude. Oh it does. Yeah, I'll be rude here
I'll be rude. I can be rude too
Okay, we have school Athens back
Yo, I just might something wrong with my mute and you'd made me laugh and summer did to you're like oh, yeah, okay?
Well, you're the only one you're like
I don't think it's gonna be a hit and then he's like I like his voice. You're like, yeah
Well, you're the only one that someone laughs so hard. I was I was trying to unmute and talk, but it wasn't
And I know he gets on some people's nerves and I just don't really understand what happened at the same time
There's people to get on my nerves that I don't you know, so I you know, I just think it's funny
on your nerves, but I love you and you love me, right? You deal with my shit, you know,
I'm here for good and I love you so much. Like Canada, you're my boy, but yeah, you're crazy.
Like someone said. Yeah, I thought you would never get a pass like you did the last day or a couple
months ago. You'll never ever get a pass like that ever again because that's why we're friends, right, hon?
Like, that's what it's not.
I'ma let you, I'ma let you, I'ma let you to fuck out next time.
I'm letting you know now.
Look, the point is, the point is, is we learn from mistakes, that's what adults do.
And friends give each other passes even when it's bad, and then you learn from that shit.
You know?
That's all I'm saying.
I hope so.
What did I tell you before girl like I was like, yo, I'm muting up right now and screaming and what did you say to me?
I appreciate that, you know, that's learning from shit, you know
I don't give a fuck what anybody thinks like oh, you're a simp. You're fucking feminine fuck that
It's about being an adult and taking accountability for your own actions and learning from them
Yep, because nobody's perfect. Yeah, it's adults
We are infallible and we are human beings and part of it is about making mistakes learning from mistakes
And improving ourselves sometimes it's low improvement. Sometimes it's not but as long as we are in the direction of improvement
You should be encouraged in that and like not like
Now some people don't want people to rise up at all, right?
And the crabs in a bucket kind of thing where it's like, okay
Well, we're not gonna let you out of here. We're all stuck in this bucket
And so they won't let a crab fall out of the bucket, right? So just keep pinching them down until
Player crap
Yeah, and so just
Okay, okay, so
Okay, so let's see. Hey Justin. Hey random guy, you know, I did I didn't let you play like five seconds of it random guy
You're Jay coming on one second. Just make sure
Hello, hello, hi gay
Hi, how are you? Oh
Hey, how are you?
Oh, that's instructor now. He's J. Are you there?
Immune himself. Okay. Well, just me and you guys. Okay. Here we go. I'm sorry
microphoneer
Hi, hi. No, it's like
Summer or you say well, I think some part of it up summer. You know who's George Stansels?
George I think he's watching he's rinsing out her hair. So she'll be back in a minute. Well, George Sanchez
There's a sound it sounds like Sanchez George Sanchez. Well, who is he like some kind of sports?
A politician that he was lying a lot. He got caught
I didn't know he served a 70-year sentence starting tomorrow. Oh, wow
Where's he from New York? Yes, Long Island
the
Yeah, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. So I'm falling y'all
Oh, sorry psych. What's the question again? You said summer. Oh, yeah
She just put away some crooked cop or something, right? Oh, yeah
Three I believe he's gonna serve three years
three years
Yeah, yeah, yeah two days ago, I think
Okay
How was the Hawaiian burger?
The Hawaiian hamburger it was very good. It was like, you know spam has some spam in it and stuff and spam was really really tasty
It was also like a really inexpensive like a meal with a you know, it was like a 60 dollar meal
I got for 15 bucks and so
Pretty good deal on DoorDash for a swim restaurant
I got a s'mores milkshake. It was just so good. Yeah, they call it french fries
It didn't like I got I bought like I'm on the side. I bought a
This thing called vampire dip. It's like a garlic. It was a garlic dip. I just kind of ate it as the dip which is kind of weird
I just the whole thing. But yeah, it was quite good. I love garlic and
Hawaiian I never heard of Hawaiian burger
Because you know they had a date spam in Hawaii, right?
You know they like spam because I think I think it's because of like dance of Japanese population though because the Japanese love spam
I just like
No, and they they cook in a different way they kind of like this like make it so that crispy on the outside
So yeah, that was my dinner it has had a really good burger tonight and still some churros they have another coffee to drink
So I'm all good to from all good for the night
Tomorrow's Friday. Yes guys. You're tomorrow. It's Friday
Look at this. This is funny. This is from Tima
Yeah, so I was on I was on yesterday. I was on the website
Tick-tock and I was going through I ran into a bunch of people that I see from YouTube that have YouTube shows
Oh, he says you fell off. Okay. Hold on. This is cool. That's
Okay
You know, it's fucking up when I'm trying to pay attention to the road. That's the most important thing.
Son of Anarchy?
That's a son of Anarchy?
It's a lot of intellectual debate.
How do you pronounce it?
A monk here, monk here.
How do you?
No, it's not at all.
That's not why I'm here.
Let me fix the microphone.
One second.
Let me try to fix the microphone.
The monk here.
Whose microphone is that?
Oh, it was yours.
OK, I fixed it.
I fixed it.
OK, perfect.
What's that called, Tiki?
I know you know.
Monk here.
How do you pronounce that?
M-o-n-k-i-e-r. What's what's oh, yeah, I don't know a moniker a monic moniker moniker
Moniker yeah, I say it wrong monkey or a moniker
Like school of Athens is my moniker Jonathan. Yeah, nice to meet you like yours is J1, right?
Yeah, J1
Oh school this is the school. Oh, I don't know. All right. Now I know
Like 18 months ago, we speak like almost once a week, you know all the time, like we've known
Advertise different
The avatar, you should have the, who do you have those?
I call it a Greek, not Greek, Greek philosophy.
Yeah, great, it's great, it's awesome.
My avatar is different than what I see,
like what I see on my screen is the school of Athens painting
by Raphael in 1511, that's not there.
I see here, I see a picture of you,
I see a picture of you and your daughter, I think.
Oh my God, no, that's my nieceie, that's my nieceie.
Uh-huh, okay.
But that's funny that it didn't change. I put that up. This is my other phone. Do you like that? That's my little niece. I named her
Definitely that was I didn't know that was you
That's me with my niece. I don't have any children. Uh, never will
Me never will have
28 years old that I didn't want to have children
So my niece
Let me try to change it, Psyche.
Help me out really quick.
I want to just take the panel over for a second.
OK, I have to take you out for a second,
and then when I see it changed, I'll breathe it out.
No, not a lot, ready?
Here we go, now.
You can do it from there?
Is it changed?
No, no.
I think you have to do it from off backstage.
Try a little real quick.
I'll just take you out for a second.
All right, no doubt.
Try it now.
I think you might want to change that okay, so yeah
I think you have to because sometimes it will stay on like the old setting for like the last show
Like you're on a different phone you went on a different show we'll go to that that's setting a little bit the name
So
Yeah, oh wow this is free look at this thing. This is pretty cool. This is $700
Wow
It's pretty good from team it right that's from team and it's it's a oversized round shade lounge fluffy bean back so far
$600 come on panel Amanda
Come up Amanda
Amanda Amanda Amanda $700 you said
So yeah, I think $150 or something like that
There's like a I guess it's probably a good deal compared to like probably would be a lot more in the
Some of this stuff looks like kind of junky here, but some of this stuff is pretty good
Everything I've been happy with all the shirts. I've got they're like $5 apiece and everything's like $3 shipping or free shipping if you're like
My over $20 of stuff and so
Very cool
Just
That kind of look really hard. I would like to get a neon sign. This is tarot cards. It does for my 20-something bucks
And they have a lot of decks for like five dollars like a lot of terror decks that we usually go for twenty to thirty dollars
Or like five dollars and so definitely check that out if you'd like to save some money on decks
Psych I want to see you and and a page to a
One-day turret cart reading. Mm-hmm. Yeah, we've done that before we do both for both full of cards. Yeah
Okay, we've done it a few times, but yeah, I would love to do more of that and
Sometimes I just let her do her thing, but she's also a page has started a channel to you and it's
She's doing really well on that and so make everyone make sure you subscribe to page this channel
She you know, she's looks like she's doing really well
There's a lot of people in there and is doing some great work. And so I support our friends, right?
Poor page page and wildflowers spiritual arts
I want to see a psychic and page to care tarot readings from live from the street the sidewalk open the street
I walk well, so we have to get and you have to be both in our areas or to get together some time and like maybe we would
need each other some day, but I don't know. It's like kind of we're quite far. Oh
Yeah, yeah, she just for you
Now these are really cute cars look at these because these are all these are 15 bucks for their expense
But they're really I love I love the style of art. You see the style of art. They kind of like a disney-ish
style
Mm-hmm
Dark Disney, you know, they got this really cool. There's some video games like Cuphead that has the kind of similar art. It's really
really cool
Yep, okay
So, how have you been a J? What what's been going on for you lately anything
Nothing just a quiet those quiet hot day. I hate this weather
Well, I'm a guy or is it just a
Sticky yeah
But you're from California, right? It's not it's not like that, right? I know it's hot over there. It's sticky
It's been really good weather this year. It's like hardly ever been like too hot or too cold
It's usually just nice nice
Nice big place 70 80 degrees and just nothing too hot
But there's places that it gets over 100 degrees in Cali like the desert play parts
Oh nice over here, but by the ocean we have a nice ocean breeze always though
Oh, yes. Yes. Yeah, I like that cut. All right.
Oh, it's like, I was actually like, uh, one time I saw a page where she was doing the reading,
right? But she also had the book. What does the cards come with the book?
Yeah, they often do, especially like if you get like a,
like my team, my, that's the guy from T-Mode didn't come
with a book, but they have it on online,
like the document with the, but yeah,
some of them do come with books and like a lot of,
like a lot of them do,
and sometimes the books better than other times
because depending on how different the cards are,
how unique they are to the author,
the author might have some certain symbology
they want to convey in the card,
but it's different maybe than traditionally.
So I'm going to bring back schooled Athens.
Did it work do you get it
Let me see
The video cameras on the video it's on yes, it is on yeah, I just got stopped here
I'm not pulled over anything. It's just something bad happened here. He was car in front of me
They're not letting us move. They told me don't move. Yeah, they're good
My car is moving
It's got a little bit of a traffic jam because it's a little, it's sometimes it actually has people that's like steric and that's why it goes as well.
Yeah, somebody got, it's just an accident.
The fireman's there, he's talking to the cop, I'm gonna try to go street past them north now.
One, two, three, four, five cops.
This is the fifth precinct of Long Island.
It's a very bad area, I'm driving through, this is North Bellport.
A lot of?
Yeah, a lot of drugs, a lot of, oh shit!
Oh shit that car got the whole front end torn off he had a pole
No, it's beautiful. Yeah, that car. I wish you guys I'm sorry
I didn't give a good camera view that car. It looks like everybody's okay though because I'm not trying to
Yeah, that everyone's okay the kid that of his car looks like a young kid and he was like limping
But that car went right into that pole and the whole front end is completely pushed in
Yeah, hopefully it's okay
He is okay, because I saw him he's limping out of the car, but he's like walking around fun
Crazy that hit a pole. He fucking went boom right into it the pole
It was a Hyundai. Do you know what like crumple zones are? I'm not gonna get into it
Do you know what that is in a car?
Tell me, Crumple's going, what is that?
Just really quick, the new cars, Hyundai, like the 5-star crash test ratings, they crumple
from the outside.
Your bed comes off right and then it's not like it's the old cars
We just come right into you where it would hit you
You know I mean now they crumple in and the cars don't you know impact you that way that's the best way to explain it
So it's basically like you know it takes away the the shock that it absorbs the shock
You explained it better than I did
I can't go away the shock absorb, shock absorbance I guess is what it is yeah
Well, you know, like, you know, alcoholics will like oftentimes survive car accidents because they're so relaxed when they crash
That they like if they're sober your body's gonna tense up and you and then it's like it kind of separates
You have to you know concussion will separate your brain from your skull basically when you put the impact will move back, right?
And it's like
Yeah, but yeah, because they're so relaxed they get drunks would often survive these cars
It's that other people that there were sober wouldn't survive
It's kind of because they're so relaxed that they just go like ease into the crash basically instead of like
So that's like the mental point of view now let's think of a physical point of view
Alcohol, I believe it's a venue medically. It's been your blood. Is that that's correct, right?
Everybody because they like
Did that have anything to do with,
now I know if you get a cut, you would bleed more,
but like, would that have anything to do with surviving?
I'm just trying to like, I never thought of this,
alcohol actually saving you.
Well, I just, I had heard that if you're like tensed up,
then it's like, it's your stiff,
but it's like your brain, but when the impact,
the brain is like, the skull and the brain
are like, attached by these little fibers.
And it's like, when you hit like that,
if you're tensed up, like the skull,
that's like, the brain will stay the same place,
I'm looking up right now
That's a little bit more like I'm thinking now perceiving it like how you just said tensing up and shit
And the brain in the skull because I am a big fan of mind over matter
You know rage against the machine the monk
That's that was my avatar for a while if anybody knows it out there the first album of rage against the machine
It says there's something called a floppy drunk theory.
It says one theory suggests that intoxicated drivers due to their relaxed muscles and delayed
reaction times may not tense up as much during a collision, potentially leading to fewer
deceleration injuries.
So for individuals, often brace themselves for impacts.
Go ahead.
Yeah, I hope you're not a lick of pee, Ann.
Yeah
And they get in car accidents
That's why most people that are drunk and that are drunk and getting car accidents like that half the time
They survive while other people die because of the sensing of your body or even get hurt
They might not die
But they could get hurt really bad because their body tenses up to where as a somebody that's trash might just kind of bounce all
Inside the car and not since up
It's a pretty crazy though. That's like, you know, it was one thing when it's like the people that are innocent like our you know
Pay the pay the price sometimes more than the guilty party. Yeah
Like guys doesn't happen all the time like somebody's drunk and he he or she survives and the people die like don't you feeling that happens a lot? Oh
Yeah, well
The worst Oprah ever so it was about this family. They were coming home from a wedding and they have the dash cam on or whatever
And then there was there an all-in-a-limo and all of a sudden like there's some truck going the wrong way down the road
Collided it's like the worst driver heard like the mother was like out on the on the
See on the curb after and like she saw her daughter's head like roll by her or something
Yeah, it's like most horrific. It was one of the worst episodes of a TV show ever
I was like Oprah one time and they went over the strong drivers
Yeah, it was terrible.
Strawberry ice cream is delicious.
That's one of my favorites.
Neapolitan is pretty good too.
Do you remember that strawberry does go well together?
I'm talking about ice cream.
Yeah, I'm eating any strawberry ice cream right now.
It's delicious.
You know everybody in the family has a favorite and like if they're the big ice cream person and you open the box up
That one part is gone because vanilla was mine
And I always used to eat the vanilla and that one part of it would be gone. Do you know what I mean?
It's like yeah, I used to eat all the all the
There's a certain smurf out of the smurfs vitamins
I would take each vitamin until I found the smurf I wanted and then I still have to eat the whole bottle looking for the smurf
Let's talk ice cream cycle. Favorite flavor all the time. Let's talk to my stream. Favorite flavor all the time
Mine is probably like white chocolate raspberry or something like that. They have the really good
Strawberry chunks
Yeah, it's like with a cheesecake with a big like big like chunks of cheese cake
I'm a big cookie doll fan and ice cream chocolate chip cookie doll man
I like vanilla ice cream too, regular just old school vanilla ice cream. I love that vanilla ice cream
I don't know I like
Now there's this ice cream spot down the street and they make birthday cake ice cream, but they like blast actual birthday cake
Into the ice cream. So there's like chunks of cake in it and it's fire
That's my favorite flavor, although I don't mean to be a dick, but it's been around for a while
Carvel makes that flavor. They came out with the original birthday cake flavor, but um
What's the name of the company, Psyche?
I know they have it in California.
It's like Carvelle and, you know,
Carvelle and what?
I just know about Cookey Puss, you know?
Cookey Hill.
So like Carvelle and Cookey Puss.
The famous Carvelle on creation is Cookey Puss.
I
Like the 31 flavors ice cream cakes. Those are really good for
Yeah, we're waking up a little bit
Also, I like butter pecan ice cream
Just made it back darker. It was like that up a little bit
I'm doing a photo shoot tomorrow, and I can't wait to have it's got I have angel wings
It's gonna be dope this fuck
But they're black
And I had some of those yes, yeah from the you
She are from you know a country. I can't really mention, but yeah
She had some black black black waterproof wings ordered
You know from a war zone basically and had them they came and they're pretty cool
But their waterproof black wings and she would wear on show which he does her dishes and stuff like that
Yeah
Yeah, so Casey is now over there because I keep you know Casey like I got kicked off of the show
I blocked in here, so he's decided to go over there and probably talk a lot of crap about me
But it's fine. I'm not over there anymore. So I don't really don't care
But yeah, Casey, you know won't be around anymore guys
Why did he get kicked off before? I mean, that's has been annoying as well.
Yeah, because he was like sort of like saying calling me all these names because I wouldn't let him on one day because I had you know
I was just doing the one-on-the-time thing and so he's like so then he's just started like going off on me in the chat
I eventually blocked him in the chat and then he went to beat us and was that nothing you there and then
Now he's got some other show
So I don't know but he's like have fun at Emma's if you want attention you're not really gonna get up there
She does not bring people on the screen or barely talks in the chat. So you're not gonna really like
I don't know. Maybe she'll maybe she'll maybe she loved ice cream. Did you go ice cream?
She's like, oh
You're eating ice cream the first time or like why they sometimes people take pictures of you the first ice cream
It's uh
I know I sometimes say I came to earth for the ice cream. It's like because it was you know, it's one of my favorite things to eat
Just in the middle of the night when you're hot
Yeah, I can get like a whole pint of it. Okay, so let's see who's here on the school of Athens is back. There we go
Okay
I really apologize. I'm almost I'm be home in 15 minutes. I'm in bad service in the woods. No problem
I'm still trying to think. I'm just gonna say once chat if you guys anybody from New York area
It's a big chain of ice cream million dollar cooperation just like Carvel and 31 flavors best grab and anybody can help me out with that food
I don't know, but I don't got a huge chunk of my strawberry. Oh, it's so big so good
Is it a creamery or something?
Coldstone is coldstone
Coldstone creamery they came out
Canada with that cat um
I know coldstone
actual birthday cake and they get actual snickers and they mash it up with the spoons and put it in yeah
And make hard ice cream soft like that birthday cake is my favorite mix that with cookie dough pieces
Canada
My favorite we used to have a cold stone ice cream in London, but it looks like they pulled them all out of Ontario
We have a lot of like mom-and-pop corner like
Like parking lot spots and certain ones are like really well known as being good
You know what I mean like just little trailer spots in the back of a parking lot or at them like
And you're a farm or something and there's just a bunch of cars parked out front
No, like we got one called scoops we got another one called Merle may and like they're just like these
Like small family-run ice cream spots, so they make their own ice cream in-house and it's they'll have like rotating like
They never have the same flavors every time you go kind of
What's my avatar Canada
Fucking no one said it's just it's just a
No, it's just
Yeah, it's the gray picture like that the pro the default fucking gray
Well, how we say you're booing
No, we can't
There do you want some ice-cream give me your mama. I think I had to do it from like offline or something like that
like
I went to her track meet today
Really cute
She's four and a half and she runs track. Well, it's awesome. There's family like that
She's born to run track
I
Go to start him young, you know, I don't know if I I don't know if I ever like, you know
You're walking yeah, I mean I'm sure it's walking I'm hoping I was running
The cross country cross-country
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
No, no, no, there's like three-minute miles
I'm just saying a mile will take at least three minutes. Did I break five minutes?
I think it was like three miles, but it's over different terrain. And so it's
I didn't do track I did cross country
It's it's way different my father was a cross-country runner and he did what you're talking about the different terrain up hill downhill
You know that like there was like wasn't shit like so I did it
I did like you have to do like Virginia life cars
We had to pass this like that's where we had to go like I think like four
Ways across the Olympics ice swimming pool like it's like good to go like we're back and forth four times and
I was like at first I was like really slow it took me over two minutes to do it and then
Then by the end, I was doing it like 20 seconds ahead of time and so, but yeah.
The hunk.
The lifeguard hunk.
Spikey.
I was just, I was like probably 10 years old and they couldn't help.
Junior lifeguards.
They have it on Baywatch.
You can see it like this.
Baywatch is filmed right here.
Baywatch is films here, by the way.
It was filmed at Redondo Beach.
Baywatch was filmed here.
Yeah, that show is a fucking...
When I watched the Pamela Anderson Tommy Lee show and they showed what they did to the women on that show.
made excuses that the bikini line of the women's ass had to be a certain inch so that was the rule
so they were allowed to get up close to the woman's ass where they could stick their nose in it
and use their fingers and make it, you know, wide enough so it was legal for television and Pamela
Anderson had to sit there while some grimy guys got two fingers on the inside of her bathing suit
I would request women, I would request a woman to do it.
School really wanted that job.
Some of those greasy crew members, you know?
I'd be like, I'd have a woman do it.
But then my life would be like,
if I was a lesbian and then do this kind of thing.
Even if you were a lesbian,
fixing Pamela Anderson's ass would have been.
You know she got this I felt so bad. Well, all right, what's your view of Pamela?
She's huge. She's like our man on my row, right of the 90s everybody agree
She was Marilyn Monroe of the 90s. I never really
Ann and Nicole Smith Ann and Nicole Smith is more like the Maryland
They were two different lengths
Yeah, I think Pamela Anderson is like more like about Jane Mansfield, Pamela Anderson was more of like the various, yeah, Jane Mansfield.
I think it's the opposite. I think Jane Mansfield is Anna Nicole Smith, but you know, it's just our opinion because like Anna just was, why do you think that? Tell me why.
I'm interested.
Kind of like it's kind of like I don't know. I just think Anna Nicole's more intelligent than and she was also back in her day
She was like the uh, they're her guest jeans like those pictures are like as beautiful as a moment row is
In the same
I thought the opposite, and I could totally be wrong because I have no facts to back this up.
I thought like Anna Nicole Smith was, I mean Pamela was more intelligent,
but all I'm saying that is, is because of the new Pamela Tommy show.
That show really backed up at...
showed her in a good light and like protected her in the show. So I got to do research because
you could totally be right and Nicole Smith could be like way more. Well she died like
Marilyn Monroe. She died the same way. I think the same age as Marilyn Monroe. She always thought
she would. She was her idol. I mean that was who she idolized. That was a lot of people vital.
So like to be honest with you like I'm obsessed with you know Andy Warhol. Like I have the you know
paint like a lot of those paints you know obviously not cause but like I have a
lot of those like fuck I have a real soup can on my wall I got the shirt I'm
wearing the shirt right now I've got a real Andy Warhol soup can no you don't
yeah it's on my wall I'll show it to you
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's not real though. If it was really be worth about hundreds of thousands. I wouldn't be in this chat room right now
I'm not gonna lie
You would not you'd be in some yuppie circle
Cocktails and wearing a Rolex. Yeah
So I keep favorite art work piece of artwork all time
It has to be that the it has to be the the garden of good and evil by Hieronymus Bosch
You expect that thank you. Yeah me neither, but I should expect it because he's
He's so smart man. I actually I saw it in person at the Prado in Spain when I went to Spain when I was a 14
We saw that in person. It's amazing. It's amazing people are
Yeah, I am a huge traveler and I still have never been to Spain, like I need to go to Madrid, Barcelona, I need to go to those two places, and Catalonia too, do you go to Catalonia?
Yeah, it's very beautiful
Beautiful country. I went to like I went to Toledo, Spain
I stayed in Granada where they have like that the Alhambra
I was back with the more when there are more stick there
So it's like a Muslim style palace there. They have really beautiful areas
I also went to a gypsy bar which is inside a cave you go into this cave and there's from my gypsy's and they
So bar I was like 14 years old when I went with the group and
I basically was really tempted to go drink, but you know
Yeah, that's our senior was raging demon that's it. It's our senior. Let's talk it shit
I like how you brought up the moors, what's your view on the moors?
Well, I mean, it's like there was like yeah, there's some Muslim colonization and like the you know
Like the 14-15 hundreds they built some palaces
You know, but there was a lot of wars fought over it and I did the religion
The Inquisition yes, the Inquisition
Inquisition yes, there was
Oh, history of the world. It's from history of the world of part one, Mel Brooks. The Inquisition, and he's dancing all the more.
There's one other guy, let me check that out. There's one of those Monty Python.
Oh, history of the world of part one.
Monty Python?
I can recite Life of Brian, and any line you want just do it with me. Just pick out a scene.
How can a ten pound sparrow... No, swallow.
maybe it's an african swallow
yeah
you know what my favorite line is
when
I can't even say
I love british humor so much
it's so much better than america
when the guy comes up on
the white guy and he goes old woman
do you remember that scene?
and he turns around and he goes man
and he goes oh sorry
do you remember that scene?
sorter?
And he's talking about a democracy in the monarchy.
And he's like, I'm your sovereign.
I'm your king.
Well, who elected you then?
You don't vote for kings.
How did you become a king?
The lady of the lake.
You remember?
He goes, so some Flamin' Todd threw a sword at you and you became a king.
How is that any form of coming, a form of government in this day and age?
Is that the same movie where they're like, they're throwing the dead people and the guy's like,
bring out your dad.
Bring out your dad!
Boom, he's almost mostly dead his 10 bucks. Okay, boom
Or it's super funny too in in the meaning of life when John Cleese is teaching his class how to fuck and he really
Fox in front of the class
I met him. I met John Cleese. He's one of my idols
So important
He really is, what's the word, selfless and admits like how other people made him good.
And he talks about America and he talks about the guy who is a spokesperson for 1A activism,
Lenny Bruce.
And that's why Lenny Bruce is the king of all comedians all the time.
He is the biggest spokesman for the 1A activism cause, posthumously, and he's the ultimate
king of comedy.
Lenny Bruce, everybody, look it up.
So funny on John Cleese. He's like instructing the kids. He's in the middle of like fucking his wife
And he's like giving the one kid it or not having his math homework
It's something funny
And then they're playing rugby and he's just getting their shit
Python scene what's your favorite for me movie what's your favorite movie meaning a life life of
brian probably meaning of life yeah what's your favorite every meaning of life i used to sing all
those songs man they're like every sperm is sacred song they're like isn't it awfully nice to have a
beginning with the orphans because that's my least well-known one but I've seen
them all yeah the beginning with the orphans and there's they're all singing
and she's like doing and a baby falls out she's like but it's all intelligent
comedy like psyche would love it because you know it has meaning behind it the
difference of the Roman Catfish
He comes home, he's like, well, I've made a decision today and I have to send a lot of you for adoption, so off you go.
Well done, Canada. Well done. I'm really sorry, dad. I'm really sorry.
Every sperm is sacred. Every sperm is good.
They don't know. They don't know.
Yeah, it's a great food, let's realize it.
What else?
Why do you not know Monty Python?
This is John Cleese, man, this is.
It's American, it's Americans that close mind.
People don't like me when I bash on Americans
because I sound like, but I love this country.
It's the greatest country in the world
and I am so grateful to be in here,
have a roof over my head, a job and be healthy,
but we're very close.
It's just like echo culture, it's just like, we don't.
Well, like, Summer taught me one thing
about local government and like,
close-minded that like not only local government but what's going on in the
world like most Americans couldn't name like four or five foreign leaders right
they maybe say black Putin right that's like it that's like what they say but
like someone taught me about the importance of local government and as I
met her I kind of I went to a city all meeting and I started voting like in the
um you know what's it called the um I voted for the you know taxes for the
That's really where you get things done more. I don't know if you're still here somewhere, but correct me if I'm wrong
You would agree right like that's where you start and you can get more things done
Yeah, you always start with your local politics before anything
That's cool
You know what happened to me some of the other day I was in a smoke shop and the guy came in
He was a liberal guy, and I'm not conservative everyone. I'm just pointing out a fact that other guy was liberal
Nice doesn't mean he's bad and he started
at the smoke shop because a girl came in and said,
do you have any handouts?
And the guy gave her a cratum.
Does anybody know what cratum is?
Cratum?
Yeah.
Yeah, so I know what it is.
And I know all the things involved with it.
And I know it's dangerous.
And my friend took it and had withdrawal problems.
But he gave her one of them.
And it's actually legal, so he didn't do anything wrong.
And this guy came in, and he was like,
how can you just give this to an addict?
I'm listening to it before I got involved because the guy was taking trenches and that's not his fault
He has a job this woman came in alone, and he's handing things out
He doesn't know about that so I interjected and helped my friend out and I was like listen man
Your problem start with him first of all
It's with her and if you want to make a difference go down to your local government and speak out about
Created him and how you think it should be will you do that? No, he won't do that
so somewhere I kind of took a page out of your book and gave him a little dose like
You know you want to make a change stop yelling like go, you know, go to your fucking city all meeting
Yeah, it just me off the creative thing I keep seeing it getting talked about on podcasts like a lot of people are like using it
Heroin and I'm being dramatic, but it really does hit
So to be scientific for psyche sake because he's my scientist but hold on the hold on where do you get freedom like it's in your gas
Yes on Long Island any and how is it packaged? It's like a pill or what?
All right, so there's a million different ways
The first ones came out and it's powder form and what they do is it's in the Southeast Asia, right?
What's some country down there psyche Burma, right? Vietnam Laos
This thing comes from and they have little kids like go into the jungle and fucking pick this shit
You know and then it comes in powder form and you can take it in a capsule
That's how I did it the first time ten years ago. I tried it
I always try everything and it fucked me up like I felt like I was on Vicodin
You know and I was like no way this ain't for me my friend
you know he's he's got a lot of trouble with um opiates and he tried to take that to get off
off of heroin well not heroin but my cannon and what happened to him is he started getting
withdrawals from that and he was paid 90 of the day that's not a lot 90 crazy weird that's so
man i'm just so like blown away like they're selling a narcotic in the gas station i know
Is it like that salvia thing? Do you remember when there was a time when you could buy salvia at the variety store?
You still can in New York, but I don't know what that is. Can you inform me summer or a psyche or what in salvia is?
Well, so when I took salvia, my friend brought it over. I think it was like a 60 or 90x bag, and I put it in a pipe.
He had already hit it. He sat he sat across from me. I was sitting on my bed. He was sitting on a chair and
He's like after you hit it like you might drop the pipe. So like I'll grab it. I was like what the fuck so I hit it and
It was like one side of my body like my arm and
My side of my face felt paralyzed and I could only slap my fucking the side of my leg for like
Yeah, for like 20 or 30 seconds and then it went away and I just felt kind of like nauseous and I was like, bro
This is fucked and he laughed. He's like, yeah, dude. It is fucked
I just like because we had been talking about it
He had already tried it and I wanted to try it and I never tried it again because it was just so weird
And I know that's a different drug than cratum, but it's just weird that like every 20 years
There's a new drug at the gas station
Yeah, because it's all over the world. So Sally is from Guam. Okay, you know Guam is right
Okay, yeah
Okay, so America owns Guam that they incorporated territory of America. We took the country over it was a
monarchy and we took it over for political military reasons, right?
Especially during World War two and we've owned it ever since and
I'm not this smart, but I knew it came from Guam, but it's called Divinorum, and that's
only in Guam, and that's why America gets so much of it, because, thank you, help me
out with the economic, like the macroeconomics of it.
We don't have to pay tariffs, right, when something's from Guam in America, because
we own the...
Isn't that correct?
Like, we just farm it and sell it, right?
I hear you, but I just I don't understand why why gas stations get to sell drugs like you here like I know I'm trying to talk
It's like a question though. Is that true psych?
Yeah
So
It's a big problem. It's legal in 29 states. Okay? And you just said you don't know I get that shit is all about money, and it's fucking local population up.
Really, really bad. People are addicted to this shit.
Big problems.
Kratom's really bad, man.
Getting old
What are you doing Canada
I'm just chillin out
Gonna show coffee. Where's psyche?
We go. I don't know. It's I don't know. He was here
It's not like I can open a drawer and find them. I'm just in my house psyche
I tried it could be in the cabinet like I understand. That's fair. I could look in my fridge
Okay, I draw could be locked, you know, but it cabinets are up higher. It's like he's always up top. Where's he at?
Psycho Roni
The fuck just happened did he pass out start looking around my house for psyche like he's not on the internet
Oh, like what yo chat what's going on with psyche like where's Waldo?
Yo, everybody makes those AI things now so easily.
Can you make like a book with the animation of psyche
that are in all those like AI things
and do like a Where's Waldo?
It's like he's hair and like it's how funny would that be?
Like in a picture.
Can you help me with that?
The psyche can dress up as Where's Waldo.
For halloween like if he if he got the striped outfit and yeah, he could do it
What's it to is that it is that a scar Oh a beanie. Is that what you call?
Well a beanie if I'm not wrong guys a beanie doesn't have the little ball on top, right?
That's also what it's like a beanie. So a toke or a watch cap. Oh
shit
Cool, you know what a watch. Yeah, we'll get it. No, but I'm guessing it's got the little ball thing on top. No, it doesn't oh
Okay, it just rolls up on the sides like it's like a sailor
Gotcha, bro. We and how about the red and white scarf and a little, you know, winter cap with the ball on top
That's red and white and give him the glasses because like he kind of looked like Superman like I'm sorry
But he definitely looking he looks like Clark Kent, right? He's got the big tin
What do you think?
Yeah, maybe a little come on. Give it to like you some love. These are good-looking dude
Those pictures show you show your feminine side, bro. It's okay
Okay, I don't have a feminine side dude. I'm 300% testosterone
You're the toughest guy. I know I'm a big muscley fucking meat. You are you're like a fucking shock man. You never show me
You fucking meat sack
Do you know what I bought myself today is a present
No, okay, you know me. I'm gonna give you one. Yeah, I'm gonna tell you a record
Nice, yeah, bro, I'm gonna show it to you right now if you want. I don't care, but
I'd fill out the air conditioning. It's a Vic Troller
Okay, and it's it's it's white with white speakers and brown
Like on the around the outside of it. Okay, like a cabinet brown light brown with white
so much of the furniture I
Bought jizza liquid swords
Money's hilarious. He had a live stream queued up and he kept delaying it and now he's just taking it off
He never went live though like himself and went on there when you're with a peep hold off. No, how do you know?
Well, I don't know
Yo psych where you have
I mean you got that we're holding it down
Right here
I'm walking around backstage to see Patrick away
We're running away from what?
It's not Patrick. It's just P.H.T. It stands for psyche wakens tarot. It's not
Yeah, I like it. I like it, but hey, hey Marcy. How are you?
Raging demon are you still screaming at everybody? Oh, yeah, hold on
At least he likes Marcy. Okay, JT triggers hurricane kid. What's going on? Gotta learn away from
How about video games?
I'll put this up on the screen. There you go guys
Guys if you go to tick-tock, let me see if it works. Hold on
I don't know if I have to type in tick-tock or this one here. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm gonna go at probably 1 a.m
Because today when I stream from there, I will be I'll get my full privileges for streaming
It's like, you have to do it three days in a row.
T-A-K-T, okay.
I don't know if I spelled it right.
Let's see if it works.
Okay, there we go.
It works.
So there's my TikTok.
If you wanna come say hi to me,
I do really quick readings there.
I just spend like just a short time, like an hour.
It goes really fast paced,
but there are a lot of people that come in and stuff.
It's fun.
If you ever wanna check out TikTok, it's pretty cool.
I don't I don't know how good it will be for monetizing but there are people that make some good money from it
No, but uh, we'll take a while to get monetized. It's 10,000 followers on a kick-talk
Easier to get that on YouTube, but still not the easiest but
Also, you cannot smoke on camera you if you smoke if I was to blow the smoke I would get like I'm a say restricted video
For smoking tobacco or something. They saw me do that. I did it yesterday. I got what happened
I'm also on steps as hella Graham. We're gonna tell a Graham
No, I'm not a telegram. I do have a kick. I sometimes stream to actually I'm also I'm also
syndicated by a trip kick on a rumble
He's he all you know, so you can I don't know I shouldn't be like really advertising that but yeah
The trip kick is like syndicating me so that's that's cool because I'd like to have some of my old episodes available
Oh, yeah, there's a pizza. Okay. I'll wait. I'll wait for you to come on panel. I might be in the background a little bit
But I do enjoy, I do enjoy TikTok.
It's actually a really, really fun thing,
especially for readings because people come in
and I probably do more readings today
than I would do in a whole show here
because they're just quick, like one card readings.
And then people will ask the question,
like it's a really fast-paced movie.
Also people are like walking through all the time.
And so.
You know, there's like a lot of people coming that don't stay, right?
It's like it's like you do you do tube scrolling, right? Do you scroll?
night guys
Okay, that's cool. Okay. It's an occasion getting your um, no
They're not they're not they're not they're not monetizing it
They just it's just for archive purposes and it's like and so I'm cool with it. I guess if I was cool with it
I was like, oh sure. I think I like it because you know
I do have to end sometime on YouTube and then delete it and then so
So some of them are there, you know, and then you can see like, you know, the stuff that's, you know, it's not as strict as YouTube with, you know, the porn bomb, I guess they'll keep up to the episode and stuff. I'm not sure, but, and plus, they're not, you know, it's like, it's harder to monetize on rumble anyway, so, but who knows, they're a good person, they are, they're the ones that do all the AI videos of a, you know, me and, me and Joe kissing or putting my face on the broke back now, so that's a trip kick.
So no problem with it like someone told me about it before like thinking I would be mad and I was like well
That's the I don't care if people share the show. It's like I
Mean any exposure I can get it's gonna be good. So yeah, they also did you also stream betas?
I think or you know, they archive betas and
Cues and a few other people
I think it's if you look up trip kick or something on room rumble. I think that's where it is. I'm not 100% sure
And then it saves me because then it's like then it's not associated with my me
So there's nothing I could ever get in trouble for on it on that, you know, so
No, no big deal
Okay, so how's miss Liz hey miss Liz. How are you? Hey Patrick, New York?
Hey everybody always some random motherfucker trying to whoa you're talking about I'm a GT. How are you JT?
Oh, look at the CJT you're unmod your Anna your unbanned remember where you were banned from the second day
I'm banned you
on the other count
The NPD don't bring your drought, oh, NPD, who's that?
We're spunky tonight.
She was here earlier, she got me a new deck
called the True Prime deck that I asked for,
it was on my wish list, and I did some readings with that
today, it's a pretty interesting deck.
Hey Ms. Liz, yeah, we're having a nice night tonight,
we got, you know, we had some sad news today,
I don't know if, I think everyone's heard of you know,
Michael L passed away.
And, you know, I just want to remember, remember him, he was part of the show, and, you know, I won't ever forget him, but I think maybe hopefully he's in a better place than, you know, doing what he wants to do.
Bless Michael. Okay, so let's see. Let's change everything Vader. What do you say?
Does that actually make sense even though it's up or down? Well, it's up or down. It's just perspective. Oh, yeah
Michael passed away. Yeah, Michael did pass away July 18th, I believe. Might loop down a little ice cream.
Yeah, kind of kind of a shocking, right? Because he seemed pretty healthy and fighting spirit and
I don't know exactly what happened, but it was unexpected for
Bitches a bitch erase that it was unexpected
I was gonna say JT is cool Patrick don't be offended, but you have like a personal issue like you maybe a little jealous of them
it's not an accumulation. First ghost tonight he must be hung over. Yeah maybe yeah he was
in here the first couple of nights. Yeah it was wild and stuff. Like last night I came back I came
back like when I ended the second time last night I did come back to like let him do the last hour
and then he needed to come back so I ended kind of early but uh yeah it was kind of it was kind
What can I say? It's like maybe I'll be able to get my new computer that I've been needing for the show
It's pretty badly or at least if not, maybe
Yeah, I don't I don't know. Um, maybe another
Tablet or something because this Amazon stuff doesn't cut it the Amazon tablet
It's okay for like Kindle reading the Kindle books. I have like over a thousand so or 10,000 books probably on Kindle
So it's probably like good for that, but nothing else really it's slow and it doesn't take any Google apps
And so and they are cheap though. I think 60 bucks from Amazon. I got it for 55
Um, you know you me she's like what don't you agree with you me? Oh, you know, oh Patrick or
You see what Slayer did typical mistake I asked the question
Accusation people can't help that but you know
Yeah, well, sometimes people take things personally if they're like maybe it's often times when they're like maybe they do
Yeah, that was a question. You're saying I don't agree, but how do you know you don't agree with me?
How do you know I actually agree with you? You took it personal.
And now you can either admit that you did or dig yourself deeper. What are you doing next, bro?
What's your next move?
I think I've got a dogging problem in my fucking in the back yard next to my house.
Cool. I want that in Slayer. Do you remember that?
I love you, bro.
These people come in they park in the parking lot and they start parking and then another car parks beside them
I think I think they're dogging bro
You guys know anything about dogging?
No, I just jt's make me laugh. Love love it
South vader
Uh vader favorite um star wars
piece of
you know
Any show or any movie which is favorite
or
It's like do you know anything about dogging is that uh, is that popular in your communities?
About what about what dog?
Dogging dog in jogging jogging dog. You know dogging dog. I know I haven't heard of that. What is that? Oh
As far as I can tell it's it's like people meeting up to watch each other have sex in public places
Hmm. Yeah, I haven't heard of that. They call it jogging.
Mm-hmm. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I'm like not even a boy
Like I literally had with some friends come over there tonight and come in and like have sex in the other room with the door
Open and I didn't even get up or like, you know, I'm not like
It is while the second time they did it for the first time they did it
He let me I came in the room. He told me to come they called me into the room
So this is like a parking lot on the other side of my house and there's just it's wild it is wild out here
Oh, and you did Marcy. You did some overnight panels with Michael. Yeah, Michael and Greenie. Yep
You're at Benny's
I think it's that I didn't have a crush on him, you know, I always like did like him, you know
Kind of good. He had a little bit of shit. I think he you know, he he was
Remember Flurry Diamond and Michael and they would fight and like, you know, he was a little bit of a chaser. I would
I would say
No, no shade. No shade. It was this thing. It was kind of yeah, he was very open-minded open-minded person
I think in that way I don't think he yeah, he acted like he was
He actually wasn't but you he was very kind just kind of a few trans people that I'm aware of MPD
You really do know what I do with stream yard and even stream yard
What do you mean the MPD? What does MPD mean in your police department?
Know it's just like that. I hope like maybe his girlfriend. He has a girlfriend more like the DMR
She'll call it. That's the couple and the number one couple in YouTube easy and Marcy
She might come in she might come out and they come in together. They're the number one couple
There's an easy married he's married to Marcy. They're married
No, he's not
Never been married
at summer. They're like more brother and sister than anything. Nobody knows. It's like he's laughing,
you know, kind of, it was just. I didn't know. No, we're laughing at you because it was ridiculous.
They're not, they don't really know. Yeah, I know that. I know that. It was just a joke,
No, you're fine. Just let us know when you're trolling because I thought you were being serious
Okay, I guess I guess
I'm sorry, I think things pretty literal sometimes well
So, you know, but I also do the same thing where I think with a straight face sometimes in a not serious way
People are like what? Yes
So let's see 1256 in Los Angeles. Let me see it. I saw some churros. I saw my whole
copy left. This is a cream caramel, caramel latte or something. Very good. Caramel, cream,
Hey easy. Oh, yeah, so I told him to ban Bruno because he was like, oh, he's everybody said he's like, oh, I don't talk to gay freaks
Okay, I'm here. Holy shit. Yeah, but in the chat
He just he said he is then my he's he tried to get him up on panels and to confirm him
He's like, well, I don't talk to gay freaks, you know, meaning me
So I just hadn't kicked out of the room, but he wants to come on panel sometime
I'm willing to talk to him, but yeah, I first met him on TPP when I went over there doing readings when I was starting out
And I did a reading for I think everyone in the room practically they all like nine people and he was like
You know, he's the only one that started talking shit about me afterward
So that's that's it. He's just like good times some people just don't like eight people
But I think they have probably some repressed homosexuality in my opinion
Yeah
Yeah, uh, there you go. Oh, you dropped. I agree with you. It's like 100% what you just said
Yeah, it's like or else people wouldn't have such a problem
They wouldn't be so is it homophobia is like really about like the insecurity of themselves not homophobic people can joke around and not
Did you run with each other and they joke around they can joke around with gay people and it's like not a big deal
And it's like some are even flattered and they like to hear that they're considered good-looking by the gay commuter or whatever
Anybody in the chat says about me two men that are
Make it love. I don't yeah, I'm not into it
But it is beautiful. Fuck anybody else who thinks I'm weird or I'm a fucking loser
It's a beautiful thing for them
It's the same thing for me and a woman and how we feel as like he feels and that's life
That's the human connection. So whether it's two males or a male and a female whoever what they like
That's what it is. I can I can tell you psyche. I'll end the plane in 20 seconds. I'm afraid
he was extremely homophobic and now he is married and he's meeting men in hotel rooms and ruining his
met me because he's gay you know what I mean he's like and he can't come clean like and that's where
a lot of like the dirty like back alley or like the park bathroom stuff comes in it's always going
to be some closet a closet case doing that like going to the middle of the park in the middle of
the night like in the bathroom stall looking for like glory hole or something it's like usually
it is easy enough to find people without having to go into a dark alley or something like that.
You drink half the weed drink. Oh, how many milligrams, Marcia? I think some of those are
pretty strong. Sure, they have a really low, like at the places I go, they have really low
THC percentages in the edibles. It's like 25 or 50 milligrams, and it should be like 500.
So there's a little bit yeah, but I like that school of Athens that you're like you can say it's beautiful
It's like, you know, is it beautiful is it not I'm like I always think of like the idea of sex is more
Appealing to me than actually having sex whenever I actually had sex I get really bored and that's like I just find it
I found it boring and it's like I'm just like oh and then it's like I'm always like wanting to end and so I don't know
It's like I'm not really like I'm more into like affection or like cuddling
No, I mean it's like
I'm not
Says he's gay, but he also tells me he does exactly what you said like he doesn't love having sex
He'd rather just be
affectionate like
He could come with a guy or a girl, but he's not really trying to get laid
I think it's pretty extreme like it's that like, you know, it's just like, you know, first of all, it's anal
It's like, you know, it's not the most pleasant pleasant things like, you know, you have to ease yourself into you, right?
But also, you know, it's like it's just so I'm not really and that doesn't feel to me and then big, you know
I'm mainly it's I'm like it's hot, but it's like and so it doesn't I
Know this is like it always seems more better in my mind
And so that's why I really don't go looking for it because I'm more than happy enough says here in Cali
It's only 100 milligram per product. Oh, yeah, so that's like the maximum was gonna be 100 milligrams, right?
I see some out of I've gotten some out of state stuff. I guess it's like a lot more and much better, but
Yeah, here's Athens back again. Sorry. I love you Alex. That's Alex. He took a screenshot of me
I could just came up right now. You see me a million times. I
Know it's Alex. Do you see the way he he writes? He was oh, yeah
I saw a loser in a cemetery today, and I thought of you that's Alex. I love you
Come on, bro
Yeah, I started out the show today with the Alex and Paige so long. Yeah, I kind of I kind of love that video
Yeah, it's way better than the gummies. Yeah
Yeah, I do like the drinks, you know
I think the drinks taste really good too. The gummies sometimes taste a little bit medicinal or
You know someone does stuff is like it burns to my tongue kind of it
Yeah, I do like the drinks the drinks a lot better. Hey, do you want to say hi tricks come on down and say hi?
Say hi everybody
This is running around that he was running around the house today like so fast. Were you running around fast? You're even around the house
He was this cat's the cuddler he's like I wake up every day and if he knows
This cat is a sweetheart. He's Mr. Tricks
Let's be high boop boop boop boop there you go. Come on back here. It's my cuddle my cuddle bud
Who's which Alice I think it's
Everyone I am school bathroom. Hello. Well, is that my who's that back picture? Hold on. That's your picture. Is that you?
Hey, that's me. He got me
He took a screenshot of like a video of me and I'm like, you know, like when you make a face
I'm like breathing in and it's like, yeah
Yeah, I don't care. You can take a million videos of someone and get us. Yeah things of it
I don't like actually people when they
They blink or something like there's so many if you video someone you can get a still shot. They look so bad
Like that's what it's got. Oh
figured out so fast because of the way he, his grammar.
He's like, look at all the time he's ready.
Come on back.
In Hollywood, they tried, the paparazzi will yell at people
like something about like their, their mom or, you know,
or they'll, they'll get, try to say something shocking
and horrible, so they, maybe they get a grimace
or they get like a, oh, that's, him's like, yeah,
that's cool about this in the chat.
Where's Vinny Paws and Pans?
I don't know where he is, he says, oh, he's trying to say that's a picture of me on his avatar. You know what I mean? I came down, he took a video of it, and the scream resolution got 60 megahertz and he slowed it down and took one picture where I'm like breathing in and I have like a fat face, you know, like, it's just, yeah, it's just an idiot, like.
He's a child. Yeah, there's plenty plenty of unflattering photos. You know, you can bring up somebody. That's why
I kind of flattered though. He looked, you know, Alex is a little obsessed with people
And he's like, yeah, he's like a bulldozer
Yeah, he's afraid. Do you know what happened? I'm gonna piss Alex off really bad now. You ready? It's like
Yeah, he really got fooled yesterday and he was this isn't troll and he was he was hurt. He was hurt by baby
You know Sean P
Mm-hmm. He was hurt
My heart is feeling yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, Alex thought that he knew what was going on for real and
He didn't and then he got um
He was like, wait a minute, I don't know the day of the fight because Big Baby is fighting
and Alex thought he had to do the real date, but he didn't know and then when he found
out he just jumped down, backed out and didn't say anything, he was hurt.
Well, Alex is, I mean, he thinks that, like...
You know flirty diamond is burdo and he thinks that like you know, he thinks
He thinks everyone has everyone and it's like I was like
You think there's like one person behind every voice
He's like this is this person and it's like that's kind of like
Crazy people say that kind of thing. Yeah. But Alex is one of the funniest people I've ever met in my life.
But sometimes he just goes too far, but he is
He's nuts. Yeah, he can be he can be he definitely can be
I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like
He's bold and wears a hair. It does kind of look like that picture, but it's like he knows my fate. I definitely ain't bold
My hair is actually down past my chin right now, so I can
Come back
How's he getting away from
You fucking know you ever win it dirty Chris K like Chris K was like Chris K is like I went viral
He did you want to show an island viral and I was like oh viral and he's like yeah
Go go play this clip on your show that I don't want to play this clip and then it's like I went and watched it
It was him like approaching in this homeless guy in a tent
Pretending he was the cop and like yelling and harassing this guy and then
Yeah, I turned around on him at the end when the guy like realized he was at a cop and then stole his cell phone
And then wouldn't give it back
Oh my god
Yeah, and it was basically the way the worst the worst
Yeah, I heard you I think it was maybe this morning he's talking about car inspections. Are they charge arm and delay Alex was talking about that actually
Yeah, he's he's he's sold his BMW and he bought a fucking
GMC Denali
he got his inspection which lasts for a year and he got his registration which
lasts for two years and he was trying to tell a big baby about it like you know
to make sure your car is legal and don't get in trouble by the cops because
the Alex was right the New York City cops and the Long Island cops are real
fucking assholes about that shit and it's big tickets
Oh, okay, you don't even need inspection in some states, you know that right?
How much is an inspection you do in California?
All right, so it depends so this is exactly what Alex and I was talking was speaking about so this year, right?
I went to Firestone. Do you know what that company is or no? It's like a yes
So I go there because it's like really close to my house
I have a special mechanic for my BMW, but I go there and I say hey, can I get an inspection?
Do you know how much the receipt said that they wanted for me to get an inspection?
How much? How much? $1,800.
And then when I was like, is there any room in here?
Or is it just, and they said no.
I went to my mechanic, and do you know how much it cost?
$27.
And that's how fucking Alex and I were talking about the price gouging and how people fuck over other people.
I
Really is bro and rich people they just go there right psyche and what do they get they just pay I get a payment car
Well, but it sometimes they you know, my dad would always teach me about like they're no oil change places
We'll always try to upsell you like everything and he's like just get the oil change for 30 bucks
Don't do the idea of cells will cost over $100. You don't need any of the stuff
But they're doing that change the air filter out and stuff that's not really necessary and
Is right
I'm trying to point out now think about somebody who is living paycheck to paycheck that just bought a car
They're legal they just got their citizenship it cost a lot of money and now they buy a pre-owned car
They buy an inspection and that inspection has to be
every year and they try to go to a mechanic and the mechanic just says you can't get an infection unless you pay this, unless you pay this.
And that's why I down south, like they, oh man, we did away with it. Like, do you know how much money that would save people?
Yeah, especially in the East Coast, right? I mean, big cities.
Well, I mean, I don't know. It's a good thing. I'm going to research that, but like, I have a feeling like Arkansas, Alabama,
Kentucky maybe I bet you I wonder if all three of those don't have inspections
So we don't have exceptions
You don't summer
Nope, so there you go, and I'm gonna do a little research that I wonder if like Alabama does or not because
So school can you can you can a person go to another state? They can a New Yorker go to I don't know down South
Did you get his car? I don't know it doesn't make sense to think about that. Hey, why would you do? Yeah, they don't like they're not
you know
You know, they can't do that. They can't get away from inspection
Summer summer
Okay, I'll say imagine summer going to a auto mechanic and he tells summer I gotta charge $800 for inspection
I actually said something. I don't usually go on Google and write bad reviews. I usually
write positive reviews, but I posted the receipt and said, look at this, and then I posted.
It's one thing to do it illegally, Jonathan, because code means in your car when you hook
No, I was to the building codes, but no no no so a code in your car means like
there's a malfunction with a sensor and if you have more than a certain amount of
codes like two or three codes then the inspection can't pass but if you have
like one code then you can clear it and pass the inspection
Some people do it illegally and go around it. Okay, and even though they have codes they give somebody an inspection
Somebody says he has like 300 bucks cash under the table. That's not what like what I was. I legally got the inspection for $37
Spoo, what happens if you don't get the inspection?
that's what Alexander was explaining to Sean P last night, it's serious tickets after, like, you know, they'll hit you once, but then you'll get aggregated, you know, registration and all that shit, and they'll take it to jail, man, and then, you know, release, you got more, yeah, they'll take it to jail.
Oh my god.
Yeah, they won't take it to jail.
I didn't pay my inspection. I know I know people a lot like people that's happened to a lot of my customers over the years
You know, I've sold them cars and then the
They come back next year and they're like, you know, I can't get it inspected
That was a lot
Right now J1
Like I didn't realize how different it is now in the jail system like
So I'm not really familiar with how it works like if you get arrested and then releasing but like I was always on the impression
You get arrested and then there's bail, but now in New York a couple people that's tried to explain to me
And then I looked it up. They did the bail reform and
Like everybody just gets released now I have to do more research. Oh
So like okay, so like you know the inspection done you get arrested then they release you party on the same day
I don't want to go up on it psyche, right? I don't want to start talking about
I don't want to do it here like that's not his platform and I'll go I'll go crazy like
Next time next time. Yeah. Yeah, because you're right. Reyes did that with the tinted windows. They all have tinted windows
So the mechanics here in the East Coast and make a good living all
Dude three things you need in your life. What is it?
Lawyer and a mechanic and a doctor, I guess. Fuck it. You are
Wow, I hate lawyers too. I don't know why I should say that there's some good lawyers
Oh
You're right
No, no, no, go ahead and ask Marcy question. I already did. I just hope she's all right. What did you say?
No, you was driving through a long island. You said it's a bad part. I don't know that ain't have bad parts
Yeah, North Bellport
Wyandanche
Gordon Heights quorum and Hempstead Terrace Avenue
Yeah, that's where met the man from the block is terrorist Avenue. Just type in terrorist Avenue, Hempstead
The Jets have a the training complex in Hempstead
The New York Jets the New York Jets they have a training camp training camp in Hempstead
Is that where it is now it used to be where I went to college it used to be Cortland. Oh, yeah, they moved
You know Cortland State right the college
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Yeah, they're from they're from CI and Brentwood. That's like we're MS-13 was but
It was a lot worse. It's a lot worse than the other areas
When I hear on that and I think of the Hamptons
Yeah, I mean I was in the Hamptons just earlier today. I was in West Hampton
We have bridge Hampton West Hampton
Hampton Bays and then East Hampton. East Hampton is the, you know, the Pete Diddy House, the JFK House, John F. Kennedy House, his wife's cousin, the movie A's, with all the cats. I don't know if you've ever seen that movie.
Drew Barrymore.
Yeah, Drew Barrymore.
Gray Goddons.
that's so that's like the super rich area desert it was and they like lost their money and
like fell into
like
What's it called when it's like you what's it called when you?
What
What they come to the already saying oh no like when somebody's a hermit and they won't like leave their house. What's that called? Oh
Yeah, I don't know. Recluse. Ah there it is my man. I mean I'm always trying to remember shit. So yeah recluse
They became recluse and the entire hat the house came like a cat house. It was really disgusting
I know now they did lose their money Amanda, but not they're not full Kennedys
You know the boobies, right Amanda?
Yeah, the movie is like Mark Simpson's name. They lost their money Drew Barrymore plater
gray God right and she's like a weird old woman who like lives in that house
and she yeah yes I've been there I'm into that house she lost her hair Drew
Barrymore the young one it's the two it's the mother and the daughter and she
was the one that was supposed to marry John F Kennedy just so you know
She like fucked it. She like she was getting drunk too much and then like the Kennedy's like no no no
She's not good for your political run Mary. Yeah, you know
We are acting so the Kennedy doesn't charge of HHS. This is part of that family
Yes, you know that stop trolling. No, no, no, no, because I can't stop it Jonathan
You teach me so much more than I teach you you know that he's part of that family
He doesn't act like you know, I'm gonna start talking about you getting lab dances unless you start
you like that
What's his name? That's not a troll the guy. That's the head of the agent which is naming him. It's his brother Kennedy. Yeah, do you like him?
You know much more about political stuff like you always
vocal
Representatives, you know like everybody's representatives in that area and all that shit not a man of those mortals. I know but you're impressive
Oh, uh, yeah, I'm taking a break though. Uh, after I'm taking a
He's the one that got shot right in this during the civil rights, right? Like Martin Luther King, right the original
Yeah, his son. Is that what Amanda's saying?
Oh, I don't know. I'll see
Amanda, he shouldn't be a he shouldn't be a Kennedy. He's a
Man, just probably a huge fan of like JFK
Just saying you're probably a big fan of them
So after tells you someone so far it's been a hot sticky summer
just working well honestly I've been trying to take a break from here and take like
8-9 days, my girlfriend and I broke up
Yeah, I heard you said that
Lord fights the dust
Wait, is there any way you could get back together making that we're just talking to be honest
I'm not trying to be rude or vulgar, but that's the truth. Got it understood
Uh, are you watching the Yankees baseball or anything like that?
So I'm I'm a huge so I like the Yankees Rangers Buffalo Bills and the Knicks and I was like I can tell you so much
shit about the Yankees from like night like I don't know 96 to like
2015 but I really I'm a soccer football guy football football like I'm a Bills guy man
I can tell you anything about the Bills
Huge soccer fan. I like Chelsea Rexham
Just wait what wait when you say big soccer, you mean a man for soccer or European?
I mean soccer in general the sport. Okay, I mean a mate. That's a football question when you say American football
Yeah, that's funny how you reverse that question like yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's how I
Oh, sorry. I got that was interesting. Yeah, it was that's why when I say my two favorite sports, they're football and football
What football do you mean North American or European sport that makes sense to call it football, right?
Not the American version
Because you know how many like things and terms we have in our society is just because we got our
Independence from Britain think about that. Why do we call football football?
Think about it. Fuck
Because we kicked the ball with their feet.
You don't though, like, I'm talking about American football.
Why do we call that football?
I don't know.
Exactly.
They should have called it American rules football.
Like, that's what they should call it.
Like Aussie rules football, American rules football.
Like handball.
Yes, that's another good point.
But we call it football because.
of the independence from Britain.
And like we couldn't have the same name as them, right?
Cricket and then we could baseball.
And cricket didn't become popular in America,
baseball did.
It's just like, cricket's actually way more exciting
than baseball, just to let you know.
A lot of things are more exciting than baseball.
I know.
Cricket is so cool because there's no foul balls. You know what a foul ball is in baseball?
Yeah, there's no foul balls in cricket. That's why it's like Mark
So if you hit the ball that goes you hit the bat and it goes behind you
That's you know, that's in play and cricket you run like imagine that so much cooler
So you can suck and play no no no no no anyway, but that's funny
Yeah, my boy
All right, I'm gonna mute up. Let I was gonna go crazy talking a little bit crazy. You're gonna go crazy
Tittany
Another one bite the dust and another one and another one and another one bites the dust